music
音楽
applause
拍手
Li Xiaoyuan Li Tebin Researcher
李暁源 李哲斌 研究者
And our Academia Sinica
そして私たちの中央研究院
Li Renhui's flamboyant potential
李仁輝の華やかな可能性
Cai Duoxiong
蔡多雄
And ladies and gentlemen and students
そして紳士淑女の皆様、そして学生の皆様
Goodnight everybody
おやすみ皆さん
Glad I came to see so many people today
今日はたくさんの人に来てもらえて嬉しかったです
Come and listen to the speech of Researcher Li Tebin
李哲斌研究員の講演を聞きに来てください。
This is what I have hosted many times
これは私が何度も主催しているものです
This is the first time I want to come to you
君のところに行きたいのは初めてだ
and it's not done yet
そしてそれはまだ終わっていない
Because many people are in other halls
他のホールにもたくさんの人がいるから
watch TV wall
テレビの壁を見る
So thank you all for coming today
それでは、今日は来ていただきありがとうございます
I think everyone cares about their own advice
誰もが自分のアドバイスを気にしていると思います
In particular, Taiwan's social economy is developing more and more
特に台湾の社会経済はますます発展しています。
When everyone's life is getting longer
みんなの寿命が長くなったとき
It is inevitable that you will face the problem of so-called dementia.
いわゆる認知症の問題に直面することは避けられません。
or our family has dementia
あるいは私たちの家族は認知症です
everyone cares
誰もが気にする
Hope to care more about our family or ourselves
家族や自分自身のことをもっと大切にしたいと思っています
So today we also have a special understanding of our researcher Zhou Yan
そこで今日、私たちは研究者の周燕氏について特別な理解を得ました。
Very distinguished scholar Li Xiaoyuan
非常に著名な学者、李暁源氏
A special researcher is here to share with you
特別な研究者がここで皆さんに情報を提供します
Lectures on Amnesia and Dementia
健忘症と認知症に関する講義
Researcher Li Xiaoyuan actually
研究者のリー・シャオユアン氏は実際に
It's early when we sex fellows
私たちがセックスするのは早いです
He came here in 1983
彼は1983年にここに来ました
I remember it was Academician Cai Zhongyong
蔡仲永学者だったと記憶しています
We had the Institute of Biomedical Sciences
生物医科学研究所がありました
just in the preparatory stage
ちょうど準備段階
I was also at that time
私もその時はそうでした
also here
ここもまた
So we're pretty old colleagues
つまり、私たちはかなり古い同僚です
An old colleague of nearly 30 years
30年近くの古い同僚
However, researcher Li Xiaoyuan's academic achievements
しかし、研究者の李暁源氏の学術的業績は、
explain to me more
もっと説明してください
he is
彼は
His main field of study is learning
彼の主な研究分野は学習です
Discussion on the protective mechanism of memory and nervous system diseases
記憶および神経系疾患の防御機構に関する考察
Dr. Li graduated from
リー博士は卒業しました
Graduated from the Department of Psychology, National Chengchi University
国立政治大学心理学部卒業
Later to the University of California
その後カリフォルニア大学へ
Neuroscience Institute at UC San Diego
カリフォルニア大学サンディエゴ校神経科学研究所
received a Ph.D.
博士号を取得しました
and in
そしてで
Green
緑
is a year conducted by the Sendiego Department of Psychiatry
センディエゴ精神科が実施する年です
postdoctoral research
博士研究員
Then in 1983, he returned to work in our holy hospital
そして 1983 年に、彼は私たちの聖なる病院での仕事に戻りました。
that in these thirty years
この30年間に
He has published nearly a hundred papers during the international academic period
彼は国際的な学術期間中に100本近くの論文を発表しました。
and it's all important
そしてそれはすべて重要です
When he was chatting with me just now, he said
たった今私と話しているとき、彼はこう言いました。
The first time he came back to see the paper written in
彼が初めて戻ってきて、書かれた紙を見たのは、
When Taiwan ROC of Academia Sinica
台湾中華民国中央研究院のとき
There is a feeling of caring for the country
国を思いやる気持ちがある
This is when we would like to be in the United States
こういう時こそ私たちはアメリカにいたいと思うのです
He actually had a good show in America for us in America
彼は実際にアメリカで私たちのためにアメリカで素晴らしいショーを見せてくれました
But he still feels
しかし、彼はまだ感じています
he should go back to this one
彼はこれに戻るべきだ
His favorite place to make his dedication
彼の献身を捧げるお気に入りの場所
Really amazing thirty years one day
30年も一日って本当にすごいですね
did a lot of excellent research on this one
これに関して多くの優れた研究を行いました
Dr. Lee he once obtained
かつて手に入れたリー博士
Top Ten Outstanding Young Women in the Tenth World of the Republic of China
中華民国の第10世界における優秀な若い女性トップ10
And the winner of the National Science Council's Distinguished Award
そして全米学術会議の特別賞を受賞した
There are also academic awards from the Ministry of Education for special research fellows
特別研究員には文部科学省からの学術賞もある
It is also the outstanding Baekwei of the Dynamic National Chengchi University
ダイナミック国立政治大学の優秀な白偉でもあります
is an alumni
卒業生です
Then a chair professor at National Chengchi University
その後、国立政治大学の主席教授に就任
He has won several cutting-edge scientific research awards from the National Science Council
彼は米国科学会議からいくつかの最先端の科学研究賞を受賞しています。
Cutting-edge scientific research is not easy
最先端の科学研究は簡単ではない
Probably people in the life science community in China
おそらく中国のライフサイエンスコミュニティの人々でしょう
About Top 1%
上位1%について
Top 1% still get this award
上位 1% は引き続きこの賞を獲得します
Then Dr. Li won several cutting-edge research projects
その後、リー博士はいくつかの最先端の研究プロジェクトを獲得しました。
All in academic research
すべては学術研究において
Not only recognized domestically
国内で認知されているだけではなく、
All of our cutting-edge research is sent abroad to please
私たちの最先端の研究はすべて海外に送られ、お客様に喜んでいただけるようになっています。
Reserved short review
予約済みの短いレビュー
He has won several cutting-edge academic research awards
彼はいくつかの最先端の学術研究賞を受賞しています
it's really not easy
それは本当に簡単ではありません
today we are very happy
今日私たちはとても幸せです
He came to introduce us to today's topic
彼は私たちに今日の話題を紹介しに来ました
I think everyone is curious about memory
誰もが記憶に興味があると思います
In fact, people's memory has timely memory
実は人の記憶にはタイムリーな記憶がある
short term memory vs long term memory
短期記憶と長期記憶
i remember i used to take care of
昔お世話になったのを覚えています
go to a nursing home to take care of
介護のために老人ホームに行く
some old man
ある老人
There is a Catholic Lord
カトリックの主がいる
according to our catholic cross old place
私たちのカトリックの十字架の古い場所によると
It's funny that he can sing to you
彼があなたに向かって歌えるなんて面白いですね
The story of Jiaocheng looks like this
聊城の物語はこんな感じ
Not a single word is dropped
一言も省略されません
but he forgot to say
しかし彼は言うのを忘れた
He said I still need to eat
彼はまだ食べないといけないと言った
But he has eaten for the third time
しかし、彼は3回目を食べました
so his recent memory is great
だから彼の最近の記憶力は素晴らしいです
But long term memory is good
しかし、長期記憶は良いです
so he can remember
彼が覚えられるように
in the church before
この前の教会で
Activities with us
私たちとの活動
very detailed memory
非常に詳細な記憶
but he doesn't remember
しかし彼は覚えていない
The wife just left has hugged him
出て行ったばかりの妻が彼を抱きしめた
but also to hug the second time like this
でもこうして二度目のハグも
so there are a lot of weird
だから変なものがたくさんある
such a reaction
そのような反応
But this also shows the
しかし、これはまた、
Taiwan is like what we just said
台湾は今言ったようなものです
The star description is getting longer and longer
星の説明がどんどん長くなっていきます
then some people
それから何人かの人々
unfortunately going into geriatrics
残念ながら老人科に進むことになりました
What is the reason for the treatment of the elderly?
高齢者を治療する理由は何ですか？
what is memory
記憶とは何ですか
Then what is the mechanism of the nerve
では神経の仕組みはどうなっているのか
can we prevent them
それらを防ぐことはできますか
or how do we face
あるいはどうやって立ち向かうのか
Neuropathy
神経障害
I think everyone is concerned today
今日はみんな心配してると思うよ
let's not talk
話さないようにしましょう
let's give a round of applause
拍手を送りましょう
Come welcome our protagonist today
今日の主人公を歓迎してください
Li Xiaolin
リー・シャオリン
Thanks
ありがとう
Thank you Vice President for the invitation
副社長、ご招待ありがとうございました
Introduction to the Vice President
副社長の紹介
In fact, of course the deputy dean has already explained what I want to say.
実際、私が言いたいことは副学部長がもちろん説明済みです。
The content of the first Sly
最初のスライの内容
In fact, the vice president also understands
実は副社長も理解してくれています
Then my research work at the Institute of Biology
それから生物学研究所での研究活動
My own field of research is about learning and memory
私自身の研究分野は学習と記憶に関するものです
can you hear
聞こえますか
tell me if you can't hear
聞こえなかったら言ってください
Over the past few years
過去数年にわたり
I'll also talk about using the animal model
動物モデルの使用についても説明します
Do substantive research
実質的な調査を行う
Hope especially Azehai's certified research
特にAzehaiの認定された研究を希望します
Hope to be able to have a little bit of human society
少しでも人間社会になれれば幸いです
present a little evidence
少しの証拠を提示する
A little bit more help and expressions
もう少しヘルプと表現
then i know you may be right
それならあなたが正しいかも知れません
I am more interested in substantively proving this listening method
この聴取方法を実質的に証明することはさらに興味深いことです
but i started
でも私は始めました
I still have to introduce
まだまだ紹介しなければいけないのですが
Memory and the basic structure of nerve cells
記憶と神経細胞の基本構造
and our brains
そして私たちの脳
a basic structure
基本的な構造
Because these foundations must have been
なぜなら、これらの基盤は、
wait a minute and listen to me
ちょっと待って私の話を聞いてください
You can better understand the administration and work
行政や仕事のことがよりよく理解できる
that's in all my fantasies
それは私のすべての空想の中にあります
If I have this in the lower right corner
これが右下隅にある場合
Logo's
ロゴ
it's me
それは私です
The work done by Academia Sinica
中央研究院による研究
if not
そうでない場合
In fact, some of them I learned from textbooks or
実際、それらのいくつかは教科書や
YouTube is not found on internal videos
内部ビデオに YouTube が見つかりません
Because I am on this occasion
この機会に私もいるから
I can't speak very professionally
あまり専門的に話すことはできません
that will sound a bit strenuous
それは少し大変に聞こえるでしょう
So I am a relatively popular family content
だから私は比較的人気のあるファミリーコンテンツです
This will just be over
これはもうすぐ終わります
Human memory is divided into simple
人間の記憶は単純に分けられます
short-term memory long-term memory
分即時記憶短期記憶長期記憶
This instant memory is in minutes
この瞬間の記憶は分単位です
even seconds seconds instant seconds
偶数秒 秒 インスタント秒
Do you think human beings need a lot of them?
人間にはそれらがたくさん必要だと思いますか？
for long time
長時間用
I give two examples
2つの例を挙げます
You are assuming today that you are going to have a meeting outside one day
あなたは今日、いつか外で会議をすることを想定しています
Why do you say you suddenly remembered
なぜ突然思い出したと言うのですか
Today may be good audio and video
今日は音声も映像も良いかもしれない
but you forgot to prepare a gift for him
でもあなたは彼へのプレゼントを準備するのを忘れました
so you might want to find a florist right away
すぐにお花屋さんを探したほうがいいかもしれません
or cake shop
またはケーキ屋さん
Then make a phone call and ask him to bring this gift
それから電話して、この贈り物を持ってくるように頼みます
Or send flowers or send cakes to friends
友達に花を送ったり、ケーキを送ったりすることもできます
this example
この例
Now everyone's attitude towards sliding mobile phones is not accurate
今、携帯電話をスライドさせることに対するみんなの態度は正確ではありません
but earlier
でももっと前に
you might hit a trombone table
トロンボーン台に当たるかもしれない
Or look up the phone number of a nearby flower shop
または、近くの花屋の電話番号を調べてください。
For example, 37681534 speaks casually
たとえば、37681534 はカジュアルに話します。
Then after you get this number
この番号を取得したら
you just call this number
この番号に電話するだけです
Then ask him to help you send the flowers to what address
次に、花をどの住所に送るかを手伝ってもらいます
Let's say this florist isn't your usual phone number
この花屋がいつも使っている電話番号ではないとしましょう
It is that you occasionally encounter this situation and need to use
時々このような状況に遭遇し、使用する必要があるということです
Then you usually after this call
通常、この電話の後、
how long you don't need a few minutes
数分も必要ないくらい
You should slowly forget this phone number
この電話番号はゆっくり忘れてください
this is correct
これは正しいです
or remember the full
または完全に覚えておいてください
Because it's not one you need to use often
頻繁に使うものではないので、
This type of memory is called immediate memory
このタイプの記憶は即時記憶と呼ばれます
In fact, these two lives often need to
実際、これら 2 つの人生では、多くの場合、
That short-term memory is another
その短期記憶は別のものです
Conceived by a little guide
小さな指導の下で考案されました
This range is
この範囲は
There are too many examples
例が多すぎる
there are students doing
やっている学生がいます
our students
私たちの生徒たち
when we were students taking exams
私たちが受験生のとき
last note face down back to back
最後の音符を裏返しにして背中合わせに
before the exam
そして試験へ
You must recite it, right?
それを暗唱しなければなりませんね？
overcome exam
試験を乗り越える
after the exam
試験の後
Usually several two to three weeks
通常、数週間から 3 週間
usually a lot of money back
通常は多額のお金が戻ってくる
just forget
忘れちゃった
that's normal
それは正常です
I was normal with you just now
さっきまであなたとは普通にいたよ
and it's important
そしてそれは重要です
what should be forgotten is to forget
忘れるべきものは忘れることだ
because not everything
すべてではないので
let us always remember
常に思い出しましょう
This is for our neurovascular
これは私たちの神経血管のためのものです
It's a tiring thing
それは疲れる事だ
unless the matter is
問題がない限り
Do you think you should keep it forever
永久に保存すべきだと思いますか
that memory is often
その記憶はしばしば
related to our survival
私たちの生存に関わる
then long term memory
それから長期記憶
This is how we humans compare
これが私たち人間が比較する方法です
comparison is emphasizing
比較が強調している
several decades
数十年
I can say I'm old now
もう年をとったと言える
will be like when i was a teenager
十代の頃のようになるだろう
what happened when you were twenty
あなたが二十歳のときに何が起こったのか
why these things
なぜこれらのことを
i will remember for so long
とても長い間覚えています
then for example
それなら例えば
for example
例えば
This machine is sometimes
この機械は時々、
It's not good. For example, when the 921 earthquake occurred
それは良くないですね、例えば921地震が起きた時。
Puli Earthquake
埔里地震
If at that time
もしあのとき
people who saw this disaster
この惨状を目撃した人々
long term memory
長期記憶
next time you come to Puli
次回埔里に来るときは
or you don't go to pulley
さもなければ滑車に行かない
see these two words
この 2 つの単語を見てください
you may recall that memory
その記憶を思い出すかもしれません
This is long term memory
これは長期記憶です
Just like what happened on the MRT recently
最近MRTで起こったようなこと
He can't forget the people he saw at the scene
彼は現場で見た人々のことを忘れられない
In fact, his age is what he still remembers
実際、彼の年齢は今でも覚えている
So roughly divided into these three
大きく分けるとこの3つになります
Then divide the time like this
では、このように時間を区切ってください
that his history
彼の経歴を
Usually our executive memory is stimulated first
通常、私たちの実行記憶が最初に刺激されます
Come on, this stimulus is usually in terms of what we have nothing to do
さあ、この刺激は通常、私たちが何もすることがないことに関するものです
Children today, nose smell, morality, etc.
今の子どもたち、鼻の臭い、道徳など。
This is usually based on our senses
これは通常、私たちの感覚に基づいています
This stimulus goes through a filtering system
この刺激はフィルタリングシステムを通過します
and then into our immediate memory
そして私たちの直接の記憶の中に
I call this filtering
私はこれをフィルタリングと呼んでいます
Let me give you an example
例を挙げてみましょう
If you are at Taipei Main Station today
今日台北駅にいる場合
Except the MRT station
MRT駅を除く
a lot of people walking around
たくさんの人が歩き回っています
what we usually do
私たちが普段何をしているのか
we're going to do this
私たちはこれをやります
Let's see if I can find anyone
誰か見つけられるか見てみましょう
The common sense is to let the human-like part of this movie begin to pass
常識としては、この映画の人間らしい部分は過ぎ去ってもらうことだ
unless you wait and see a person
待って人に会わない限り
So this category is
ということで、このカテゴリーは
Our nervous system does a lot of physical work
私たちの神経系は多くの肉体的な仕事をします
let our feelings mature
私たちの気持ちを成熟させましょう
exposed to these stimuli
これらの刺激にさらされると
after the vast majority
大多数の後
and was thrown out too much
そして捨てられすぎた
because we don't need to be specific about everything
すべてを具体的にする必要はないので、
Dupei is hungry and mature, continue to do it
Dupei はお腹が空いていて成熟しているので、続けてください
have something in immediate memory
すぐに記憶に残っているものがある
or you may
あるいは、あなたは
Oops, I suddenly saw a friend
おっと、突然友達に会った
This friend met 20 years ago
この友人は20年前に会った
but there may be no connection
でも繋がりがないかもしれない
So say hello and go
だから挨拶して行ってください
you might even think of other names
他の名前も考えられるかもしれません
immediate memory
即時記憶
Immediate memory then passes through our nervous system
即時の記憶は神経系を通過します。
Filtering Mechanisms of the Nervous System
神経系のフィルタリングメカニズム
then filter out
それからフィルターで取り除きます
there are some short doses
短い用量もいくつかあります
this kind of time is a bit short
こんな時間はちょっと短い
For example, what the teacher said in class
たとえば、授業中に先生が言ったこと
if you don't know how to communicate
コミュニケーション方法がわからない場合
but honestly
でも正直に言うと
That is to say, this thing is very important
つまり、これはとても重要なことなのです
I may take one of the exams and accept the exam
いずれかの試験を受けて、試験を受けることができます
then you will pay a little attention
それなら少しは注意してください
So some things are selectively moved to short-term memory
したがって、いくつかの事柄は選択的に短期記憶に移動されます
and some more filtered
さらにフィルタリングされたもの
long term memory
長期記憶
There are some things that are very important to human survival
人間が生きていく上でとても大切なことがあります
very influential very important
非常に影響力がある 非常に重要
sometimes skip this
時々これをスキップします
From immediate memory to long-term memory
即時記憶から長期記憶へ
For example, where is the screen like that seen on the prison
たとえば、刑務所で見られるような画面はどこにありますか
Then I want to talk about the mechanism of this filter in the human
次に、人間のこのフィルターのメカニズムについて話したいと思います。
is very important
はとても重要です
That is to say, our nerve cells
つまり、私たちの神経細胞は、
No need to register every stimulus
すべての刺激を登録する必要はありません
we talk about register
レジスターについて話します
we don't need to do this
私たちはこれをする必要はありません
No need because if that's the case
必要ない、そうなら
our neurons get tired
私たちのニューロンは疲れます
but this phenomenon
しかしこの現象
Its importance in psychiatry
精神医学におけるその重要性
means you know something about this
あなたはこれについて何かを知っていることを意味します
Of course I'm not that psychiatrist
もちろん私は精神科医ではありません
but i know this phenomenon
でも私はこの現象を知っています
That is to say, some patients with schizophrenia
つまり、統合失調症患者の中には、
He actually has no intellectual problems
彼は実際には知的問題を抱えていない
There is no problem with his intelligence and his administrative memory
彼の知能と管理上の記憶には問題はありません
but he
でも彼は
you probably know
あなたはおそらく知っています
Some mental and professional patients
一部の精神疾患および専門職患者
There will be things like auditory hallucinations and fantasies
幻聴や空想のようなものもあるでしょう
he can feel and see
彼は感じて見ることができる
Hearing a lot of sounds or images
音や映像がたくさん聞こえる
Actually we are
実は私たちは
We ourselves, ordinary people can't feel it
私たち一般人には感じられない
that reason is because
その理由は
One reason is because patients like this
理由の 1 つは、患者がこれを好むことです。
The filtration system of his neurovascular cavity is defective
彼の神経血管腔の濾過システムには欠陥がある
So he can't rule out some
したがって、彼はいくつかのことを除外することはできません
irrelevant stimulus
無関係な刺激
he takes all the stimuli
彼はあらゆる刺激を受け入れる
Lots of stimuli are registered
たくさんの刺激が登録されています
so he'll see what you can't see
そうすれば彼はあなたに見えないものを見るでしょう
hear something you can't hear
聞こえないものを聞く
Then such a person is actually very tired
そうすると、そういう人は実はすごく疲れているんです
Because his nerves and blood cavity are tired
神経と血管が疲れているからです
something bloody
血まみれの何か
So suppose you have someone who knows
それで、知っている人がいるとします
or your friend or something
またはあなたの友人か何か
Such a phenomenon is actually
このような現象は実際にあります
long
長さ
The phenomenon is actually a little bit
この現象は実はちょっとしたもので、
a little bit dangerous
少し危険です
as far as i would suggest
私が提案する限り
I should look at the meaning of lower body Hengge
下半身ヘンゲの意味を見てみよう
short term advice he goes to short term advice everywhere
短期的なアドバイス 彼はどこにでも短期的なアドバイスを求めに行きます
For example, some of the sex and areas of our brain
たとえば、性別と脳の領域の一部
wait a minute i will introduce
ちょっと待ってください、紹介します
Long-term memory is also stored in long-term memory
長期記憶も長期記憶に保存される
Our long term memory is stored in our big old flat city
私たちの長期記憶は、古くて大きな平らな街に保存されています
right in your skull
あなたの頭蓋骨の中に
Now we are knocking on the skull of Hehai
今、我々はヘハイの頭蓋骨を叩いている
Below it is Tate Old Pingcheng
その下はテート・オールド・ピンチェンです
wait a minute i'll show you
ちょっと待ってください、見せます
Our memory is stored there
私たちの記憶はそこに保存されています
we humans
私たち人間
not only humans
人間だけではない
including rats
ネズミを含む
mouse
ねずみ
This is not enough animal
これでは十分な動物ではありません
where memories are formed
記憶が形成される場所
See where memories are stored
思い出がどこに保存されているかを確認する
are different
異なっています
good division of labor
良い分業
I'll talk about it later
それについては後で話します
just like that
まさにそのように
but today if something
でも今日何かあったら
You need to retrieve it from long-term memory
長期記憶から呼び出す必要がある
for example
例えば
When you go through Jiangzi's reminder to fight again
再び戦うようにとのキョン子の警告を乗り越えるとき
20 years later
20年後
you may still remember that scene
あなたはまだそのシーンを覚えているかもしれません
This is a way to retrieve it from long-term memory
これは長期記憶からそれを取り出す方法です
Retrieval of short-term memory
短期記憶の検索
for example
例えば
You memorized for a long time
あなたは長い間暗記していました
There will be an exam in a week
一週間後に試験があります
so when you take the exam
だから試験を受けるときに
see those memories
それらの思い出を見てください
this is what i carried
これは私が運んだものです
So you figure out how to store it from short-term memory
それであなたはそれを短期記憶から保存する方法を見つけます
you take what you have carried on your back
あなたは背負ってきたものを受け取ります
Take it out to write the test paper
取り出してテスト用紙を書く
So it goes like this basically a shorthand
基本的に略記すると次のようになります
this is the relationship
これが関係です
And here is an important memory
そして大切な思い出がここにあります
Which means only we humans have only long-term memories of getting out of town
つまり、私たち人間だけが町を出たときの長期記憶しか持っていないということになります。
required for the synthesis of new proteins
新しいタンパク質の合成に必要
We have neuroses in our brains, proteins in belly parts
私たちの脳には神経症があり、腹部にはタンパク質が存在します
But if the protein is a new protein
しかし、そのタンパク質が新しいタンパク質であれば、
DNA
DNA
It is a step like deoxynucleic acid nucleic acid
デオキシ核酸・核酸のようなステップです
make protein
タンパク質を作る
Only long-term memory requires new protein synthesis
長期記憶のみが新たなタンパク質合成を必要とする
None of these short-term immediate memories are needed
これらの短期即時記憶はどれも必要ありません
synthesis of new proteins
新しいタンパク質の合成
it's you in the nerve cells
神経細胞の中にいるのはあなたです
Some modifications to existing proteins are enough
既存のタンパク質にいくつかの変更を加えるだけで十分です
other memories out of town
街の外でのその他の思い出
first have other this concept
まず他のこのコンセプトを持ってください
good
良い
Then let's introduce other nerve cells
それでは他の神経細胞を紹介しましょう
Our nerve cells generally look like this
私たちの神経細胞は一般的に次のようになります
I mean the nerve cells in the brain
脳の神経細胞のことです
this is its cell body
これがその細胞体です
The most important area is the nucleus
最も重要な領域は核です
Basically did not stand in such a big bottom
基本的にそんな大きな底には立たなかった
Its body will be bigger
体も大きくなるよ
Elements related to our life information and software
私たちの生活情報やソフトウェアに関わる要素
Everything in the DNA is inside the nucleus
DNAのすべては核の中にあります
Heart protein core needs this too
心臓タンパク質コアにもこれが必要です
it's on the periphery of its cell body
それは細胞体の周縁部にあります
There are many such branches
そういう支店はたくさんあるよ
like its name tree diagram
その名前の樹形図のように
It just looks like a big tree
まるで大きな木のように見えます
trunk with branches
枝のある幹
Then branch and then have small branches
その後分岐し、さらに小さな分岐が発生します
really like a tree
本当に木のように
So Chinese is translated into a tree diagram
つまり中国語は樹形図に翻訳されます
Then what
じゃあ何
When the outside world came across this tree diagram once
かつて外の世界がこの樹形図に出会ったとき
This cell produces some electrical signals
この細胞はいくつかの電気信号を生成します
The electrical signal follows the axis diagram
電気信号は軸図に従います
pass to the end of a mysterious situation
不可解な状況の終わりに至る
where's the end of it
終わりはどこですか
It's also like our big tree
それは私たちの大きな木のようでもあります
under the tree
木の下で
like the branch under the chair
椅子の下の枝のように
so it has many branches
なので支店が多いです
For each branch it has this called
ブランチごとにこれを呼び出す
it has a bump
でこぼこがある
We say it contains a lot of chemicals
化学物質が多く含まれていると言われています
wolf-like thing
狼のようなもの
when it hits the magnet
磁石に当たると
This potential signal transmits the message to the terminal
この電位差信号はメッセージを端末に送信します。
And these branches at the end
そして最後にあるこれらの枝
Then make a link with the next nerve cell diagram
次に、次の神経細胞図とリンクします。
I'll wait and there's a video I need to show you
待ってるよ、見せたいビデオがあるんだ
That's how the message gets passed
そうやってメッセージは伝わるんだよ
Most of our nerve cells
私たちの神経細胞のほとんどは
Many of our nerve cells are
私たちの神経細胞の多くは、
Then the outer layer of the bread is called Suiqiao
パンの外側の層は水橋と呼ばれます
it's some plowed gills
それは耕されたエラです
some glycols
いくつかのグリコール
some glycolipid stuff
いくつかの糖脂質のもの
sugar-stimulated lipids
糖激化脂質類的東西
Our general axis graph transmission speed is per second
一般的な軸グラフの送信速度は 1 秒あたりです
0.5 to 2 meters
0.5～2メートル
also very happy
とても幸せです
A person's body length is so fat in one second
人の体の長さは1秒でこんなに太ります
one long so fast
とても早くて長い
But with the tuned axis plot it passes to
しかし、調整された軸プロットでは、次のようになります。
You can see 120 meters in one second
1秒で120メートル先が見える
very fast
とても早い
This class of cells with axis plots
軸プロットを持つこのクラスのセル
Usually during, for example, sensorimotor heatstroke
通常、たとえば感覚運動熱中症のとき
For example, if someone scolds you
たとえば、誰かに叱られたとします。
You won't call that great
そんなに素晴らしいとは言えないだろう
do you cry after half an hour
30分後に泣きますか？
or angry
または怒っている
This message travels fast
このメッセージは速く伝わります
someone hit you or something
誰かがあなたか何かを殴った
you can run right away or go back
すぐに逃げることも、戻ることもできます
you won't wait long
長く待つことはありません
I'll be back in 20 minutes
20分以内に戻ります
This kind of conduction is conduction with tune
この種の指揮は調子のある指揮です
know a little bit
少し知っています
I just said that we have electricity
電気があるって言ったばかりだよ
This is where the action potential starts
ここから活動電位が始まります
then pass the signal on
それから信号を渡します
So our brain basically has two nerve cells
つまり、私たちの脳には基本的に2つの神経細胞があります
two features
2つの特徴
One is electricity, the other is chemistry
一つは電気、もう一つは化学
When electrical signals are transmitted to nerve cells
電気信号が神経細胞に伝わるとき
If there is a severed hand, there will be a release of chemicals
手を切断すると化学物質が放出される
release to the next nerve cell
次の神経細胞に放出する
Then I said, there will be a potential when stimulated
それから私は言いました、刺激されると可能性があります
After the electric potential this nerve cell
この神経細胞は電位の後に
This period of time is very important, called the recovery period
この期間は非常に重要であり、回復期間と呼ばれます。
that is to say during this time
つまりこの間
it will be better than normal
通常よりも良くなります
The normal center is not easily stimulated
正常中枢は刺激されにくい
so react
それで反応する
It means that our nerve cells
それは私たちの神経細胞が
In fact, once you work
実際、一度働いてみると、
After it needs to activate, it needs to rest
アクティブにする必要がある場合は、休ませる必要があります
at this stage
この段階では
You just give it a stronger stimulus
より強い刺激を与えるだけです
it won't respond either
それも反応しません
this is our nerve cell
これは私たちの神経細胞です
a protection mechanism against itself
それ自体に対する保護メカニズム
Because it can't stand on the face all the time
ずっと顔の上に立っていられないから
active, always active
アクティブ、常にアクティブ
always in an active state
常にアクティブな状態にある
then resting
それから休む
it's slowly resting
ゆっくり休んでいます
Then start preparing for the next stimulus
そして次の刺激に向けて準備を始める
Here is a schematic
これが概略図です
just tell us
教えてください
This nerve cell conducts electricity
この神経細胞は電気を伝導します
send the message under here
ここの下にメッセージを送信してください
And below this is another neuron
そしてこの下には別のニューロンがあります
place of tree soil
木の土の場所
Let's zoom in on this white space
この白い部分を拡大してみましょう
that's it
それでおしまい
wire vesicles
ワイヤーベシクル
These cysts are stimulating in terms of
これらの嚢胞は次の点で刺激を与えます。
it will break
壊れるだろう
Then some chemicals in it
それから、その中に化学物質が含まれています
These round red
この丸い赤は
it will be released
それはリリースされます
released
解放された
it will go down
それは下がります
On the tree soil of the next nerve cell
次の神経細胞の木の土の上に
on a specific receiver
特定の受信機で
This is very important
これはとても重要です
this particular idea
この特定のアイデア
They are concepts with structure and function
それらは構造と機能を備えた概念です
This is called structure function
これを構造関数といいます
it won't just find a place
それは場所を見つけるだけではありません
do it
やれ
not like the wind blows
風が吹くようなものではない
this matter is very important
この問題はとても重要です
it just does the wrong place
それは間違った場所をやっているだけです
The message transmission after it is all wrong
全てが間違っていた後のメッセージ送信
Then look at where its nerve cells are
次に、神経細胞がどこにあるかを見てください。
What kind of problems will it cause us humans?
それは私たち人間にどのような問題を引き起こすのでしょうか？
This middle control place is called Synapse
この中間制御の場所はシナプスと呼ばれます
Synapse in Chinese
シナプス中国語の意味
synapse
シナプス
I'll show you later
後で見せます
the signal is like this
信号はこんな感じです
Nerve cells communicate one by one
神経細胞は一つ一つ通信します
I don’t know why this video was released yesterday
なぜこのビデオが昨日公開されたのかわかりません
It was a bit broken when I released it just now.
さっき出した時はちょっと壊れてました。
so i show you this
だからこれを見せます
a piece of words
一言
So I think the lights should be able not to look back
だから光は振り返らないようにすべきだと思う
this one you can see
これはあなたが見ることができます
wait a minute i animate it
ちょっと待ってください、アニメーション化します
you'll see under a microscope
顕微鏡で見るとわかります
this nerve cell
この神経細胞
when it sticks out
それがはみ出したとき
The end of the axis chart sticks out
軸グラフの端が飛び出ている
as slowly
ゆっくりと
Connect with this plasticine of nerve cells
この神経細胞の粘土で接続します。
Then how to pass the message over
では、どうやってメッセージを伝えるかというと、
very interesting
とても興味深い
really photographed under a microscope
実際に顕微鏡で撮影したもの
you can take a look
見てみることができます
See? Shake hands
わかりますか? 握手してください
The phenomenal quantity of connections astounding in their inter-ca-see and complexity eventually number in the trillions.
その相互接続性と複雑さにおいて驚くべき接続の驚異的な量は、最終的には数兆に達します。
It's these connections that allow neuron to neuron communication, the basis of all great activity.
これらの接続により、すべての偉大な活動の基礎となるニューロン間のコミュニケーションが可能になります。
Neurons talk to each other in a two-step process using electricity and chemistry, electrical...
ニューロンは、電気と化学、電気を使用する 2 段階のプロセスで相互に通信します。
Thank you.
ありがとう。
For memory, I just need to talk about a psychedelic film
記念に、サイケデリックな映画について話したいと思います
tell a very simple theory
非常に単純な理論を語る
But this theory is so important because
しかし、この理論は非常に重要なので、
1949 I don't quite remember now
1949年 今ではよく覚えていない
Is this from Spain or from which country?
これはスペインのものですか、それともどこの国のものですか?
The Great Chinese Teaching of Neuropathy
神経障害に関する中国の偉大な教え
Turn it up in Chinese
中国語で上げてください
You know there are long and long in the book
この本には長いことがたくさんあるのはご存知でしょう
He proposed a consolidation theory
彼は統合理論を提案した
That is to say, your Chinese can be thought of as solidification theory
つまり、あなたの中国語は固まり理論と考えられます。
That is why a neuropathic cell
だからこそ神経障害細胞は
Connect with another neuron to exchange ideas
別のニューロンと接続してアイデアを交換する
Then finally memory can be formed
そしてついに記憶が形成される
What is his hypothesis
彼の仮説は何ですか
A when this nerve cell receives a stimulus
この神経細胞が刺激を受けると
make it exciting
刺激的なものにする
it sends some exciting news
それはいくつかのエキサイティングなニュースを送ります
to the B cell
B細胞に
B then sends this message
B はこのメッセージを送信します
to the neuron of C
Cのニューロンに
I think these neurons are all brains
これらのニューロンはすべて脳だと思う
It has nothing to do with the arm
腕とか関係ないよ
Then C this nerve cell
それから C この神経細胞
Pass this exciting message to D
この刺激的なメッセージを D に伝えてください
D will pass back to A
DはAに戻ります
So talk about Lanlan Huihui Lanlan Huihui
ランラン・ホイホイについて話しましょう ランラン・ホイホイについて
This is more formal
こちらの方がフォーマルです
just a simple idea
ただの単純なアイデア
There is a group of nerve cells in Lanlan's back
ランランの背中には神経細胞のグループがある
sad heart
悲しい心
And this group of cells
そしてこの細胞群は
If they happen to be sitting
彼らがたまたま座っていたら
relatively close
比較接近
they're in their head again
彼らはまた頭の中にいます
If the responsible functions are the same
担当する機能が同じ場合
Then these cells
そうすると、これらの細胞は
deconstruction
脱構築
If this group of cells happens to be responsible for memory
この細胞グループがたまたま記憶を担当している場合
That is
あれは
One of the purposes of our long-term memory formation
私たちの長期記憶形成の目的の一つ
cell biology
細胞生物学
It is a physiological structure
それは生理学的構造です
his theory
彼の理論
until now still
今までまだ
also used by biologists
生物学者も使用
So if he loads
それで彼がロードしたら
he'll get someone else's award
彼は他の人の賞を受賞するだろう
good
良い
this is us
これが私たちです
side view of this brain
この脳を横から見た図
it's very simple
それはとても簡単です
just like me
私と同じように
This is what I'm standing on now
これが今私が立っているものです
then i just said
それから私はちょうど言いました
this is the outermost
これが一番外側です
just this one white this one
これだけ白いこれ
white top
白いトップ
is our skull
私たちの頭蓋骨です
you can touch it now
今すぐ触れてもいいよ
Our skulls are not too thick
私たちの頭蓋骨はそれほど厚くありません
In fact, the skull is several people
実はその頭蓋骨は数人なのです
i think at most one centimeter
せいぜい1センチくらいだと思います
To be honest, a few centimeters too much
正直数センチ多すぎる
But this head cover is trying to
しかし、このヘッドカバーが目指しているのは、
of our brains
私たちの脳の
This part is the cortex of the brain
この部分は脳の皮質です
Because the cerebral cortex actually occupies a large part of the
なぜなら大脳皮質は実際には大部分を占めているからです。
It is divided into sixty percent
60パーセントに分けられます
Our brains are soft
私たちの脳は柔らかい
It's all about the brain
すべては脳の問題です
actually soft
実は柔らかい
After removing the head cover
ヘッドカバーを外した後
Westerners say the brain is like cheese
西洋人は脳はチーズのようなものだと言う
We Chinese say the brain is like tofu
私たち中国人は脳は豆腐のようなものだと言います
you just
あなたはただ
Probably know
おそらく知っています
ah that person
ああ、あの人
but he knows
しかし彼は知っています
so you know sometimes cutting tofu is not so good
だから、豆腐を切るのは時々あまり良くないことを知っています
Some of you said that the knife will go down
ナイフが落ちるだろうと言う人もいた
It just sinks, it doesn't necessarily cut down
沈むだけで必ずしも減るわけではない
But sometimes you have to use the line
ただし、場合によっては回線を使用する必要があります
I don't want to take it up like this
このように取り上げたくない
so it may be squishy
だからふにゃふにゃになるかもしれない
This cerebral cortex is in the following areas
この大脳皮質は次の領域にあります
The cerebral cortex is below
大脳皮質はその下にあります
These areas are the class-related areas of the communal district
これらのエリアは、コミュニティ地区のクラス関連エリアです
they are very important
彼らはとても重要です
So evolutionarily where they do
進化的に彼らがやっているのは
not on the outside
外側ではない
Because the brain you said has something
あなたが言った脳には何かがあるから
more serious than us
私たちよりも真剣です
I hold my hand off
私は手を離す
It is not these evolutionary
それはこれらの進化論ではありません
This is an evolutionarily important region
これは進化上重要な領域です
So it's in the deepest part of our brains
つまりそれは私たちの脳の最も深い部分にあるのです
you can watch like this
このように見ることができます
So it's a circle like this
ということで、こんなサークルです
Such a circle structure is called seahorse ghost
このような円構造はタツノオトシゴゴーストと呼ばれます
look from the top of that bag
そのバッグの上から見てください
Around here in a circle like this
ここら辺はこんな感じ
I'm talking about this area because
私がこの領域について話しているのは、
This area is related to our learning and memory
この領域は私たちの学習と記憶に関連しています
too obvious
あまりにも明らかだ
Do you think of any learning and memory patterns
何か学習と記憶のパターンについて思いつきますか
it's responsible for everything i can almost say
私が言えることすべての責任は彼にあります
It's important that you remember the name
名前を覚えておくことが重要です
Then its special important role is Ren Lu
そして、その特別な重要な役割はRen Luです
The formation of the concept of spatial space
空間概念の形成
how do you know
どうして知っていますか
For example, how do you go to find a friend?
たとえば、どうやって友達を見つけますか？
Because there's a right turn over there
そこ右折があるから
Then there's SF over there and you have to turn left
そしたら向こうにSFがあるので左に曲がらなければなりません
Then look at the gas station and turn left and so on
次に、ガソリンスタンドを見て左折します。
Now it’s more inaccurate, now everyone takes the MRT
今ではもっと不正確になりました、今では誰もが MRT を利用します
I only know which port to come out from the naval battle
海戦でどの港から出るかしか分からない
direction has longer
方向が長くなりました
But I said why do you know how to get to these places
でも私は言いました、なぜあなたはこれらの場所への行き方を知っているのですか
if these
もしこれらが
These are some of the clues on the space
これらは宇宙に関するいくつかの手がかりです
There is a way to say
言う方法があります
That's how the teaching method is
指導方法はこんな感じです
It is also to let us form a cognitive map
それは認知地図を形成させるためでもあります
Cognitive Map
認知マップ
so you know how i know to go home
だから私が家に帰る方法を知っているでしょう
You see there's already a refueling round here
ここですでに給油ラウンドが行われていることがわかります
next one next
次へ次へ
did not follow him
彼に従わなかった
what's his difference
彼の違いは何ですか
In particular, it has a lot to do with any effort
特に、それはあらゆる努力に大きく関係します
another district
別の地区
His is a little below
彼は少し下にいる
I don't know that I'm so deep
そんなに奥が深いのか分からない
His name is Almond River
彼の名前はアーモンド・リバーです
He came because of his name
彼は自分の名前のために来た
Because of Zhuang style Almond River
チワン流アーモンドリバーだから
I am also not certain
私も定かではありません
This very common Chinese saying is Han Xingrenhe
この非常に一般的な中国語のことわざは「韓興仁和」です。
He also learned memory from us
彼はまた私たちから記憶を学びました
very concerned
とても心配です
And he plays an important role
そして彼は重要な役割を果たしています
is disgusting with us
私たちに嫌悪感を抱いている
hate this
これ嫌い
It's about memory, that's what you hate
それは記憶に関するもの、それがあなたが嫌うものです
Others think I hate eating a food
他の人は私が食べ物を食べるのが嫌いだと思っています
eggplant
茄子
so you've had sugar before
それで砂糖を食べたんですね
you may think it tastes bad
不味いと思うかもしれない
So next time that dish will be served
ということで、次回その料理が出てくるのは
if eggplant
ナスがあれば
Your memory will come back and say
あなたの記憶が戻ってきて言うでしょう
i don't want to eat it
食べたくない
this thing is terrible
これはひどいです
That memory is here
あの思い出がここにある
memory formation
記憶形成
But in the end it will be re-stored to the brain Heisei
でも最終的には平成の脳に再保存される
then this place is very interesting
それならこの場所はとても興味深いです
That is to say
つまり
if you see something you don't like
気に入らないものを見た場合
you had a fight with him
あなたは彼と喧嘩をしました
you don't get on well with him
あなたは彼とうまくいっていません
so you might see it from afar
だから遠くからでも見えるかもしれない
You may want to Gupi you to eat a lot
よく食べるグピしたいかも
I don't want to mess with it
台無しにしたくない
you don't like that person's memory
あなたはその人の記憶が好きではありません
also exists here
ここにも存在します
So this evolutionary lower animal
つまり、この進化の下等動物は
it is actually more important
それは実際にはもっと重要です
like a belly
お腹のように
he wants to see
彼は見たいです
He once watched his mate get eaten by a tiger
彼はかつて自分の仲間がトラに食べられるのを見たことがある
So he has to see from afar
だから彼は遠くから見なければならない
next time he sees a wife forever
次に彼が妻に永遠に会うときは
he is extroverted to escape
彼は逃げるために外向的だ
That memory is in sexual nature
その記憶
So in the lower animals
だから下等動物では
It's about survival
それは生存に関するものです
there is also an interesting phenomenon
面白い現象もあります
that is
あれは
as I just said
今言ったように
Some people don't get along well with others
他人とうまくやっていけない人もいる
For example, in actual 20 years
例えば、実際の20年で
Let's say this guy later gets dementia
この人が後に認知症になったとしましょう
He forgot to go out with this person
彼はこの人と出かけるのを忘れた
he'll go over and say hello
彼は行って挨拶するでしょう
so this place
それでこの場所
If the function is slightly weaker
機能が少し弱ければ
It will also make human beings forget about hatred.
それは人類に憎しみを忘れさせることにもなるだろう。
yes, then there will be something like this
はい、そうするとこのようなものがあります
So these are two things that have nothing to do with our experience
つまり、これら 2 つは私たちの経験とは何の関係もありません
Then I will say that these two areas are Hexue
それでは、これら 2 つの領域が Hexue であると言います。
objection formation
異議の形成
Long-term manager formation
長期的な経営者の形成
After forming
形成後
After the memory is formed
記憶が形成されてから
after a while
しばらくして
these formed memories
これらの形成された記憶
will move to the cerebral cortex to be stored there
大脳皮質に移動してそこに保存されます
this thing is interesting
これは面白いですね
You can put the cerebral cortex
大脳皮質を置くことができます
Think of it as a computer hard drive
コンピューターのハードドライブと考えてください。
those areas
それらの地域
You can think of it as your pen drive
ペンドライブと考えることができます
or the job you call it out of
またはあなたがそれを呼び出す仕事
So not only are you all files
つまり、皆さんはファイルを持っているだけではありません
you will need
必要になるだろう
So you put a
それで、あなたは
in the hard drive you don't usually use
普段使わないハードディスクに
One day when you need to take out its memory
ある日、その記憶を取り出す必要があるとき
You may put that hard drive again
そのハードドライブをもう一度取り付けてもよい
connect to your computer
コンピュータに接続する
Then call out the file you let me
次に、あなたが許可したファイルを呼び出します
you can think of it this way
このように考えることができます
So in a situation where the world is consistent
つまり、世界が一貫している状況では
There will be a situation where
という状況が発生します。
when it started
それが始まったとき
it's not in these areas
これらの地域にはありません
it has no way to form
それは形成する方法がありません
very new memory
とても新しい記憶
Just now Fu Yuanang said
ちょうど今、傅元ナンが言いました。
he was yesterday or when
彼は昨日だったのか、いつだったのか
just give someone a hug
ただ誰かをハグしてください
i asked one thing
私は一つ尋ねました
how many hours did he go
彼は何時間行きましたか
or he forgets the next day
あるいは次の日には忘れてしまう
Because he can't form new memories
新しい思い出を作ることができないから
But you ask him long ago
でもあなたはずっと前に彼に尋ねました
his memories for you say
あなたへの彼の思い出はこう言う
what was he like twenty years ago
20年前の彼はどんな人だったのか
what happen
何が起きましたか
how did he remember this
彼はこれをどうやって覚えたのでしょうか
so usually day and night
だから通常は昼も夜も
you start with these
これらから始めます
learning and memory
学習と記憶
in case a defect occurs first
先に不具合が発生した場合に備えて
Of course it sucks to wait till the end
もちろん最後まで待つのはもったいない
Because he doesn't know the way home
彼は帰り道を知らないから
he's the last one who won't recognize
彼は認識できない最後の人だ
his family
彼の家族
all these are
これらはすべて
These are the stages behind them
これらはその背後にある段階です
That is, the function of cerebral sebum is not
つまり、脳の皮脂の働きは
So start with this place of memory
だからこの思い出の場所から始めましょう
Then finally to the storage place without
そして最後に何もせずに保管場所へ
Then our brains store memories
そして私たちの脳は記憶を保存します
There is another feature
もう一つ特徴があります
just okay
大丈夫です
This is the evolutionary protection for us
これは私たちにとっての進化の保護です
such a big brain
とても大きな頭脳
so much sebum
皮脂がとても多い
But our memory is stored
でも私たちの記憶は保存されている
but different
でも違う
unlike the formation of our memories
私たちの記憶の形成とは異なります
so confined to these areas
これらの領域に非常に限定されている
it is area theory
それは地域理論です
it is anywhere
それはどこにでもあります
So you assume today the brain sebum
今日は脳の皮脂が原因だと思いますね
5 to 10 percent of injuries
怪我の5～10パーセント
it doesn't matter
それは問題ではありません
because you may only be around that
あなたはその周りにしかいないかもしれないから
your memory is impaired
あなたの記憶力が損なわれています
But the other 90% or more are OK
でも残りの90％以上は大丈夫
So there is no specific point in what you divide
したがって、何を分割するかについては特に意味はありません
But when memory is formed
しかし、記憶が形成されると、
do you have a specific meaning
何か特別な意味があるのですか
Then this reflects a direction
次に、これは方向性を反映します
If you look at it like this
こうやって見ると
we just didn't talk
私たちは話さなかっただけです
this is the cerebellum
これは小脳です
This is the cerebellum
これが小脳です
so we people
だから私たち人間は
It has more to do with our balance
それは私たちのバランスにもっと関係があります
But this is better in birds than in seas
しかし、これは海よりも鳥の方が良いです
also plays the main role
も主役を演じます
So in fact you can actually see
実際に見ることができます
cerebral sebum
脳皮脂
Its area is full and relatively small
そのエリアはいっぱいですが、比較的小さいです
Then this is serious
じゃあこれは深刻だよ
we talk about your life
私たちはあなたの人生について話します
say breathing heartbeat blood pressure here
ここで呼吸、心拍、血圧を言う
So a person can be unconscious
つまり人は意識を失ってしまう可能性がある
It's the brain without consciousness
脳は無意識です
but it breathes heartbeat blood pressure
しかしそれは心拍血圧を呼吸します
can stay there
そこにいてもいい
it's bad
これは悪いです
This is a vegetative state
これは植物状態です
and here it is
そしてここにあります
Dry
ドライ
Just start from here
ここから始めてください
spine down
背筋が下がる
this is the brainstem
これが脳幹です
Okay, this is not turning around
オーケー、これは好転していない
turn around and look this way
振り返ってこちらを見てください
So what I want to tell you is that
それで、私があなたに言いたいのは、
This is our middle waist hook
こちらはミドルウエストフックです
If we want to divide
分けたいなら
This is the sensory area behind it
これはその背後にある感覚領域です
That is to say, if I hit you today
つまり、今日あなたを殴ったら
Your signal will first pass through the spine to the back
信号はまず背骨を通って背中に伝わります
after all received
結局受け取った
dorsal side of the spine
背骨の背側
Turn up, turn around, turn to the brain
上を向いて、振り返って、脳の方を向いて
send here
ここに送信します
feel
感じられる
Then it will command
それからそれは命令します
can command to the front
前線に指揮を執ることができる
In front of the middle waist hook is actually the sports area
真ん中のウエストフックの前は実際にはスポーツエリアです
it will send the message to its motor area
メッセージをその運動領域に送信します
then this time
それから今度は
we'll make a move
私たちは行動を起こします
answer or run away
答えるか逃げるか
It is the feeling area on the thigh surface of the middle waist hook
つまり、フィーリングエリアはミッドウエストフックのバット面にあります。
then the sports area is in front
スポーツエリアが目の前にあります
I mainly want to tell you this
主にこれをお伝えしたいのですが
you don't need to worry about these
これらについて心配する必要はありません
that's brainy
それは頭がいいです
You now see that there is another very important feature
もう一つ非常に重要な機能があることがわかりました
You see there are many wrinkles
シワがたくさんあるのがわかります
A lot of wrinkles, right?
シワがたくさんありますよね？
you go
あなたが行く
why is that
何故ですか
Wrinkle is a very space-saving
リンクルは非常に省スペースです
If you remove all these wrinkles
このシワを全部取り除けば
spread out
広がる
then the surface area of ​​our brains becomes very large
私たちの脳の表面積は非常に大きくなるでしょう
wrinkle in unevenly
不均一なシワ
In this way you will become very compat
そうすればあなたはとても仲良くなれるでしょう
Let's talk about a car compat car
カーコンパトカーについて話しましょう
It's just so tightly packed.
こんなにぎっしり詰まっているんですね。
So it is a space saving design
省スペース設計なので
It is the result of evolution
それは進化の結果です
So our heads won't be as big as sea elves
だから私たちの頭は海の妖精ほど大きくないでしょう
Why do you have such a big head?
どうしてそんなに頭が大きいのですか？
Yes, it is a burden for us
はい、それは私たちにとって負担です
So the evolution sprite is very streamlined
進化スプライトは非常に合理化されています
But in this streamlined mind
でもこの合理的な頭の中では
We have nearly 100 billion god cells
私たちは約1000億個の神の細胞を持っています
just incredible
ただただ信じられないほど
I'll wait for the way to get the crown
王冠を手に入れる方法を待っています
So the more evolved animals are the more wrinkled
つまり、進化した動物ほどしわが多くなります
Second only to us are monkeys
私たちの次に猿です
Mouse brains also wrinkle a lot
マウスの脳にもシワが多い
I would say that human beings have quite a lot of wrinkles.
人間にはシワがかなりあると思います。
I mainly show you this
主にこれを紹介します
sensorimotor area
感覚運動野
This one was found in a textbook room a long time ago
これは昔、教科書室で見つけたものです
But now I can't find it in this textbook
でも今はこの教科書には載ってない
that has its meaning
それは意味がある
Cut it like this, look at it like this, look at the next six and a half years
こう切って、こう見て、次の6年半を見て
What this graph tells us is that
このグラフが教えてくれるのは、
in the cortex of the brain
脳の皮質で
The temperature of our movements and sensations
私たちの動きや感覚の温度
In the corresponding area of ​​the cerebral cortex
大脳皮質の対応する領域で
He has a little intention to tell us that it is exhausted and discarded
彼はそれが使い果たされて廃棄されたことを私たちに伝えたいというちょっとした意図を持っています
It's also about evolution
それも進化の話だ
He doesn't necessarily buy a person's hands and face
彼は必ずしも人の手と顔を買うわけではありません
The feet are not necessarily here
足がここにあるとは限らない
mean to tell us
私たちに伝えるという意味
in our limbs
私たちの手足の中で
what do we use most humans
ほとんどの人は何を使っていますか
it's hard to deal with
対処するのは難しい
no comments
コメントはありません
what do we do with
何をしますか
Then put your finger inside
それから中に指を入れてください
Large membrane fingers are used the most
大きなメンブレンフィンガーが最もよく使用されます
So his feeling is very fine
だから彼の気持ちはとてもいいです
Cortex in our brain
私たちの脳の皮質
of the motor functions of our hands
私たちの手の運動機能の
occupies a considerable area of ​​our brain
私たちの脳のかなりの領域を占めています
so fine
とてもいいです
You can take it and knock a brick with your hands
それを手に取って、手でレンガをたたくこともできます
But you can also thread a needle
でも針に糸を通すこともできます
It's very delicate to thread this needle
この針に糸を通すのはとても繊細です
Actually moving things is very different
実際に動くものは全然違います
So he needs very fine control
だから彼には非常に細かいコントロールが必要だ
That foot is longer
その足は長いです
We just walk and basically
基本的にただ歩くだけです
The other one is our face
もう一つは私たちの顔です
facial expression
表情
Of course you don't know if it's good or not
もちろんそれが良いかどうかは分かりません
We use our mouths too much
私たちは口を使いすぎます
just do two things
たった2つのことをするだけ
one is speech
一つはスピーチです
That's less than two years may be better
2年以内ならもっといいかもしれない
The other one is eating
もう一人は食べています
to eat
たべる
so a very interesting
とても興味深いです
schematic diagram
回路図
That's what he said in his head
それが彼が頭の中で言ったことだ
A distribution of sensory and motor functions
感覚機能と運動機能の分布
with his functional one
彼の機能的なものと一緒に
ok now i'll show you one more level
さて、もう 1 つのレベルをお見せします
wait a minute and pay attention
ちょっと待って注意してください
At the beginning of this video
このビデオの冒頭で
There will be a rotating map of the human brain
人間の脳の回転マップが存在するでしょう
you pay attention
あなたは注意してください
If you look at him right in the middle
彼を真ん中から見ると
Our brains are symmetrical between the left and right hemispheres
私たちの脳は左半球と右半球で対称的です
Then later he introduced
その後、彼は紹介してくれました
every nerve
あらゆる神経血管
How to connect with nerve blood hair
神経血毛との接続方法
I just talked about two
さっき2つ話したんですが
a phenomenon, an electricity, a chemistry
現象、電気、化学
These are the planets that the gods wish for that are real in our minds
これらは私たちの心の中に現実に存在する、神々が望んだ惑星です
I just think these gods hope to be beautiful and unbelievable
私はただ、これらの神々は美しく、信じられないほど美しくなることを望んでいると思う
This is what the gods hope
これが神々の望みです
So you can take a look at that
それで、それを見てみましょう
maybe a little perspective
ちょっとした視点かもしれない
what shape does each have
それぞれはどんな形をしているのか
Neurons come in thousands
ニューロンは数千個存在する
perhaps tens of thousands of different kinds
おそらく何万種類もの
each with a unique shape
それぞれがユニークな形をしています
a distinct molecular composition
明確な分子組成
and a unique pattern of connections within the brain
脳内の独特の接続パターン
ok
Ok
so you see it twinkle
だから、それがきらめくのが見えるでしょう
That's the signal it generates electricity
それが電気を発生させる信号だ
To send a message to the next cell
次のセルにメッセージを送信するには
Then you just saw it in
それからあなたはそれを見たばかりです
You may remember that when the brain spins
脳が回転するとき、あなたはそれを思い出すかもしれません
You can see the change view from the central tick
中央のチェックマークから変化ビューを確認できます
If it is not viewed from the middle, the left and right are symmetrical
真ん中から見ないと左右対称です
Then I want to emphasize that
それから強調したいのは、
Structurally speaking, our brain
構造的に言えば、私たちの脳は
Left and right are symmetrical
左右対称です
But our function is asymmetric
しかし、私たちの関数は非対称です
it's amazing
すごい
In terms of us humans
私たち人間で言えば
Chasing our left brain is responsible for language
左脳を追い求めることが言語を担当する
So suppose we have a language area in the left brain
それでは、左脳に言語野があると仮定します。
That part of the cerebral cortex is the language area
大脳皮質のその部分は言語野です
so if that place hurts
だからそこが痛かったら
Whether trauma or swelling
外傷なのか腫れなのか
that person's
あの人の
Ability to speak can be affected
会話能力に影響が出る可能性がある
Women's Zhongshu is here
女性メンバー鍾州が登場
Then our right brain generally speaking
それでは、私たちの右脳は一般的に言えば、
From the point of view of scientists
科学者の観点から
is more about artistic abstraction
芸術的な抽象化に重点を置いています
features like music
音楽などの機能
so you just think
だからあなたはただ思うだけです
what is bad about art
芸術の何が悪いのか
It may be that the function of the right brain is less
右脳の働きが低下しているのかもしれません
so it is
それはそうです
The result is symmetrical and the function is asymmetrical
結果は対称的ですが、関数は非対称的です
There is another characteristic
もう一つ特徴があります
The whole sense of the brain and our limbs
脳と手足の感覚全体
The senses are crossed
感覚が交差する
So what the right eye sees
では、右目で見えるものは
its image after crossing
渡った後のイメージ
almost here
もうすぐここ
is projected to the back of the left brain
左脳の後部に投影される
What you see on the left is the right brain
左側に見えるのは右脳です
so are the ears
耳もそうです
So I think there will be such a phenomenon
なのでそういう現象はあると思います
That is to say, assuming a moderate patient
つまり、中等度の患者を想定すると、
it is a hemorrhage that hurts the left brain
左脳を傷つける出血です
A blood clot presses into its nerve haemoperitoneum
血栓が神経血腹膜を圧迫する
left nerve hematomania damage
左神経血腫損傷
It is often unable to move the right hand and right foot
右手と右足が動かなくなることが多い
or right brain injury
もしくは右脳損傷
It will be unable to move the left hand and left foot
左手と左足が動かなくなります
Don't go into the details of these neurotic encounters
これらの神経症的な出会いの詳細には立ち入らないでください
but you know this
でもあなたはこれを知っています
Our brains are not as good as those of animals.
私たちの脳は動物ほど優れていません
rats are like this
ネズミはこんな感じ
to a basic feature
基本機能まで
Adjustment with one of his functions
彼の機能の1つによる調整
you just saw
あなたは今見た
Wrapped outside our heads, underneath our brains
頭の外側、脳の下に包まれている
actually very light
実際にはとても軽い
We weigh tens of kilograms
私たちの体重は数十キロあります
Our brains are only about three or four pounds
私たちの脳の重さはわずか 3 ～ 4 ポンドです
very small very light
とても小さい とても軽い
But our brains
しかし、私たちの脳は
80 billion to 100 billion nerve cells
800億～1000億個の神経細胞
This is undeniable
これは否定できません
previous rottenness was
以前の腐りは
But now the newer ones are just
しかし、今では新しいものはただ
Because 80 billion is a lot
800億って大きいから
eight hundred billion ten
八千億十
The tenth room is completely stuffed in
10番目の部屋は完全に詰め込まれています
We say these wrinkles surface, the inside of the face
このしわを顔の表面、内側といいます。
Diameter of each neurovascular chamber
各神経血管室の直径
about twenty five to thirty
25時から30時くらい
Minecraft
マインクラフト
Minecraft is ten of the rot six magnetic room denunciation
Minecraft は 10 の腐った 6 磁気部屋の非難です
you can go home by yourself
あなたは自分で家に帰ることができます
deproportional release
非比例解放
Everyone see how small he is
誰もが彼がどれほど小さいかを見てください
But he functions like this
しかし、彼にはそのような機能があります
Every neurovascular video we just watched
私たちが見たすべての神経血管ビデオ
look
見て
I also talked about it making connections with other nerve cells
他の神経細胞との接続についても話しました
for the purpose of message delivery
メッセージ配信の目的のため
Each nerve cell can see nearby
各神経細胞は近くを見ることができます
sometimes far
時には遠くに
Sometimes one of our nerve cells
時々私たちの神経細胞の一つが
Can go from here to here in the head
頭の中でここからここまで行ける
that's pretty far
それはかなり遠いです
whether it is far or near
遠くても近くても
Each neuron can communicate with other neurons
各ニューロンは他のニューロンと通信できます
There can be up to 1000 contacts and 1000 links
最大 1000 の連絡先と 1000 のリンクを含めることができます
so you can miss our brain is a
だからあなたは私たちの脳を見逃すことができます
In terms of computer
コンピューターに関して言えば
It is a place with a very dense network distribution
ネットワークが非常に密集している場所です
Only in this way can our message delivery be quickly reached
この方法によってのみ、メッセージを迅速に届けることができます
Let me give you an example
例を挙げてみましょう
That is to say, our human brain
つまり、私たち人間の脳は、
how to say
どのように言って
That is, you want to be like
つまり、あなたはこうなりたいのです
How many buses are there in Taipei?
台北には何台のバスがありますか?
We don't necessarily have 100 buses
必ずしも100台のバスがあるわけではありません
Then say this bus goes to this place
それからこのバスはこの場所に行くと言う
that bus to that place
あの場所行きのバス
Because the bus is so big
バス停がとても広いので
so it gets stuck
だから行き詰まってしまう
A better plan is
より良い計画は、
Maybe we only need 30 buses or 40 buses
おそらくバスは 30 台か 40 台しか必要ないでしょう
But we have planned its route
しかし、私たちはそのルートを計画しました
you can form a good network
良いネットワークを形成できます
Let you go to Taipei, all four-way and eight-way road
台北へ行かせてください 四方八方道路
but he is in his physical
しかし彼は肉体的には
He really doesn't take too much risk in terms of size
彼はサイズに関してあまりリスクを冒さない
but rely on the Internet
でもインターネットに頼る
I mean relative
親戚という意味です
Let's say we don't need
必要ないとしましょう
don't say why you like
なぜ好きなのかは言わないでください
But there needs to be a link between them
しかし、それらの間にはリンクが必要です
well done
素晴らしい
this matter is more important
この問題の方が重要です
there is another phenomenon
別の現象があります
Maybe you don't know that well
たぶんあなたはそれをよく知りません
It's a bit scary to hear it cold
寒いと聞くとちょっと怖いです
people from birth
生まれたときからの人
Our nerve cells are dying
私たちの神経細胞は死につつあります
And once you die, you don't regenerate
そして一度死ぬと再生することはありません
Over 90% of the countries
90％以上の国が
Nerve cells in only a few areas
神経細胞は一部の領域のみに存在する
will regenerate
再生します
And one of those areas is the seahorse ghost
それらのエリアの 1 つはタツノオトシゴの幽霊です
That's what I just said is responsible for the memory schedule
それが私が今言ったことであり、記憶スケジュールに責任があるのです
then you will sound
そうすればあなたは鳴るでしょう
feel terrible
ひどい気分になる
In fact when a baby is born
実は赤ちゃんが生まれると
he is his neuron
彼は彼のニューロンです
When the number of nerve cells in the brain is the largest
脳内の神経細胞の数が最も多いとき
But this baby may
でも、この赤ちゃんはもしかしたら、
have they studied
彼らは勉強しましたか
So each of his nerve cells
つまり、彼の神経細胞の一つ一つが
Like other nerve cells
他の神経細胞と同じように
Let's just give a simple example
簡単な例を挙げてみましょう
His link may only have 100 links
彼のリンクには 100 個しかリンクがない可能性があります
but you can speak
でもあなたは話すことができます
why a person seems like you feel
なぜ人はあなたの気持ちと同じように見えるのか
he is the best years
彼は最高の年だ
or when you think he's smart
または彼が賢いと思うとき
maybe thirty or forty years old
30歳か40歳くらいかな
or feel as if
または次のように感じます
The end of life after middle age
中年以降の人生の終わり
Actually at that time
実はあの時
The number of our nerve blood light has died a lot
私たちの神経血の光の数はかなり減りました
many people died
多くの人が亡くなりました
but why do you feel
しかし、なぜ感じますか
People learn from experience and get smarter
人は経験から学び、賢くなる
that reason is because
その理由は
Those who are still alive are different.
今生きている人は違います。
What's the connection between them and other nerve blood lights?
それらと他の神経血灯との間にはどのような関係があるのでしょうか?
so a baby
だから赤ちゃん
he may be this nerve blood light
彼はこの神経血の光かもしれない
with another nerve blood light
別の神経血液ライトで
100 links
100リンク
but in adulthood
しかし大人になってから
to a mature stage
成熟した段階へ
Four or fifty years old
4、50歳
he may be bloody
彼は血まみれかもしれない
can another bleed
また出血できるでしょうか
There are seven or eight hundred links
有七、八百個連結
so that link
そのリンク
that network is important
そのネットワークは重要です
rather than exactly
正確にではなく
The number of cell bodies is important
細胞体の数が重要
certainly
そうです
neurohemophore
神経血液団
Can't die indefinitely
無限に死ぬことはできない
because we are aging
私たちは老化しているから
The number of nerve blood light is always dying
神経血の光の数は常に死んでいます
to a certain extent
ある程度まで
In fact, it is the time of processing caused by life
実はそれは生命による処理の時間なのです
This is normal aging and death
これは正常な老化と死です
so
それで
You sound like it's really scary
本当に怖いみたいだね
And then as soon as you are born these cells are dying
そして、あなたが生まれるとすぐに、これらの細胞は死にます
OK, then I'll just keep watching.
わかりました、それでは見守り続けます。
How do we scientists do learning and memory experiments
私たち科学者は学習と記憶の実験をどのように行うのか
We can't just experiment with people
ただ人を使って実験することはできない
neither one
どちらでもない
It's not ethical
それは倫理的ではありません
two no way
2 まさか
Because human variables vary too much
人間の変数はあまりにも変化しすぎるため
Everyone is very different
みんな全然違うんだよ
We're looking for ten people at random
ランダムで10名様募集します
The ten of us will have a lot
私たち10人にはたくさんのものがあるでしょう
There will be ten different reactions for the same number of times
同じ回数でも10通りの反応が得られます
So animals actually provide a homogeneity and distance
したがって、動物は実際に均一性と距離を提供します
It's an experiment on animals that many of us do for the most part
それは私たちの多くが頻繁に行う動物実験です
It's all small numbers
どれも小さな数字です
They often prefer to use them for any experiment
彼らは多くの場合、あらゆる実験に使用することを好みます。
Any direction
任意の方向
This is mainly because Ren Lu is actually a very complicated idea.
これは主に、Ren Lu が実際には非常に複雑なアイデアであるためです。
Then his experimental results
そして彼の実験結果は
It is also more applicable to human
それは人間にもより応用可能です
such as human dementia
人間の認知症など
or something related to the Ashhan process
またはアシュハンプロセスに関連するもの
Because people also have this task
人間にもそういう仕事があるから
chief of science
科学部長
It's all done on land.
すべて陸上で行われます。
That is to say, this is called pole turning
つまりこれをポールターニングと言います
like this is twelve turns
これで12ターンです
How do you guys do this experiment?
みなさんはこの実験をどうやってやりますか？
At the beginning, let the mouse starve for a whole day
まず、マウスを丸一日絶食させます。
he's going to be a little hungry
彼は少しお腹が空くだろう
That's why he wants to find food
だからこそ彼は食べ物を見つけたいのです
then it's hard
それなら大変だ
These twelve turns
この12ターン
360 degrees per turn
1回転あたり360度
It's only 30 degrees apart
たった30度しか離れていない
30 degrees only
30度のみ
So this rat is hungry to learn how
つまり、このネズミはその方法を学ぶことに飢えているのです
That is to say, the Chief of Science
つまり科学部長
First time he put a food pellet here
初めてここに餌のペレットを入れました
this mouse is hungry
このネズミはお腹が空いています
try many times
何度も試してみる
As a result, he turned his eyes here
その結果、彼はこちらに目を向けた
he eats him
彼は彼を食べる
The second time he had to learn
二度目に彼は学ばなければならなかった
our scientist
私たちの科学者
can put this food here
この食べ物をここに置いてもいいです
he has to learn to say
彼は言うことを学ばなければならない
I'm going to turn 30 degrees to the right this time
今度は右に30度曲がってみます
i can find food
食べ物を見つけることができます
Next time he will learn
次回彼は学ぶでしょう
turn right another 30 degrees
さらに30度右折します
i find it hard to be honest
正直になるのは難しいと思う
Even I can't tell
私にも言えない
so when later
それで、後で
Then mouse of course you are smart
それならマウス、もちろんあなたは賢いです
How many times did he learn
彼は何回学びましたか
he ate three times
彼は三回食べた
eat a certain person
ある人を食べる
he feels less hungry
彼はお腹が減ったように感じます
he started not to go
彼は行かなくなり始めた
but in the middle
しかし真ん中で
You will never be able to complete this experiment
この実験を完了することは決して不可能です
So in 1986 there was a scientific
そこで 1986 年に科学的研究が行われました。
very smart
とても賢い
His name is Ritramoris
彼の名はリトラモリス
he is still there
彼はまだそこにいる
Shending Science Center at the University of Edinburgh
エディンバラ大学シェンディング科学センター
Doubtsbury
ダウツベリー
He thought of a way
彼はある方法を考えた
Just put the mouse in the water
マウスを水の中に入れるだけ
you can't believe it
信じられないでしょう
A mouse is not a real water animal
ネズミは本物の水生動物ではない
but he can swim and think
でも彼は泳ぐこともできるし、考えることもできる
that this
これは
Behavioral pattern called Morris
モリスと呼ばれる行動パターン
because its surname is Morris
姓がモリスだから
Do you know that westerners often do this
西洋人はよくこれをすることを知っていますか
what did you invent
あなたは何を発明しましたか
do it with your name
あなたの名前でやってください
that code name
そのコードネーム
Mondown
モンダウン
Ting Horton
ティン・ホートン
etc.
等
So it's called Morris
だからモリスって言うんだよ
Spend every eschatological water already
終末論的な水をすべて使い切ってください
this pool
このプール
That is, I am in Calefort or the night market
つまり、私はカレフォールかナイトマーケットにいるのです
buy that kid
あの子を買う
summer wash
夏の洗濯
swimming pool
スイミングプール
Then he put water in this
それから彼はこれに水を入れました
what about the water
水はどうですか
use some
いくつか使って
bleach or powdered milk
漂白剤または粉ミルク
make it slightly mushy
少しどろどろにする
So this time you put the mouse in
そこで今回はマウスを入れます
it looks like
のようです
Can't see anything in the water
水の中では何も見えない
But in fact somewhere in this water
でも実はこの水のどこかで
it's just a little bit below
ほんの少し下にあります
if the water is here
ここに水があれば
just below
すぐ下に
there is a table
テーブルがあります
So if that mouse kicks kick kick
だからねずみがキックキックしたら
have been to that place
その場所に行ったことがある
It will stand up when it kicks it
蹴ると立ち上がる
Because it doesn't want to become drowned
溺れたくないから
So that I do this lab
このラボを行うために
I don't believe it either
私も信じられない
In my heart I'm afraid it will drown
心の中では溺れてしまうのではないかと心配している
but its life
しかし、その人生
sealed in water for the first time
初めて水の中に封じ込められた
it will flow away
それは流れ去ってしまうだろう
So I think the human lab
人間の実験室は
Sometimes some functions are similar to animals
場合によっては、いくつかの機能が動物に似ていることもあります
we're still a bit regressed
私たちはまだ少し後退している
if we go down maybe
下がったら多分
it won't work
それはうまくいきません
Then what is the important thing about this experiment
では、この実験で重要なことは何でしょうか
when you sit in the water
水の中に座ると
clean the walls
壁を掃除する
you can't have any tricks like this
こんなトリックはありえない
in vain
無駄に
Then we put some signals on purpose
次に、意図的にいくつかの信号を置きます
with color
色付き
Do not use the wrong shape
間違った形状を使用しないでください
because I don't know how to prove it
それを証明する方法がわからないので
I have never heard that mice have poor vision.
ネズミの視力が悪いという話は聞いたことがありません。
it is a bit
それは少しです
It seems to be a bit colored
少し色付いてきたような気がします
So we use the shape
そこで、この形状を使用します
a round shape
丸い形
a square etc.
正方形など
natural often
天然常常
It didn't recognize this at first
最初はこれを認識しませんでした
where is the platform
プラットフォームはどこですか
But after several training
しかし、数回のトレーニングを経て、
he will watch these
彼はこれらを見るでしょう
This picture looks like he is looking at it
この写真は彼がそれを見ているように見えます
He will send these signals
彼はこれらの信号を送るでしょう
Like I just said there is a 7
先ほど言ったように、7 があります
there's a gas station there
そこにガソリンスタンドがあります
so you know how to turn
だからあなたは向きを変える方法を知っています
He will put the platform problem
彼はプラットフォームの問題を提起するだろう
connect with some signals
いくつかの信号に接続する
several times later
数回後
He'll get on the platform in no time
彼はすぐに壇上に上がるだろう
so the shorter the period the better
なので期間は短いほど良いです
we'll remember later
後で思い出します
time for him to escape
彼が逃げる時間
because he said he'd get up soon
なぜなら彼はすぐに起きると言っているからです
There are also some teachers who really can't learn
本当に勉強ができない先生もいる
We have about 100 seconds and 120 seconds
100秒と120秒くらいあります
Then you have to pick him up when it's time
それから、時間になったら彼を迎えに行かなければなりません
switch to that table
そのテーブルに切り替えてください
Otherwise you eventually
そうしないと、最終的には
he'll drown in the end
彼は最後には溺れてしまうだろう
so he stood up
それで彼は立ち上がった
this
これ
This can be thought of by others
これは他の人も考えられる
you know from 1980 to now
1980年から現在までをご存知ですか
You go to see what kind of top journals like nature
自然のようなトップジャーナルがどんなものなのかを見に行くんだ
Many, many studies have been done using this method
この方法を使用して非常に多くの研究が行われています
because what i just said
なぜなら私が今言ったこと
he is a compulsive learner
彼は強迫的な学習者です
You can't force it on purpose
故意に強制することはできません
the second
二番目
Ren Lu's learning
レン・ルーの学び
His many research results
彼の多くの研究成果
Can be applied to human dementia
人間の認知症にも応用できる
a study
研究
Some research and development
一部の研究開発
it has its importance
それは重要性を持っています
That's why I'm here to say
だからこそ私はここで言いたいのです
This mouse learns how to swim
このネズミは泳ぎ方を学びます
Then
それから
this is this no sound
これは音が出ない
It's okay, here's for you to see
大丈夫、ここを見てください
When doing real experiments
実際に実験をするときは
how did they put the mouse down
彼らはどうやってマウスを置いたのか
it swims there
それはそこで泳ぐ
Then you will see the mouse a few red
すると、マウスが少し赤いのが見えます。
it's not red
赤くないです
You see it swims like a cloud
雲のように泳ぐのがわかります
It's not red, it's because of the light reflection
赤くないよ光の反射だから
so you look like that red over there is a mouse
だから君はあそこの赤いネズミに見えるね
I'll show you this time
今度見せてあげるよ
Really such an experimental operation
本当にそのような実験的な操作
how they operate
どのように動作するか
this can be slower
これは遅くなる可能性があります
That's why the experimenter put the mouse down
だから実験者はマウスを置いた
In fact, we can probably see
実際、おそらく見ることができます
Because I think Zheng Mao is stupid
鄭毛はバカだと思うから
He just can't find where the platform is
彼はプラットフォームがどこにあるのか見つけられない
So he's been probably
だから彼はおそらくそうしてきた
The number of seconds to have an upper limit for this experiment
この実験の上限を秒数で指定します。
Then they often sometimes
それから彼らはしばしば、時々
now there is
現在邊上有
Finally run to the middle
ようやく真ん中まで走ります
still a little insecure
まだ少し不安です
This is how the experiment goes
実験はこんな感じで進んでいきます
Yes, compare the water Mingjing experiment
はい、水の明神実験を比較してください
um , ok , that ' s it
えー、わかりました、それで終わりです
No, otherwise we will draw together
いいえ、そうでなければ一緒に絵を描きます
it is this
これです
good
良い
I also found this picture in an earlier textbook
この写真も昔の教科書で見つけました
it compares
それは比較します
rat brain
ラットの脳
one, untrained
1人は訓練を受けていない
without e.g. studying and training a teacher
例えば教師の勉強や訓練を行わずに
with a trained teacher
訓練を受けた教師と一緒に
it goes better than his cerebral cortex
彼の大脳皮質よりもうまくいきます
cell, cellular
細胞、細胞
Density of axis plots, dendrograms
軸プロット、樹状図の密度
here is trained
ここは訓練を受けています
here is no training
ここではトレーニングはありません
can you see it
見えますか
A little bit of difference is the teacher here
ちょっと違うのはここの先生です
The density of connections of his branches
彼の枝の接続の密度
It will be less than here
ここよりも少ないでしょう
may not be so obvious
それほど明白ではないかもしれません
but there is a difference
しかし違いがあります
why is it hard to be obvious
なぜ明白であることが難しいのですか
If you only select one area to see
表示するエリアを 1 つだけ選択した場合
may be comparable
匹敵するかもしれない
the reason is because
その理由は、
very progressive animal
とても進歩的な動物
It's very high, not an animal
とても高いです、動物ではありません
so stupid mouse
とても愚かなマウス
Its brain is already very complicated
その脳はすでに非常に複雑です
so you
だからあなたは
Called Ceiling Effect C0E1 Block
天井効果と呼ばれる C0E1 ブロック
It's hard for you to move like this
このように動くのは難しいです
Then see a particularly obvious change
その後、特に明らかな変化が見られます
Now scientists make time words
今、科学者たちは時間に関する言葉を作っています
will take out an area
エリアを取り除きます
one by one area
エリアごとに
Different areas are better
違う分野の方が良い
It will be a bit difficult for a large piece
大きい作品だとちょっと大変かも
But this is a precious photo
でも貴重な写真ですね
Because I talked about this later
このことは後ほど話したので、
I don't think it's easy for you to see
あなたにとってそれは簡単ではないと思います
good
良い
You just saw the side view of this picture
この写真の側面図を見ました
Now this picture is like this
さて今回の写真はこんな感じです
say i face you now
今あなたに直面していると言ってください
This slice is cut like this
このスライスはこんな感じで切ります
from my head like this
このように私の頭から
Cut back one by one like this
こんな感じで一枚一枚切り戻します
So this is a full front section
これがフロントセクション全体です
The full front area is very cut down
フロントエリア全体が大幅にカットされています
I want to show everyone
みんなに見せたい
This is the area of ​​the seahorse ghost
ここはタツノオトシゴのエリアです
this whole rhythm
この全体のリズム
It is very easy to dye just dye
染めるだけなのでとても簡単です
seahorse ghost area
タツノオトシゴの幽霊エリア
I just said that this area is in charge of our study
この分野が私たちの研究を担当していると言いました
with memory
記憶とともに
with learning and memory
学習と記憶とともに
Especially this place related to the task
特にこのタスクに関連する場所
That
それか
Especially related to the area of ​​C1
特にC1の領域に関連
don't talk so much
あまり話さないでください
then wait until you ask
それからあなたが尋ねるまで待ちます
all the way back
ずっと戻って
I'll cut to the back
後ろまでカットします
This area of ​​the hippocampus goes down slightly to the sides
海馬のこの領域はわずかに側面に下がっています
This is relatively front to back
これは比較的前から後ろへ
it goes down slightly to the sides
わずかに横に下がります
So this is the area of ​​the hippocampus
つまり、これは海馬の領域です
And this place is what we call the Xinren River area
そしてこの場所は私たちが新仁河地区と呼んでいる場所です
so it's a bit on the bottom of the comparison
それで、それは底を少し比較しています
At this time, we just take the medicine
現時点では薬を飲むだけです
To be injected into this Xinrenhe area
この新仁河地域に注入される
Then look at the impact and change of the learning and memory of the mice
次に、マウスの学習と記憶の影響と変化を観察します。
So these are sliced ​​graphs
これがスライスグラフです
I'll put one or two next
次は1つか2つ載せます
A straight picture or two of that mouse brain
ネズミの脳のまっすぐな写真 1 ～ 2 枚
I miss you
あなたが恋しい
i asked them
私は彼らに尋ねました
they feel ok
彼らは大丈夫だと感じています
i think i hope you feel okay
あなたが大丈夫だと思うよ
but it feels good
でも気持ちいいです
this is a mouse
これはマウスです
not a rat
ネズミではありません
It's the guy you're like watching ghosts
幽霊を見てるような奴だよ
that cerebellum
その小脳
The situation where the brain is cut off
脳が切断される状況
so symmetrical
とても対称的
This is just from the skull
これは頭​​蓋骨からだけです
Take it out after your neck and feet
首と足の後に取り出します
So these are the sides of the brain
つまり、これらは脳の側面です
this is the cerebellum
これは小脳です
under it is the brain cover
その下には脳のカバーがあります
But there is no need to cut the back
でも背中を切る必要はない
so just took it out
それで取り出しただけです
There will be bone fluid blood vessel wind
骨液血管風が発生します
But then we put it in
しかし、その後、それを入れました
physiological experiment water
生理実験水
Some of these blood vessels were taken away by fine water after clearing
これらの血管の一部は浄化後にきれいな水によって取り除かれました
So this is another way after sucking up all the bloodshots
これはすべての充血を吸い取った後の別の方法です
so symmetrical
とても対称的
if we
もし私達
Let me tell you where the hippocampus will be
海馬がどこにあるのか教えてください
So if we start from this place
だからこの場所から始めたら
We use a pinch to push the sides apart
ピンチを使って側面を押し広げます
When you pull it out, you'll see it's like this inside
引っ張り出すと中はこんな感じです
This is where the two sides are pushed apart
ここで双方が引き離されることになる
Spread it out again, just like that
また広げて このまま
whole
全体
So these two areas are left-right symmetrical, which is the hippocampus area.
つまり、この2つの領域は左右対称であり、それが海馬領域です。
it's obvious in this way
このようにして明らかです
Right in our hand and mouth are these two slices
私たちの手と口の中にあるのは、この 2 つのスライスです
they say value the belt
彼らはベルトを大切にすると言います
not sure
わからない
This is the hippocampus area
ここは海馬の領域です
and then in this flipped area
そしてこの反転したエリアで
Let's talk about it
では、それについて話しましょう
This area is symmetrical to this area
この領域はこの領域と対称です
Stylistic
文体的な
This area is responsible for managing motor function
この領域は運動機能の管理を担当します
You said that there are often patients with strokes or long streams
脳卒中や長いストリームの患者がよくいるとおっしゃいましたね
he can't move his hands and feet
彼は手と足を動かすことができない
often bleeding
頻繁に出血する
or a blood clot in this place
またはこの場所に血栓がある
it's a homeland security movement
それは国土安全保障運動です
Manage wear, running, balance, and more
摩耗、ランニング、バランスなどを管理
all important
すべて重要な
That is, the Ministry of Homeland Security cannot
つまり、国土安全保障省はできない。
This is the Department of Homeland Security's study of genetics
これは国土安全保障省による遺伝学の研究です
Then in the name of the former Russian student
それから元ロシア人留学生の名において
jump it in for everyone to see
みんなに見てもらえるようにジャンプしてみよう
That is, the hippocampus will be left-right symmetrical
つまり海馬は左右対称になります
so you probably know
だからあなたはおそらく知っているでしょう
It really uses the brain's gotta go
本当に脳を使うんだよ
probably where
おそらくどこで
This is when we actually experiment
ここからは実際に実験していきます
do with pre-uncertainty
事前不確実性を扱う
This is the three-dimensional brain positioning shift between three-dimensional collisions
これは、3 次元衝突間の 3 次元の脳の位置のずれです。
We put the numbers on this shelf
この棚に数字を載せます
In fact, we saw the same thing in our hospital.
実際、私たちの病院でも同じようなことがありました。
The doctor also has to help us put it on a shelf like this
医者も私たちをこのように棚に上げなければなりません
That's it, it's a bit more severe
それはそれです、それはもう少し厳しいです
Then we usually do mice
それから私たちは通常マウスを作ります
Just ordinary glasses and a microscope
普通のメガネと顕微鏡だけ
But do doctors use an operating microscope?
しかし、医師は手術用顕微鏡を使用するのでしょうか?
We will first put a tube
まずはチューブを入れていきます
in a specific area of ​​the rat's brain
ラットの脳の特定の領域で
Then just wait for it to recover in a week
あとは一週間以内に回復するのを待つだけです
we go through real barrel
本物のバレルを通過します
through very thin tubes
非常に細いチューブを通して
Put this medicine slowly in its
この薬をゆっくりと入れてください
Inject it into the brain and put it in slowly
脳内に注射してゆっくりと入れてください
Doing the teacher's experiment, doing animal experiments is very hard
先生の実験、動物実験はとても大変です
Each one has to go through such an operation
それぞれがそのような操作を経なければなりません
The assumption is that there are some drugs
何らかの麻薬が存在すると仮定して、
we need him to go very slowly teacher
先生にはゆっくり行ってもらう必要があります
import teacher
輸入教師
And it requires him to give up slowly for a long time
そして、それは彼に長い間ゆっくりとあきらめることを要求します
So we'll put these tubes in his head
それで、これらのチューブを彼の頭に入れましょう
And then these tubes will knock down
そして、これらのチューブはノックダウンします
look over here you can see those
ここを見てください、あなたはそれらを見ることができます
Then knock down a needle and the whole thing goes to a pump
それから針を倒すとすべてがポンプに送られます
We use the pump to control him
私たちはポンプを使って彼を制御します
micro-injection into the brain
脳へのマイクロインジェクション
And then we'll measure it as behavior
次に、それを行動として測定します
So here you may have a question
ここで質問があるかもしれません
That is, why do we experiment with mice?
それは、なぜマウスを使って実験するのかということです。
i just said
私はちょうど言いました
Because of course we can't experiment directly with people.
もちろん、人を使って直接実験することはできないからです。
But there are also important features
しかし、重要な機能もあります
you probably can't believe it
おそらく信じられないでしょう
We look very different from mice, don't we?
私たちはネズミとは見た目が大きく異なりますね。
we are totally different animals
私たちは全く違う動物です
We are Qualitatively different
私たちは質的に異なります
It's not just that we don't have tails
尻尾がないだけではありません
But the homology of the mouse brain
しかし、マウスの脳の相同性は
One percent of our absolute brains
私たちの絶対的な頭脳の 1 パーセント
Our more than ninety homology
90以上の相同性
I will say this to mean
という意味でこれを言います
His brain is smaller than ours
彼の脳は私たちの脳より小さい
he has fewer neurons than us
彼は私たちよりもニューロンが少ない
but the size of each neuron
しかし、各ニューロンのサイズは
In fact, about the same as us
実は私たちと同じくらい
We put in 25 to 30
25～30個入れました
He's about 20 to 25 centimeters
体長は20～25センチくらいです
But what I just said about homology means that
しかし、相同性について私が今言ったことは、次のことを意味します。
he's in his head
彼は頭の中にいます
Where are the nerve cells in the brain?
脳の神経細胞はどこにあるのでしょうか?
What to do and what to do
何をすべきか、何をすべきか
90% of the time we endure
90％の時間、私たちは耐えます
That nerve cell is also in charge of that function in that part of our brain
その神経細胞は私たちの脳のその部分でもその機能を担当しています
this is not enough
これはたりない
That 90% to 93%
その90%から93%
So you know the results of the mouse study
マウスの研究結果はご存知ですね
many offer a
多くの人が提供しています
Because mice can reproduce in large numbers and there are many
ネズミは大量に繁殖することができ、数も多いため、
So in the mouse provides a
したがって、マウスでは、
Basic data for a scientific study
科学研究のための基礎データ
Based on these data
これらのデータに基づいて
we may do it again
またやるかも知れません
Be a dog, be a pig
犬になっても豚になっても
Then step by step are optimistic
そうすれば一歩ずつ楽観的になる
be a monkey again
また猿になる
Then start the human
それから人間を始めてください
Prikling and Spirituality Tests
チクチクと霊性のテスト
so
それで
Because in fact, the biomedical research at my old place is
なぜなら、実際、私の以前の職場での生物医学研究は、
big now
今は大きい
Based on the fact that our brains and brains are nine percent
私たちの脳と頭脳は9パーセントであるという事実に基づいて、
please
お願いします
ok , now i ' ll talk about forgetting a little bit
さて、今から少し忘れることについて話します
Then start talking about the real evidence
それから本当の証拠について話し始めます
Scientists do less about forgetting
科学者は忘れることについてほとんど何もしていない
Mainly forgetting is not so easy to do
忘れることはそう簡単なことではありません
The other is the process of forgetting
もう一つは忘れる過程です
It's actually a little simpler
実際にはもう少し単純です
That is, when your memory cannot be retrieved
つまり、記憶が取り戻せないとき
it is actually forgetting
それは実際には忘れている
So let's study memory as an example.
それでは、例として記憶を研究してみましょう。
But for the study of forgetting
しかし、忘れることの研究のために
The scientist's perception is
科学者の認識は、
It does not indicate memory loss
記憶喪失を示すものではありません
where it just stand by
ただ立っているところ
I just didn't get called out by you
ただあなたに声をかけられなかっただけです
this matter is very important
この問題はとても重要です
It means you have learned one thing
それはあなたが一つのことを学んだことを意味します
never learned from you
あなたから何も学ばなかった
you learned something
あなたは何かを学びました
you can't forget
忘れられないよ
never learned from you
あなたから何も学ばなかった
are two things
二つのことです
Wait a minute I'll show you an animation
ちょっと待ってください、アニメーションをお見せします
you have learned
あなたは学びました
Your neural network connections
ニューラル ネットワーク接続
will link up
リンクします
Then you have no way in the end and often can't remember
そうなると結局は方法がなく、思い出せないこともよくあります
because of your extraction process
抽出プロセスのせいで
The ability to call him out of the hard drive deflection
ハードドライブの偏向から彼を呼び出す能力
If you haven't learned anything at all
まったく何も学んでいない場合
His neural networks never formed
彼の神経ネットワークは決して形成されなかった
So based on this our cognition and understanding of this
したがって、これに基づいて、これに対する私たちの認識と理解は
In fact, everyone, especially young people, should try
実際、誰もが、特に若い人は試してみるべきです
Of course you don't have to learn everything
もちろんすべてを学ぶ必要はありません
but you learned something
しかし、あなたは一つのことを学びました
Forget that you have never learned before
忘れることは、学ばなかったことと同じではありません
Yes, the networked nature of the nervous system
そう、神経系のネットワーク化された性質です。
In terms of connectivity and full utilization
接続性とフル活用の観点から
Learning is basically good
勉強は基本的に良いものです
That can be explained like this
それは次のように説明できます
Physician means that you have been genetically
医師とは、あなたが遺伝的にそうであることを意味します
Those neural pathways and nerve protrusions are still there.
これらの神経経路と神経突起はまだ存在しています。
he just wasn't sparked
彼はただ興奮しなかっただけだ
You'll have to wait until the proper stimulus comes along
適切な刺激が来るまで待たなければなりません
His gene was extracted
彼の遺伝子が抽出された
Then this you forgot that decline theory, that's it
じゃあ、あなたはその衰退理論を忘れてしまいました、それだけです
Memories are just beginning to form
思い出はまだ形成され始めたばかりです
strong at first
最初は強い
but you don't remember it
でもあなたはそれを覚えていない
you don't extract it
あなたはそれを抽出しません
don't even remember it
それさえ覚えていない
You slowly slowly this will disappear
ゆっくりゆっくりこれが消えていくよ
But if you often use it
でもよく使うなら
Rehearsal is to review again
リハーサルはもう一度見直すこと
Practice and extract
練習して抜粋する
then this memory will come back
そうすればこの記憶は戻ってくるだろう
So sometimes at a certain age
だから時々、ある年齢になると
a certain age
ある程度の年齢
more things to remember
もっと覚えるべきこと
That is to say, it is always good to remember
つまり、常に覚えておくと良いということです
because you reactivate your neural pathways
神経経路を再活性化するため
Of course we want to try to remember as much as possible
もちろん、できるだけ覚えておきたいと思っています
happy things
幸せなこと
It's really important to remember this event
この出来事を覚えておくことは本当に重要です
but i just said
でも私は今言いました
actually forgotten
実は忘れられていた
Originally Uyghur Church
もともとはウイグル教会
Forgetting is also very important
忘れることもとても大切です
because we just talk
私たちはただ話しているだけなので
Life is not as good as eight or nine at a time
人生は一度に8人や9人ほど良いものではない
So in fact we humans are
ですから実際のところ、私たち人間は、
tend to forget things
物事を忘れる傾向がある
it's again once
もう一度です
This is it
これだよ
It's a neuroprotective mechanism
それは神経保護メカニズムです
because we don't want to make ourselves
自分たちで作りたくないから
often caught in that pleasant thing
よくその楽しいことに囚われてしまう
emotion and experience
感情と経験
So oblivion is a very important reporter
つまり、忘却は非常に重要なレポーターです
It's just that the first-class ones can't forget, so they can't forget
ただ、一流の人は忘れられないから忘れられないのです。
Otherwise, it doesn't matter if you forget something
そうでなければ、何かを忘れても問題ありません
Then the animation below tells us that
次に、以下のアニメーションは次のことを示しています。
he uses a
他用一個
That is to say, in fact, forgetting can be done less
つまり、実際には、忘れることは少なくなる可能性があります
Just because something went wrong with the extraction process
抽出プロセスで何か問題が発生したため
He has no problem forming
彼は形成に何の問題もありません
he is still there
彼はまだそこにいる
after that neural pathway
その神経経路の後に
Because in the beginning he will have a few footprints running on his mind
なぜなら最初は彼の頭の中にいくつかの足跡が残るからです
What he means is that when you are learning something
彼が言いたいのは、何かを学んでいると、
That way will pass and you will form a memory
そうすれば過ぎていき、思い出が形成されるでしょう
Then there seems to be a high-speed road like mine
そうしたら、私のような高速道路があるようです
It's very smooth to play in all directions
全方向にプレイするのは非常にスムーズです
But if you forget later
でも後で忘れてしまったら
That road seems to be closed
その道は閉ざされているようです
just like different venues
別の会場と同じように
He is hoped that education will often use some very
彼は、教育が非常に優れたものを頻繁に使用することを望んでいます。
Very deep animation as an example
非常に奥深いアニメーションの例
Then let beginners this will be more of a
それなら、初心者はもっと簡単になります。
good spirituality
良い精神性
so everyone can ring the bell
そうすれば誰もが鐘を鳴らすことができます
Didn't get to this point
ここまでは至らなかった
so he just told us
それで彼はちょうど私たちに言いました
words that have been learning
勉強してきた言葉
that way is usually
通常はその方法です
you forget it's just the way
あなたはそれがただの方法であることを忘れています
not usually
不通常
but it still exists
しかしそれはまだ存在します
So it's good to learn more
だからもっと学ぶのは良いことだ
and
と
Old age should be like this
老後はこうあるべきだ
I'll give you some more data later
後でもう少しデータを提供します
tell us everybody is saying
みんなが言っていることを教えてください
no matter live to old age
老後まで生きても
It is actually very useful to learn the old saying
古いことわざを学ぶことは実際に非常に役立ちます
what factors are there now
今どんな要因があるのか
affect the formation of our memories
私たちの記憶の形成に影響を与える
Then this is the early research
それならこれは初期の研究です
but i started last year
でも去年から始めた
When the annual scientific meeting is approved
年次学術集会が承認されたとき
Found this research and came back
この研究を見つけて戻ってきました
there are many
沢山あります
Sleep is actually the formation of our memories
睡眠は実際には記憶の形成です
a great help
大きな助け
In the past three days, I just cite these representative
過去 3 日間で、以下の代表的なものを引用しました。
Like both sides are very good journals
どちらもとても良い雑誌です
tell us that
それを教えてください
If Guodu sleeps
郭都が眠ったら
deprivation of sleep
睡眠的deprivation
affect memory formation
記憶形成に影響を与える
let affect memory formation
記憶形成に影響を与えよう
It will affect the pain road formed
それは形成された痛みの道に影響を与えます
So it's really a good way to learn
それは本当に素晴らしい学習方法です
just the way you remember
あなたが覚えている通りに
after you learn one thing
一つのことを学んだ後
if you let your nerve cells
神経細胞を放っておけば
if you have enough rest
十分な休息があれば
actually you will remember this
実際、あなたはこれを覚えているでしょう
remember best
一番よく覚えておいてください
learn to keep in mind
心に留めておくことを学ぶ
In psychology there's something called the Interference Theory
心理学には干渉理論と呼ばれるものがあります
Let's interview this theory
この理論をインタビューしましょう
What I hate the most is what you are learning now
私が一番嫌いなことは、あなたが今学んでいることです
You haven't solidified these neurons yet
これらのニューロンはまだ固まっていません
We are talking about Hab and Consolidation theory
Hab と統合理論について話しています。
haven't made it solid yet
まだ固まっていない
you go to learn the next one
あなたは次のことを学びに行きます
After learning A, learn B
Aを学んだ後はBを学ぶ
B has not yet consolidated
Bはまだ統合されていません
A is not consolidated yet
Aはまだ統合されていません
You go to learn C again
もう一度 C を学びに行きます
This is the worst in terms of long-term memory
これは長期記憶という点では最悪です
But I don't want when I was a student
でも学生の頃は嫌だった
This is the most used
これが一番よく使われます
here small is by english
ここの小さいのは英語です
The next elementary school is to do some math
次の小学校は算数をすることになっています
Then by Guowen, right?
それからGuowenさんですよね？
I can't remember anything
何も思い出せない
but it's okay
しかし、それは大丈夫です
That's useful for coming here for the exam
試験のためにここに来るのに役立ちます
because we were originally
なぜなら私たちはもともと
just want it to go further in the short term
短期的にはさらに前進したいだけです
You just pass the exam
ただ試験に合格するだけです
But interviews are better than long-term memory
しかし、インタビューは長期記憶よりも優れています
this is not good
これは良くない
You're really serious about making it stand in long term memory
長期記憶に残すことに真剣に取り組んでいます
you should learn later
後で学ぶべきです
rest or sleep
休むか寝るか
let those nerve cells
神経細胞を放っておいてください
Repeatedly can form a pathway loop
繰り返して経路ループが形成される可能性がある
and then allow it to form long-term memory
そしてそれが長期記憶を形成できるようにします
That
それか
Yes, I know a lot of people have this insomnia problem
はい、多くの人がこの不眠症の問題を抱えていることは知っています
I would feel
私が感じるだろう
sleep is really important
睡眠は本当に大切です
So if you really have serious insomnia problems
もしあなたが本当に深刻な不眠症の問題を抱えているなら
I think it's time to go to the doctor and prescribe some medicine.
医者に行って薬を処方してもらう時期だと思います。
i have friends to eat
食べる友達がいる
I've been taking this insomnia pill for 20 years
私はこの不眠症の薬を20年間服用しています
I think it's okay too
それも大丈夫だと思います
you don't see any very bad effects
あまり悪い影響は見られません
Because you can at least help you after you take the medicine
少なくとも薬を飲んだ後は助けてもらえるから
Don't even think about sleeping for seven or eight hours
7時間も8時間も寝ることさえ考えないでください
at least this medicine may help
少なくともこの薬は役に立つかもしれない
Might be able to help a person sleep more than four hours
人の睡眠を4時間以上助けることができるかもしれない
get a good four hours of sleep
4時間しっかり睡眠をとる
I can't sleep with you drenched
ずぶ濡れになった君と一緒には眠れない
much worse
ずっと悪いです
Because we sleep a lot in four hours
4時間でたくさん寝れるから
Wave cycle
波の周期
means you sleep for four hours
4時間寝ることを意味します
you are basically a sleeper
あなたは基本的に寝ている人です
Let's talk about the complete cycle
完全なサイクルについて話しましょう
This is actually very important
これは実はとても重要なことなのです
so i think
だから私は思う
There are some medicines that are so effective
こんなに効く薬もあるんですね
because sleep is more important
睡眠の方が大事だから
So you can take that bad effect of the medicine
だからあなたは薬の悪い影響を和らげることができます
I think it can be put second
2番目に置いてもいいと思います
You know that report I don't know where he's watching
彼がどこを見ているのかわからないレポートを知っていますよね
Most used medicine in the world
世界で最も使用されている薬
It's like a drug for insomnia
不眠症の薬のようなものだ
only high blood pressure
高血圧だけ
Only what cholesterol medicine
コレステロールの薬だけ
So people with insomnia all over the world will ask me how much
それで、世界中の不眠症に悩む人々が私にいくらかと尋ねるでしょう。
and depression
とうつ病
This is also a bit troublesome
これもちょっと面倒です
Let's wait until we get to parenchyma
実質に到達するまで待ちましょう
let's talk a little about depression
うつ病について少し話しましょう
ok this is sleep
はい、これは睡眠です
Because what I'm citing you are all about the age of science
なぜなら私があなたに引用しているのは科学の時代だからです
research report
調査報告書
i'm not...
私はそうではありません...
I have no ill intentions
悪意はありません
I said that when you usually look for this car, it becomes oppressive.
普段この車を探すと圧迫感があると言いました。
and then you just take it
そしてそれを受け取るだけです
not necessarily so
必ずしもそうではない
you just look at where that one came from
それがどこから来たのかを見てください
The source of those news
それらのニュースのソース
If it is really a report of scientific research
それが本当に科学研究の報告書であれば
Where is the word
その言葉はどこにありますか
you are more inclined to believe
あなたは信じる傾向が強いです
one more important thing
もう一つ重要なこと
This is something we can control
これは私たちがコントロールできることです
is sports
スポーツです
This was done as early as 1990
これは 1990 年にはすでに行われていました
Exercise can help boost memory
運動は記憶力を高めるのに役立ちます
so good thing this is us
とても良かった、これが私たちだ
that we can control
私たちがコントロールできること
Then exercise can cause some catastrophes of nerve blood hair
その場合、運動は神経血毛の重大な障害を引き起こす可能性があります
We finally have a very important neurotrophic factor
非常に重要な神経栄養因子がついに見つかりました
neurotrophic factor
神経栄養因子
It translates into brain circle neurotrophic factor in Chinese
中国語では脳円神経栄養因子と訳されます。
Randy Rive Neutropic Better
ランディ・ライブ 好中性向性改善
Experiments in mice tell us
マウスの実験が教えてくれる
This is a big white horse that has not been exercised
これは運動されていない大きな白い馬です
This is the weather for rats to exercise
ネズミが運動する日和です
Activities such as running rollers, etc.
ローラーランニングなどのアクティビティ
After the weather
氣天以後
It uses a special developer
特殊な現像液を使用しています
Let you see that is the red part
それが赤い部分であることがわかります
orange part
オレンジ色の部分
It's this VDN, the neurotrophic factor
それはこの VDN、神経栄養因子です
new place
新しいところ
this thing is very important
これはとても重要なことです
It's not just about our learning genes
それは私たちの学習遺伝子だけの問題ではありません
It is related to the protection of neurodegenerative diseases
神経変性疾患の保護に関連しています
but you can't eat it
でも食べられない
you can't buy any of this
これは何も買えません
it can't synthesize
それは合成できません
And it's useless if you eat it
そして食べたらダメだよ
It's impenetrable to what we call cerebrovascular barriers
いわゆる脳血管関門を通過できません
so what you put in your mouth
それで口に入れたものは
out of my mind
私の心の外に
Our nerve blood hair will synthesize itself
私たちの神経血毛は自己合成します
so you just have enough
それで十分です
Basic Cellular Drugs
基本的な細胞薬
protein fat
タンパク質脂肪
carb throat
炭水化物のど
minerals blah blah blah
ミネラルなんとかなんとかなんとか
as long as you have
あなたが持っている限り
these should have things
これらには物があるはずです
our nerve cells
私たちの神経細胞
will make
作る予定です
BDF comes
BDFが来る
these good things come
これらの良いことが起こる
But if you go to exercise today
でも、今日運動に行くなら
you can see
見ることができます
this thing will increase
これは増えるだろう
so this is
それでこれは
The published natural
公開されたナチュラル
natural difference
自然差異
no tell everyone
いいえ、みんなに言いません
In fact, as early as 695
実際、695 年にはすでに
there are such reports
そのような報告があります
so
それで
Everyone wants to let their learning
誰もが自分自身の学びを作りたいと思っています
good with skills
スキルが良い
just wait and listen
ただ待って聞いてください
Can't find it, go for a run
見つからない、走ってみましょう
that video is
そのビデオは
look
見て
let you see
見てみましょう
How can I be
どうして私はなれるの？
neurotrophic factor
神経栄養因子
nerve growth factor
神経成長因子
added to the cells
セルに追加される
look at this cell
この細胞を見てください
long case
ロングケース
It is different from not adding water
水を加えないのとは違います
Wait a minute, the screen will be cut like this
ちょっと待ってください、このように画面が切れます
There is no addition in the lower left corner
左下隅には追加はありません
There is a plus in the upper right corner
右上隅にプラスがあります
so give you some
だから、いくつかあげてください
real evidence
本当の証拠
The substance was added to the neurons on the right.
物質は右側のニューロンに追加されました。
Axons are growing rapidly.
軸索は急速に成長しています。
Restoration of brain function begins with this new growth.
脳機能の回復は、この新しい成長から始まります。
Some researchers speculate that nerve growth factor
一部の研究者は、神経成長因子が
helps account for the flexible wiring in the brain.
脳内の柔軟な配線を説明するのに役立ちます。
A site like this,
このようなサイトでは、
neurons sprouting fibers and establishing new connections.
ニューロンは線維を発芽させ、新しい接続を確立します。
Dismetals are previous notions about the brain's stepping
ディスメタルは脳のステップに関する以前の概念です
and hard-wired character.
そして堅実な性格。
Sorry, she's completely in English
申し訳ありませんが、彼女は完全に英語です
Because her class is in English
彼女の授業は英語なので
That is to say, emotions can affect our learning
つまり、感情は学習に影響を与える可能性があるということです
What she said was
彼女が言ったのは、
We learn best when we are...
私たちが最もよく学ぶのは、次のときです...
We...
私たち...
Go...
行く...
When we are...
私たちがいるとき...
just go and dance
ただ行って踊ってください
right
右
that is
あれは
Excuse me, this word is wrong by comp'ing pace
すみません、ペースを合わせるとこの単語は間違っています
Tell Reel when we are happy
幸せなときはリールに伝えてください
When we are happy and reel nice
私たちが幸せで素敵なとき
I'll fix it now
今すぐ修正します
Otherwise you are too serious
そうでないと真面目すぎる
我們Learn best when we are...
私たちがいるときに最もよく学ぶことができます...
when we are...
私たちがいるとき...
a bit hot
少し暑い
We don't think we're stressed either
私たちもストレスを感じていないと思います
she told us
彼女は私たちに言いました
when we are in a happy
私たちが幸せなとき
when in a relaxed situation
リラックスした状況のとき
Our ability to learn is the best
私たちの学習能力は最高です
So everyone has to find a way
だから誰もが方法を見つけなければならない
tell myself
自分に言い聞かせる
You have to learn in this situation like this
このような状況で学ばなければなりません
If you really are that day
本当にあの日なら
very upset very frustrated
とても動揺している とてもイライラしている
very bad mood very angry
とても機嫌が悪い とても怒っている
you don't go
あなたは行かない
Because it may be a waste of time to learn
学ぶのは時間の無駄かもしれないから
just go change it
それを変更しに行ってください
What is the effect of learning so poorly?
勉強が下手だとどんな影響があるのでしょうか？
is when a person is anxious
それは人が不安になっているときです
It's really hard to learn when you're under a lot of pressure
大きなプレッシャーにさらされていると、学ぶのは本当に難しい
So you don't want to learn at this time
だから今は学びたくないのね
How to learn at the same time
同時に学ぶ方法
adjust this pressure
この圧力を調整してください
This is the unlearned chapter of neurohistory for psychologists
これは心理学者にとっての神経史の知られていない章です
I am now a comprehensive bad picture
今では全体的に悪いイメージになってしまいました
Talk about a situation of stress and study
ストレスのある状況や勉強について話す
we are
私たちです
degree of stress
ストレスの程度
when we are under no pressure
プレッシャーがないとき
In fact, our ability to learn is not good
実際、私たちの学習能力は良くありません
moderate pressure
適度な圧力
Human competition is always sympathy
人間の競争は常に共感です
same power
同動力
so take it slow
だからゆっくりしてください
when slowly increasing
ゆっくり増やしていくと
to a degree
程度に
is our ability to learn
私たちの学習能力です
at your best
最高の状態で
But after this
しかしこの後
will come down again
また降りてくるだろう
I think everyone will agree with this picture
この写真には誰もが同意すると思います
You're thinking of all the countries you've studied a lot
あなたはたくさん勉強したすべての国のことを考えています
so we
だから私たちは
We must let ourselves that pressure
私たちはそのプレッシャーを自分自身に与えなければなりません
the best place to be
最高の場所
give us moderate pressure
適度な圧力をかけてください
but not big
でも大きくない
Because this is the domain of psychiatry
ここは精神科の領域なので
A lot of stress can lead to depression
ストレスが多いとうつ病になる可能性がある
So we figured out that
それで私たちはそれを理解しました
Let us learn with such giri
そんなギリで学ぼう
But let's not let ourselves be in
でも、自分自身を巻き込まないようにしましょう
Study without stress
ストレスなく勉強できる
Because what you learn will be of no use
学んだことは何の役にも立たないから
Everyone, you will talk later
皆さん、後で話しましょう
We have nothing to do with people
私たちは人々とは何の関係もありません
Our human genes have more than 99.5% homology
私たちの人間の遺伝子は 99.5% 以上の相同性を持っています
no bladder
膀胱がない
we are very close people
私たちはとても親しい人たちです
But the tolerance of each of us to stress
しかし、私たち一人ひとりのストレスに対する耐性は、
or how we look at the same stimulus
または同じ刺激を私たちがどのように見ているか
The same stimulus teaches different pressures to different people
同じ刺激が異なる人に異なるプレッシャーを与える
Everyone disagrees with this
誰もがこれに同意しない
So there might be an individual
だから個人もいるかもしれない
It's stimulating all the time like this
こうやってずっと刺激してるんだよ
it's so low pressure
とても低気圧です
then slowly
それからゆっくりと
So when the stimulus increases
それで刺激が増えると
it pressures up
圧力がかかる
It's just that the pressure has been so great
ただプレッシャーがすごく大きかったです
it's bad if it goes on
このままだとダメだ
But some people may be equally stimulated
でも同じように刺激を受ける人もいるかもしれない
This stimulation must be so strong
この刺激はとても強いはずです
He felt the pressure
彼はプレッシャーを感じた
then stimulate even there
そこでも刺激する
he might as well
彼もそうかもしれない
In addition to individual participation
個人での参加だけでなく、
Because in fact individual participation is
なぜなら、実際には個人の参加は
is hard to tune
チューニングが難しい
you can't make yourself into someone else
自分を他人にすることはできない
you will not be equal to him
あなたは彼と同等ではないでしょう
but i think we
でも私たちはそう思う
little of these relationships
これらの関係はほとんどありません
One thing to learn is
学ぶべきことの 1 つは、
you adjust yourself
あなたは自分自身を調整します
you let this thrill
あなたはこのスリルを許してくれる
It would have been such a little stimulation
ちょっとした刺激だったかもしれない
stimulus like this
このような刺激
The stimulation in the medium will make you so stressed
媒体の刺激はとてもストレスになります
You try to move this curve to the right
この曲線を右に移動させようとすると、
adjust yourself
自分を調整する
through their own education
自らの教育を通じて
or remind yourself
または自分に思い出させてください
accumulation of experience, etc.
経験の蓄積など。
you make you the same stimulus
あなたも同じ刺激を与えます
The pressure he generates is only so low
彼が生み出すプレッシャーは非常に低い
This is what we need for a healthy life
これは健康的な生活に必要なものです
talk button
トークボタン
just with
ちょうど
To resist pressure and external
外部からの圧力に抵抗するために
all sorts of things out of control
あらゆる種類のことが制御不能になっている
say we tried it ourselves
自分たちで試してみたと言う
to do this kind of adjustment
このような調整をするために
Actually this is really
実はこれ、本当にあるんです
You are
あなたは
There is no way to teach this
これを教える方法はありません
to teach
教的
but
しかし
you know the pressure right
あなたはプレッシャーを正しく知っています
learning team memory
学習チームの思い出
bad about many things
多くのことで悪い
we try to do something like this
私たちはこのようなことをしようとしています
well , our last half hour
さて、最後の30分
Let's talk about Hayworth
ヘイワースについて話しましょう
We just talked about the topic "Lions Formation"
先ほど「ライオンズのフォーメーション」というテーマについてお話しました。
"Lions" is a collective term
「ライオンズ」は総称です
Azhewar formation is inside the lion formation
アゼワール層はライオン層の中にあります
the most proportion of the most
最も多くの割合
It translates "Azihaiwo Formation" in English
「アジハイウォ層」を英語に訳すと
or the most common one
または最も一般的なもの
There are estimated to be Alzheimer's patients worldwide
世界中にアルツハイマー病患者がいると推定されている
30 million people
3,000万人
Actually this is
実はこれは
a little bit
若干
only underestimate not overestimate
過小評価するだけで過大評価しない
because some people
なぜなら一部の人は
especially likely in a certain area of ​​cultural science and technology medicine
特に文化科学技術医学の特定の分野でその可能性が高い
He's not going to see a doctor
彼は医者にかかるつもりはない
So there are still some underestimated possibilities
したがって、まだ過小評価されている可能性がいくつかあります
But with technological civilization
しかし、テクノロジー文明によって
Advances in medicine are really commanded to prolong
医学の進歩には長期化が不可欠です
In fact, the population is increasing
実際に人口は増えている
but there is a
しかし、ある
One thing might be better
一つ良いことがあるかもしれない
It has nothing to do with genetics
遺伝とか関係ないよ
Ninety percent of the patients we see
私たちが診察する患者さんの90パーセントは、
Azhewar's Trouble
アゼワールの悩み
it is last come
最後に来ました
it is the key factor
それが重要な要素です
non-genetic factors
非遺伝的要因
Sportradiq speaks like this in English
Sportradiqは英語でこのように話します
Only less than 10% of patients are genetic
遺伝性の患者はわずか 10% 未満です
It's if the people who are in the family have hydrogen, hydrogen, hydrogen, hydrogen
水素水素水素水素水素を家に持っている人が持っていればです。
he has a better chance
彼にはもっと良いチャンスがある
But such a population is relatively small
しかし、そのような人口は比較的少ないです
Genetic factors compared patients with a large distinction under
遺伝的要因は、以下の点で大きな違いがある患者を比較しました。
He had an early onset
彼は早期に発症した
Sometimes the 50s start
時には50代が始まることもある
This is a characteristic of patients with genetically
これは遺伝的疾患を持つ患者の特徴です。
Then clinically tell us
それから臨床的に教えてください
From the time the patient is symptomatic
患者さんに症状が出た時から
just can't remember things he can't remember
彼は思い出せないものを思い出せないだけだ
He has been confirmed to be symptomatic by a doctor since he had symptoms
症状が出たため医師から症状があると診断された
He usually lives 8 to 20 years
通常8～20年生きます
this range is very large
この範囲は非常に広いです
On the one hand, individual differences
一方で個人差はありますが、
Then after a person is diagnosed
そして、人が診断された後、
His progression is the evolution of this stage of the disease
彼の進行は病気のこの段階の進化です
Some people evolve quickly and some people don't
すぐに進化する人もいるし、そうでない人もいる
And every time a patient goes to see a doctor
そして、患者が医師の診察を受けるたびに、
His degree is different
彼の学位は違う
Some people are very slight, some people are very strong
とても軽い人もいれば、とても強い人もいます
is it serious
それは深刻ですか
Then why do you say often
ではなぜよく言うのですか
For example, to see a doctor for a doctor's diagnosis
たとえば、医師の診断を受けるために医師の診察を受けること。
that's what's wrong with saying
それは言うのが間違っているのです
Usually the nerve cells die
通常は神経細胞が死ぬ
can't regenerate
再生できない
we just talked
私たちはちょうど話したばかりです
So actually
それで実際には
what the doctor can handle
医者が対処できること
just let the course
コースに任せてください
slow down
徐行
Actually there is no way
実際には方法がありません
no way
とんでもない
let that cell grow back
その細胞を再び成長させましょう
That's usually when you see symptoms occur
通常、症状が現れるのはこのときです
At this time, I have a stomachache in my head
この時、頭の中がお腹が痛くなりました
It's like yelling at these people for kneeling
この人たちに土下座して怒鳴っているようなものだ
or big old sebum
または大きな古い皮脂
30% of the nerve cells have died
神経細胞の30％が死滅している
Only then will there be symptoms
そうして初めて症状が現れる
then you will feel
そうすればあなたは感じるでしょう
why doesn't it just die
なぜそのまま死なないのか
5% have symptoms
5％に症状がある
that way
そうやって
not just us
私たちだけではありません
We could have caught it early
早めに捕まえることができたかもしれない
so our nerve cells
つまり私たちの神経細胞は
is a feature
特徴です
they are very united
彼らはとても団結しています
as a nerve cell
神経細胞として
or when a few nerve cells are injured
またはいくつかの神経細胞が損傷した場合
in these nerve cells
これらの神経細胞の中で
nearby nerve cells
近くの神経細胞
will rush past
急いで通り過ぎます
share the function of this nerve cell
この神経細胞の機能を共有します
so what is it supposed to do
それで、それは何をするべきですか
Its neighbors will help it do this
その隣人がこれを助けるだろう
So each neuron will do 10% more
したがって、各ニューロンは 10% 多くのことを行うことになります
do more do more
もっとやれ、もっとやれ
just take what he should do
彼がやるべきことをただ引き受ける
just did it
やったところです
But wait until these surrounding nerve cells
しかし、周囲の神経細胞が現れるまで待ってください。
can't reproduce
再現できない
he is so tired
彼はとても疲れている
worn out
使い古した
When I can't copy myself
自分をコピーできないとき
Symptoms will appear at this time
この時期に症状が現れる
It is because our nerve cells have such characteristics
それは私たちの神経細胞がそのような性質を持っているからです
So think about us humans really
だから私たち人間について本当に考えてください
Should learn from our neurocytology
私たちの神経細胞学から学ぶべきです
This is why we doctors see symptoms and say
これが、私たち医師が症状を見てこう言う理由です。
it's too late
もう手遅れです
what risk factor does he have
彼にはどのような危険因子があるのか
because i really really am not a doctor
私は本当に本当に医者ではないので
so i have to be conservative
だから私は保守的でなければなりません
I'm just summarizing some results for you
いくつかの結果を要約してご紹介します
from danger we know
私たちが知っている危険から
A real risk factor for Azheyor
アズヘイウォにとっての本当のリスク要因
The first is aging
一つ目は老化です
His agreement is very high
彼の同意は非常に高い
there is no way
道はない
hidden by aging
老化によって隠された
It's the neurons that are dying
死んでいくのはニューロンです
So your chances increase
それでチャンスが増える
because you can use neurons
ニューロンを使えるから
no more
もういや
because a nerve cell
神経細胞だ​​から
Everyone has 1000 years
誰にでも1000年はある
Once he dies, he won't have the thousand yuan.
彼が死んだら、その千元はなくなる。
this is the case
これは事実です
Then let's leave him alone
それなら彼を放っておこう
Because I have no one in the middle who can fight aging
老化に対抗できる真ん中の人がいないから
there is something else
他に何かあります
Exercise helps you sleep better
運動すると睡眠が良くなります
make you feel better
気分を良くしてください
reduce stress and more
ストレスを軽減するなど
Another is oxidative stress
もう一つは酸化ストレスです
We just said that Xie Baoli is constantly oxidizing and reducing
Xie Baoli は常に酸化と還元を行っていると言いました。
oxidative buffers that work
機能する酸化緩衝剤
there are things like stimulation
刺激のようなものがあります
There are some stimuli such as stress, etc.
ストレスなどの刺激もあります。
make our body produce
私たちの体が生成するようにする
autooxidative stress
自己酸化ストレス
But it's already called free radicals for farmers
しかし、農家にとってはすでにフリーラジカルと呼ばれています
Free-reduce
フリーリデュース
it is some very unstable atoms
それは非常に不安定な原子です
so it's annoying
だから迷惑だよ
When the oxidative stress is too high
酸化ストレスが高すぎる場合
produce more free radicals
より多くのフリーラジカルを生成する
These free radicals make our cells
これらのフリーラジカルは私たちの細胞を作ります
Watch cells pour out of colliding cells inside
内部で衝突するセルからセルが流れ出す様子を観察してください
Then it will burst our cell nest
そうすればそれは私たちの細胞の巣を破裂させるでしょう
Then finally let's what
それでは最後に何をしましょう
Cuboids also break
直方体も壊れる
Then let's get into the cell reasonably
それでは適当に独房に入りましょう
Let's break DNA
DNAを壊しましょう
So it makes these cells what
それで、これらの細胞は何を作るのですか
So find ways to reduce oxidative stress
したがって、酸化ストレスを軽減する方法を見つけてください
is also very important
も非常に重要です
In addition, genetic mutation
さらに、遺伝子変異
this too
これも
Too...
それも...
what do we know about mental mutations
精神の突然変異について私たちは何を知っていますか
but we can't
でも私たちは助けることができません
There is no way to control our teacher
私たちの先生をコントロールする方法はありません
which elites mutate
どのエリートが突然変異するのか
This elite mutation is too much trouble
このエリート突然変異は面倒すぎる
it's not just dementia
それは認知症だけではありません
Cancer, cancer is a very important factor
がん、がんは非常に重要な要素です
Also an elite mutant
エリートミュータントでもある
Then another hypothesis is that nerve inflammation
そして、もう一つの仮説は、神経の炎症です。
because we know that nerve cells
私たちは神経細胞を知っているので、
between nerve cells
神経細胞の間
In fact, there are some microglial cells
実際には、いくつかのミクログリア細胞が存在します
Those cells release some inflammatory factors
これらの細胞はいくつかの炎症因子を放出します
So one hypothesis is that nerve cells
したがって、1 つの仮説は、神経細胞が
Inflammation of nerve cells can cause
神経細胞の炎症により引き起こされる可能性がある
is a factor in dementia
認知症の要因である
The other one is definitely a brain injury
もう一つは間違いなく脳損傷です
Whether internal or external
内部でも外部でも
like you are swollen
腫れているように
or hit outside, car or whatever
あるいは外、車などにぶつかったり
after a brain injury
脳損傷の後
Nerve cells die
神経細胞が死ぬ
with degeneration and atrophy
変性と萎縮を伴う
so of course
だからもちろん
For more than just dementia
認知症以外にも
For many diseases of neurons
神経細胞の多くの病気に
it's all about brain injury
それはすべて脳損傷に関するものです
So after rehab or a brain injury
リハビリや脳損傷の後
I want to study here to learn more
もっと詳しく知りたいのでここで勉強したいです
something with memories
思い出のある何か
You rewire your neural network
ニューラルネットワークを再配線する
this matter is very important
この問題はとても重要です
but there are other
しかし他にもあります
known or unknown factors
既知または未知の要因
The patient who was needled overseas in Az
海外アリゾナ州で針を刺された患者
How does the doctor judge
医師はどう判断するのか
very simple
とてもシンプルな
this disease is very troublesome
この病気はとても厄介です
But he has only two very important characteristics
しかし、彼には非常に重要な特徴が 2 つだけあります
I'll show you later
後で見せます
Positive cancer in this patient
この患者の癌は陽性です
Because we shouldn't have plaques on our brains
脳にプラークがあってはいけないから
But the patients who received injections overseas in Az
しかし、海外のアリゾナ州で注射を受けた患者たちは、
There are some weird plaques on the brain
脳に奇妙なプラークがいくつかあります
Then this plaque dominates the nerve
そして、このプラークが神経を支配します
transfer of information to and from nerves
神経との間での情報の伝達
one is
一つは
create some tangles of nerve fibers in there
そこに神経線維のもつれが生じる
like line
線のようなもの
A lot of lines will form a ball like this
たくさんの線がこのようにボールを形成します
Nerve fibrillary tangles are primarily a
神経原線維もつれは主に
Tao's protein
タオのプロテイン
it's annoying
気に障る
Then show everyone
じゃあみんなに見せてよ
A soap called A
Aという石鹸
These are the two proteins that shouldn't be there
これらは存在すべきではない 2 つのタンパク質です
Or he shouldn't have so many
それとも彼はそんなにたくさん持っているべきではない
once got
一度手に入れた
will find a fault
欠点を見つけるだろう
this
これ
tell you if you lie
嘘なら言ってください
This is the plaque
これがそのプラークです
you can see normal cells
正常な細胞が見える
neurovascular bladder
神経血管膀胱
it's clean
きれいです
That kind of micro-selling is clear
この種のマイクロセリングは明らかです
But something like this is from an Alzheimer's patient
しかし、このようなものはアルツハイマー病患者からのものです
Keeping the collar like this schematic
襟をこの図のように保つ
This is not the whole, this is a schematic
これは全体ではありません、これは概略図です
this plaque
このプラーク
But it's also plaque, it shouldn't be here
でもそれもプラークだからここにあるべきではない
but it blocks the connection between the neurohemocoel and the neurohemocoel
しかし、それは神経血腔と神経血腔の間の接続を遮断します
This is the result of our own time
これは私たち自身の時代の結果です
We intentionally made this
私たちは意図的にこれを作りました
The chemical that forms the plaque
プラークを形成する化学物質
This drug, it deliberately hits the brain of the mouse
この薬はマウスの脳を故意に攻撃する
After a while, break, encounter a
しばらくすると休憩、遭遇
it forms these plaques
これらのプラークを形成します
This is the photo on the poster
これがポスターの写真です
Because I'm afraid that the poster has this copyright, what's the problem
投稿者に著作権があるのではないかと思うのですが、何が問題なのでしょうか？
so I usually use
だから私は通常使用します
I experimented with this result myself to make this poster
このポスターを作成するために、この結果を自分で実験してみました
I'm afraid that the poster will follow later
投稿者は後から来ると思います
Westerners see what they say is this copyright
西洋人は、これが著作権であると彼らが言うことを理解しています
So certify this rat brain here
だからこのネズミの脳をここで証明してください
should be clean
きれいでなければなりません
But these plaques
しかし、これらのプラークは
So you're saying that the mouse experiment is still helpful.
つまり、マウスの実験はまだ役に立つということですね。
because it can
それができるから
A tool that provides us with some basic research
基礎的な研究を提供するツール
This is another experimental picture, you can see the normal
これは別の実験写真です。正常な状態がわかります。
Nerve cells look like this
神経細胞はこんな感じ
Then another Azhai man becomes a cell
その後、別のアズハイ人が独房になる
it will have these plaques
これらのプラークが付いています
This is between cells
これは細胞と細胞の間です
And inside the cell it has these tangles
そして細胞の中にはこれらのもつれがあります
did you see
あなたは見ましたか
These entanglements are annoying
こういう絡みは迷惑だよな
It ends up making our skeleton protein
それは最終的に私たちの骨格タンパク質を作ることになります
Today the protein is disintegrated from it one by one
今日はそこからタンパク質が一つ一つ分解されていく
disintegrate, disintegrate
崩壊する、崩壊する
In the end, of course, this nerve cell can't survive.
もちろん、最終的にはこの神経細胞は生き残ることができません。
this is another image
これは別の画像です
plaque
プラーク
These are the kinks
これらがねじれです
You can see it's like some balls of string
糸の玉のようなものであることがわかります
together
一緒
Where did those plaques come from?
それらの銘板はどこから来たのでしょうか?
I'm speaking very simply
私はとても簡単に話しています
don't look at these
これらを見ないでください
There's a protein in the back of our brain called this
私たちの脳の後ろにはこれと呼ばれるタンパク質があります
APP for short
略してアプリ
It is cleaved by some enzymes
何らかの酵素によって切断される
it will generate this thing
これを生成します
There are 42 amino acids
アミノ酸は42個あります
It's called A-beta 42
それはAベータ42と呼ばれています
this thing is disgusting too
これも嫌なことだ
It accumulates and causes Alzheimer's disease
蓄積してアルツハイマー病を引き起こす
Then you say why it accumulates
じゃあなぜ溜まるのか言うと
We normal people also have this protein
私たち一般人もこのタンパク質を持っています
will also factor out this
これも考慮に入れます
Just the words of us normal people
私たち普通の人の言葉です
It will have a normal data metabolized
通常のデータが代謝されます
But in Alzheimer's patients
しかしアルツハイマー病患者では
just maybe
かもしれないだけ
Something went wrong with some metabolic pathways
一部の代謝経路に問題が発生しました
and aging
そして老化
There are some other questions that I don't know
他にも分からない質問がいくつかあります
factors such as genetic pathways
遺伝的経路などの要因
These people are more likely to accumulate this protein
これらの人々はこのタンパク質を蓄積する可能性が高くなります
It is the protein that will cause these methods
これらの方法を引き起こすのはタンパク質です
this is a normal cell
これは正常な細胞です
This is a dying cell
これは死にかけている細胞です
So the branches are not
したがって、枝はそうではありません
Then slowly the cells will shrink
そしてゆっくりと細胞は縮小していきます
This is where we live in my actual life
ここが私の実際の生活の中で私たちが生きている場所です
The big old white rat Hua did this cell staining
大きな老白ネズミのフアがこの細胞染色を行いました
can see me this is under control
見えますか、これは制御されています
you see every blue
あなたにはすべての青が見えます
whole normal nerve cells
正常な神経細胞全体
But if we give
しかし、もし私たちが与えるなら、
This fast-growing drug
この即効性のある薬は
14 days to a month later
14日から1ヶ月後
You can see that these neurons are
これらのニューロンが
My cell shape is a little different
細胞の形が少し違う
This is the real experimental result
これが実際の実験結果です
not only people
人だけではない
rats
ネズミ
Then there will be problems with water
そうなると水の問題も出てきます
So why is it called Alzheimer's disease?
では、なぜアルツハイマー病と呼ばれるのでしょうか?
this sick person
この病気の人
a german doctor
ドイツ人の医師
His last name is Axel here again
ここでも彼の姓はアクセルです
so what's your last name
それであなたの姓は何ですか
The one with the crown at the end
最後に王冠が付いたもの
so hurry up young people
だから若者たちは急いでください
just try to invent something
何かを発明してみてください
that thing will always be
それはいつもそうなるだろう
Carry's name
キャリーの名前
Carry down
キャリーダウン
His name is Alois Arzheimer
彼の名前はアロイス・アルツハイマー
he's the guy on the cover
彼は表紙の男です
This is the man on the cover poster
表紙のポスターの男です
He's a neuropathologist in Germany
彼はドイツの神経病理学者です
with a psychiatrist
精神科医と一緒に
When he was in 1906
彼が1906年にいた頃
The first time I saw a patient
初めて患者さんを見たとき
Is there a fine AZ poster certificate
立派なAZポスター証明書はありますか
so the last name
それで姓は
In the end, he used his surname to represent the name.
結局、彼は名前を表すために自分の姓を使用しました。
Just say this scientist is a pity
この科学者は残念だとだけ言ってください
He only lived to be 51 years old
彼は51歳までしか生きなかった
since the 19th century
19世紀以来
Some of this medical development can't be compared
この医療開発の中には比較できないものもあります
He only lived to be 51 years old
彼は51歳までしか生きなかった
This is what he carried the patient he described
これが彼が説明した患者を運んだものです
I believe this is agree
これは同意だと思います
He or his family agrees
彼または彼の家族が同意する
because you are in the textbook
教科書に載ってるから
what on youtube
youtubeでは何ですか
Pay-per-tum will see this man
ペイ・パー・タムでこの男に会える
So of course there is no copyright issue
もちろん著作権の問題はありません
This person is a woman he diagnosed with Alzheimer's disease
これは彼がアルツハイマー病と診断した女性です
but he may be premature
しかし彼は早熟かもしれない
Because he can't get out when he dies
死んだら出られないから
but unfortunately
しかし残念ながら
Did the doctor die before him?
医者は彼より先に亡くなりましたか？
Because doctors aren't Alzheimer's
医者はアルツハイマー病ではないから
That is to say, this may be premature
つまり、時期尚早かもしれない
this age
この年齢
Assuming that in general
一般的にそう仮定すると
Usually in the 70s
だいたい70年代くらい
why the later time
なぜ遅い時間に
Here are a few images for you to see
ここにいくつかの画像がありますのでご覧ください
A normal brain and an Alzheimer's brain
正常な脳とアルツハイマー病の脳
what is the difference
違いはなんですか
We can see that this is a normal human brain
これが正常な人間の脳であることがわかります
wrinkled a lot
たくさんしわが寄った
The Alzheimer's brain
アルツハイマー病の脳
You can see not only the entire tail of the brain
脳尾部全体だけでなく、
shrink smaller
小さく縮む
His wrinkled ruler lessened
彼のしわのある定規は減りました
Then his ditch became big
それから彼の溝は大きくなりました
The whole becomes smaller
全体が小さくなってしまう
Then make this face straight
じゃあこの顔を真顔にして
This is a normal human brain
これは正常な人間の脳です
you just see this yellow place
この黄色い場所が見えるだけです
That is, he is using energy
つまり、エネルギーを使っているということです
GoCos
ゴーコス
He is the one that can reflect the activity of cells
細胞の活動を反映できるのは彼だ
So the more yellow
だから黄色が多ければ多いほど
This is when the nerve cells are more active
神経細胞が活発になる時期です
But you look at a patient with Asperger's disease
でもアスペルガー病の患者を見ると
Not only did his brain become smaller
脳が小さくなっただけではない
He has yellow, red
彼は黄色と赤を持っています
There are fewer orange places
オレンジ色の場所が少なくなりました
So the amount of activity in his entire brain
つまり、彼の脳全体の活動量は
activity is very low
活性が非常に低い
Of course you'd say it's obvious
もちろんそれは明らかだと言うだろう
right? it's obvious
そうでしょう？それは明らかです
But it's all about guiding people with Asthympiasis
しかし、それはすべて、無心症患者を指導することです。
It will be so obvious at a very late stage
それはかなり後の段階で明らかになるだろう
Here is another picture
こちらが別の写真です
You can see here is the brain of a normal person
ここに普通の人の脳があることがわかります
This is an advance
これは前進です
already serious
すでに深刻な
Asperger's disease patients
アスペルガー障害患者
The whole atrophy
全体の萎縮
And the brain gets bigger
そして脳も大きくなる
I'll get to that later
それについては後で説明します
This is also a pointing photo
こちらも指さし写真です
Yellow-orange areas are active
黄オレンジ色の領域がアクティブです
so normal people like this
普通の人はこういうのが好きなので
But the words of an asperger's disease patient
でもアスペルガー障害患者の言葉
The orange-yellow area is noticeably smaller overall
オレンジがかった黄色の領域が全体的に著しく小さくなっている
So the whole amount of activity in his brain
つまり、彼の脳内の活動の総量は
is getting lower
低くなっている
Here is another picture
こちらが別の写真です
Tell you about the shrinking of your brain
脳の萎縮について教えてください
this is the patient
これが患者です
this is normal
これは正常です
so the whole thing gets smaller
それで全体が小さくなる
then throw it down
それからそれを投げます
mad dog grows bigger
狂犬は大きくなる
then this is even scarier
それならこれはさらに怖いです
this is our ventricle
これは私たちの心室です
We have two lateral ventricles
私たちには側脳室が 2 つあります
There's also a third ventricle here
ここには第三脳室もあります
it is empty
それは空です
it has no nerve cells
神経細胞がない
Cerebral spine will be here at will
脳脊椎は自由にここに来ます
it goes from here to our spine
ここから私たちの背骨まで続いています
So the doctor sometimes goes to the hospital to check
それで医者は時々病院に行って検査します
need brain pumping random
脳をランダムにポンピングする必要がある
It doesn't follow the brain here
ここでは脳には従わない
it will jerk down the spine
背筋がゾクゾクするだろう
But it's all tied together
でもそれはすべてつながっている
down the spine
背骨の下に
but look
でも、見てください
The words of this sea membrane disease patient
海膜疾患患者の言葉
its brain is so big
その脳はとても大きいです
it has no cells
細胞がありません
it's all empty
全部空だ
This is the third ventricle
これが第三心室です
This is really a serious trans-morbidity
これは本当に深刻なトランス疾患です
this is brain rot
これは脳の腐敗だ
This is another image
これは別の画像です
can see
見える
You can see the spine with enlarged ventricles
心室が拡大した脊椎が見えます
compared to normal
通常と比較して
is very serious
とても深刻です
as you say
あなたが言うように
Could this be used as an early
これは早期として使用できるでしょうか
diagnostic goals
診断目標
Of course I may have to ask the doctor for the answer
もちろん医師に答えを求めなければならないかもしれません
But I think in the early days
でも初期の頃はこう思ってた
is not easy to see
見るのは簡単ではありません
if not
そうでない場合
not even
均等ではない
National students are often
国立の学生はよく、
It's the late stage of Big Red
ビッグレッドの後期です
Only the doctor can see
医師だけが見ることができる
That was the early days abroad
それは海外の初期の頃でした
Believe I made this
私がこれを作ったと信じてください
Anyway, it should be National Taiwan University
どうせなら国立台湾大学でしょう
I think it was put up by National Taiwan University Hospital.
国立台湾大学病院が貼ったものだと思います。
A shrinking brain on the web
ウェブ上で縮小する脳
Still a patient of Haiwen
まだハイウェンの患者だ
with a normal human brain continues to grow
正常な人間の脳では成長し続ける
this is simpler
これはもっと簡単です
This CT is OK
このCTは大丈夫です
The brain keeps growing
脳は成長し続ける
There is no need to do any complicated way
複雑な方法を行う必要はありません
That's the one
それだ
that is
あれは
Licensed shape
ライセンス形状
Or the PAD may not need that
あるいは、PAD にはそれが必要ない可能性があります
It can be seen from continuous achievement
継続的な実績からも分かる
but of course it
でももちろんそれは
This is also relatively late
こちらも比較的遅いですが
you can see
見ることができます
normal human brain is so small
普通の人間の脳はとても小さい
it's so big here
ここはとても大きいです
normal people like this
普通の人はこういうの
Its brain is so big
とても大きな脳を持っている
simply speaking
簡単に言えば
clinical diagnosis
臨床診断
broken from computer
コンピューターから壊れた
The following phenomena can be seen
以下のような現象が見られます
one is positive
1人はポジティブです
Then the hook widens
するとフックが広がります
so neurons
それでニューロン
atrophy
萎縮
Brain atrophy
脳萎縮
then pinch first
次に最初にピンチします
this place
この場所
side view
側面図
we just
私たちはただ
not in the head
頭の中にない
Orthocephalic
直頭型
not behind
後ろではない
Because these places on the side
こういった場所が横にあるので、
is what we say
それは私たちが言うことです
pay back
返済する
performance lock
性能合鎖
loaded some regions
いくつかの領域をロードする
then this will not help
それならこれは役に立ちません
no
いいえ
Our Cosmic Caretaker Gives Our Human Nervous System
私たちの宇宙の管理人は私たちの人間の神経系に与えます
great potential and plasticity
大きな可能性と可塑性
great potential
大きな可能性
but we regret that
しかし、私たちはそれを後悔しています
we humans
私たち人間
We have 80 billion brain nervous systems
私たちの脳神経系は 800 億個あります
i just said
私はちょうど言いました
But we may not even use a tenth of it in our lifetime
しかし、私たちは一生のうちにその10分の1さえも使わないかもしれません
It's a pity
それは残念だ
Because why especially after a professionalized society
なぜなら、なぜ特に専門化社会以降では
We're all trying to do the same thing
私たちは皆同じことをしようとしています
readers every day
毎日の読者
we are reading
我々が読んでいます
Athletic people are desperately exercising
体育会系の人は必死に運動している
we have a group
私たちにはグループがあります
There are many groups of cells
細胞のグループ
It's what we don't usually use
それは私たちが普段使わないものです
then let's make the most of our
それなら私たちの能力を最大限に活用しましょう
or activate our nervous systems that we don't normally use
または、普段使用していない神経系を活性化します。
is a very important thing
とても重要なことです
ideal
最理想的
should be ideal
理想的なはずです
I mean
つまり
you read
あなたが読む
then go for a swim
それから泳ぎに行きます
listening to music
音楽を聴く
drawing a picture
絵を描く
It means that you accept it many times
何度でも受け入れるということです
Let all the nervous systems in your brain be activated
脳内のすべての神経系を活性化させましょう
His mutual connection will increase
彼の相互のつながりは増加します
The best and the least derogatory
最高かつ軽蔑的ではない
But we know it's useless
でも私たちはそれが無駄だと分かっている
Because I want to be in this professional society
このプロフェッショナルな社会にいたいから
you have to work and go to work
働くためには働かなければなりません
You are civilian consciousness
あなたは民間人の意識です
may include the fact that we use only
のみを使用するという事実が含まれる場合があります
those thinking minds
それらの考える心
nowhere else
他にはどこにもない
But what I'm going to say now is to say
でも、今から言いたいのは、
Suppose we take individual
個人を取るとします
into a rich and diverse environment
豊かで多様な環境へ
English is the Environmental environment
英語は環境Environment
English is very full very full
英語はとても充実しています とても充実しています
just turn it into a diverse and rich environment
多様性のある豊かな環境に変えるだけです
It is of great help to our nerve cells
それは私たちの神経細胞にとって非常に役立ちます
look
見て
This is what I did first
これが私が最初にやったことです
then continue to pretend
それからふりを続けます
Is it here to buy a birdcage
鳥かごを買いに来ましたか
you haven't
あなたはしていない
and then we'll put some fun stuff in the way
それから、楽しいものをいくつか入れてみましょう
Then
それから
This runner you know rats really like to run this
このランナーはネズミが本当にこれを走るのが好きだということを知っています
Then we specially go to release
それから特別にリリースに行きます
those tree stands
それらの木が立っています
No, just cut some tree stands and put them over there
いいえ、木の幹を切ってそこに置くだけです
You know mice like to drill pipes, drill holes
ネズミはパイプや穴を開けるのが好きなのはご存知でしょう
so you see they're all happy inside
だから彼らは内心幸せなのがわかるだろう
And then this one is just running down
そして、これはちょうど流れ落ちています
We usually do lab rats and they're boring
私たちはいつも実験用のネズミをやっていますが、退屈です
They are kept in a cage every day
毎日檻の中で飼われています
two or three people standing there
そこに立っている2人か3人
two or three mice
2匹か3匹のネズミ
adapt to me the same thing for a lifetime
一生同じことを私に適応させてください
So their environment is very monotonous and boring
彼らの環境は非常に単調で退屈です
Really, they can't live with
本当に、彼らは一緒に生きていけない
you come across these mouse cakes in the park or in the gutter
公園や側溝でネズミのケーキを見つけます
they are so happy
彼らはとても幸せです
So we can't experiment with some mice
したがって、一部のマウスを使って実験することはできません
Otherwise those mice
そうでなければあのネズミ達
is far bigger than our caged rats
私たちの檻に入れられたネズミよりもはるかに大きいです
There are many people
たくさんの人がいます
they are all dull
彼らは皆鈍いです
then we put them every day
それから私たちは毎日それらを置きます
every day
毎日
let them next time
次回は彼らにさせてください
from the cage they live in
彼らが暮らす檻の中から
get such an environment
そんな環境を手に入れる
let them run for ten minutes
10分間走らせてください
only ten minutes
たった10分
ten minutes in the morning
朝の10分
run this after running
実行後にこれを実行します
what is this
これは何ですか
I'll just take the delivery carton
配送用ダンボールだけ持って行きます
Take it to pick up a little black post
小さな黒いポストを拾いに行ってください
also dig some holes
穴も掘ってください
then play some
それから少し遊んでください
you see they play a lot
彼らはたくさん遊んでいるのがわかりますね
heart bricks come and go
ハートレンガが行ったり来たり
and put some in it
それからそれに何かを入れてください
you see there are
あるのがわかりますか
swing forward
前に振る
I found that mice like to eat
ネズミは食べるのが好きだということが分かりました
So when you and I worship mice
だからあなたと私がネズミを崇拝するとき
Definitely buy light fresh fish
淡白な鮮魚は必ず買う
Then the shortbread kind
続いてショートブレッド系
They're here to play very happy
彼らはとても幸せに遊ぶためにここにいます
Fifteen minutes a day they play
彼らは1日に15分間遊ぶ
play this, play him this
これをかけて、彼にこれをかけて
Then put the cabinet dragon here
それからキャビネットドラゴ​​ンをここに置きます
Let them do it again this afternoon
今日の午後にもう一度やらせてください
You are only ten days in total
あなたは合計10日だけです
then my young mouse
それから私の若いネズミ
and older mice
そして古いマウス
Because he has a mouse that is a year old
彼は1歳のネズミを飼っているので、
he is not too old
彼はあまり年をとっていない
The lifespan of a mouse is about one year and ten months
ネズミの寿命は約1年10ヶ月
So you are up to two years
だからあなたは2年までです
up to two years up to two years
最長2年 最長2年
so you talk about a one year old mouse
それであなたは1歳のネズミのことを話していますね
we say he's not too old
私たちは彼はそんなに年をとっていないと言います
but he is h
でも彼はhです
he is an old mouse
彼は年老いたネズミです
Like just now we probably
たった今のように、私たちはおそらく
I think forty or fifty years old
40歳か50歳くらいだと思う
then we let them
それから私たちは彼らにさせます
After running like this every day
毎日こうやって走ってたら
Let them go to study with crystals again
もう一度クリスタルと一緒に勉強させてください
I was doing this experiment
こんな実験をしていたのですが
trying to control them as a
それらをコントロールしようとしています
what i want to say is to say
私が言いたいことは言うことです
such an old mouse
あんな古いマウス
None of these trainings worked for him.
これらのトレーニングはどれも彼にとっては役に立ちませんでした。
too late with energy
エネルギー的には遅すぎる
But the result of this experiment
しかし、この実験の結果は、
we have published
私たちは出版しました
This is the escape from the water to the ass
これは水からお尻への脱出です
time required
所要時間
so shorter is better
だから短いほど良い
this is an old mouse
これは古いマウスです
I just sleep a lot
ただたくさん寝ているだけです
control group
対照群
This line is the control group
この行はコントロールグループです
Didn't give him to play those games
彼にそれらのゲームをプレイすることを与えなかった
That group of mice
あのネズミの群れ
It is to let him play every day for thirty years
30年間毎日遊ばせることです
Thirty years long, I want thirty years
30年は長い、30年は欲しい
When I look at this data
このデータを見てみると
i was startled
私はびっくりした
that's what you'll find
それがあなたが見つけることです
Even though the mouse is so old
マウスはかなり古いものですが、
but you give him these every day
でもあなたはこれを毎日彼に与えます
Diversified and rich visual environment
多様で豊かな視覚環境
he just learns faster
彼はただ学ぶのが早いだけです
And next door was testing his memory
そして隣では彼​​の記憶力をテストしていました
He also remembers better
彼はまたよく覚えています
what does the time tell us
時間は私たちに何を教えてくれますか
just older people
ただの高齢者
as long as you can learn
学べる限り
can also function
機能することもできます
can also express
表現することもできる
don't go into a nursing home
老人ホームに入らないでください
because that's a
それは
An environment that is neither rich nor diverse
豊かでも多様性でもない環境
really so
本当にそうです
contact with society
社会との接触
give yourself a little more stimulation
もう少し自分に刺激を与えてください
is very important
はとても重要です
not old and bad
古くも悪くもない
not
いいえ
It's a kind of neuroexitability
これは一種の神経興奮性です
then we later
それから私たちは後で
tell him these two punches
この2つのパンチを彼に伝えてください
then test him
それから彼をテストしてください
It's just that there's one in his head
ただ彼の頭の中にそれがあるだけだ
Genes Associated with Neuroplasticity
神経可塑性に関連する遺伝子
you can see
見ることができます
Mice in rich and diverse environments
豊かで多様な環境のマウス
He is more than twice as many as a phoenix mouse
彼はフェニックスネズミの2倍以上です
So we have countless
だから私たちは数え切れないほどの
Genes Associated with Neuroplasticity
神経可塑性に関連する遺伝子
We speak of plasticity as
私たちは可塑性について次のように話します
Inspired again
またまたインスピレーションを得た
is the nervous system
神経系です
especially the brain
特に脳
a permanent process of adaptation to an environment
環境に適応する永続的なプロセス
permanent
永続
So don't you think you're 80
だから、自分は80歳だと思っていませんか？
you don't have this plasticity
あなたにはその可塑性がありません
no you still have
いいえ、まだあります
So you're going to find yourself some
それで、あなたは自分自身をいくつか見つけるでしょう
things you don't usually see
普段は見られないもの
or multiple stimuli
または複数の刺激
Mouth your nerve cells
神経細胞を口に出す
Let your nerve cells and nerve cells
神経細胞を神経細胞に任せましょう
link increase
リンク増加
It's a permanent process of adaptation
それは永続的な適応プロセスです
nervous system
神経系
us
私たち
I just said that we have countless such
私はちょうどそのようなものが無数にあると言いました
plasticity genes
可塑性遺伝子
But we don't have us humans
でも私たちには人間がいない
In other words, some of us have infinite predecessors
言い換えれば、私たちの中には無限の前任者がいるということです
But most of us
しかし、私たちのほとんどは
None in our finite years
私たちの有限な年には何もない
Not getting the most out of our money
お金を最大限に活用できていない
it's a bit disappointing
少し残念です
like us
私たちのような
Let us humans evolve into
私たち人間は次のように進化しましょう
a thought of the highest
最高の考え
So you have to have confidence in yourself
だから自分に自信を持たないといけない
Then go develop your own money man
それなら自分のお金持ちを育てましょう
go give yourself more
もっと自分を与えに行ってください
make yourself present one more day
もう一度自分自身を存在させてください
you don't usually think about it
あなたは普段それについて考えないでしょう
or have not been exposed to some stimuli
または何らかの刺激にさらされていない
So older adults actually use the Internet more
つまり、高齢者は実際にインターネットをより多く使用しているということです
In fact, it's good to go online.
実際、オンラインにするのは良いことです。
because don't be afraid to learn
学ぶことを恐れないでください
you continue to use him
あなたは彼を使い続けます
Now the situation is the best idea
今の状況が最善の考えだ
Young people shouldn't help you write more on the Internet
若者はインターネット上での書き込みを手助けすべきではありません
Desperately on the Internet
インターネット上で必死に
but older people
でも年上の人たち
In fact, you should get in touch with them more.
実際、もっと彼らと連絡を取るべきです。
you didn't think about it
あなたはそれについて考えていませんでした
you are educated
あなたは教育を受けています
no it doesn't matter
いいえ、関係ありません
That is to say, how much you learn counts
つまり、どれだけ学んだかが重要です
I'm talking about your neural network.
私はニューラルネットワークについて話しているのです。
right where you are
あなたがいる場所で
that can
ができる
The more you use your brain
脳を使えば使うほど
I got this from the internet
これはインターネットから入手しました
The more efficient
より効率的
you will become more efficient
あなたはより効率的になるでしょう
Same
同じ
Do you think of the exhaustion just now
今の疲れを思い出しますか
Get out of that hut
あの小屋から出て行け
where the fingers stand
指が立つ場所
you use it all the time
あなたはいつもそれを使っています
Your brain is less likely to shrink
脳が萎縮する可能性が低くなります
the more chance you have of dementia
認知症の可能性が高くなる
In fact, the further back you win
実際、後退すればするほど勝ちます
not saying how
どのようにしてかは言わない
In fact, modern medicine can
実際、現代医学では、
I just said he can't help
彼は助けられないって言っただけだよ
There's nothing doctors can do to make him die
彼を死なせるために医者にできることは何もない
regeneration back
再生バック
the only thing you can do is
あなたにできる唯一のことは
Delay the onset of dementia
認知症の発症を遅らせる
one is backward
1つは後ろ向きです
You could have
あなたはそうすることができます
Only at the age of 75, 70, and 80
75歳、70歳、80歳の時のみ
He extended to 88 years old
88歳まで延長されました
Maybe you can solve the problem
もしかしたら問題を解決できるかも知れません
This person is very rare
この人はとても珍しい人です
Or let him get serious, slow down
それとも彼に真剣になってもらい、ゆっくりさせてください
Medicine is doing things like this now
医学は今こんなことをやっている
after we understand
私たちが理解した後
we help ourselves
私たちは自分自身を助けます
delay the process
プロセスを遅らせる
ok , then i will stop here today
わかりました、それでは今日はここで終わります
I think that's what I'm going to write
それが私が書こうと思っていることです
Of course, the Institute of Biomedicine, Academia Sinica
もちろん、中央研究院生物医学研究所
It's my company's case
うちの会社の場合です
30 years
30年
then what i want to say is
私が言いたいのは
really yourself later
本当に後は自分自身
I think the best research unit in the world
世界で最高の研究ユニットだと思う
not only give us enough duel
十分な決闘を与えるだけでなく
academic freedom and a lesson
学問の自由と教訓
I can have a place to manage
管理する場所ができる
In addition, I think the work unit is
また、作業単位は
what is given to us is
私たちに与えられているものは
The development of a scientist
科学者の成長
And the qualities that scientists should have
そして科学者が持つべき資質
I think my work unit
私の職場の単位だと思います
have made great contributions
多大な貢献をしてきた
i feel i'm lucky
私は幸運だと感じています
can work in this place for so long
この場所で長く働ける
then this is
それならこれは
Units will also look to support
ユニットもサポートを検討します
If everyone walks in through the gate of Academia Sinica
みんなが中央研究院の門をくぐったら
Go 50 meters to the right
右に50メートル進みます
The first building is
最初の建物は、
This is the second picture
これは2番目の写真です
And of course I'm grateful
そしてもちろん感謝しています
Now this year it will be renamed
今年から名前が変わります
Resurrection of science and technology
科学技術の復活
It used to be called the Biological Map of the National Science Council
以前は米国科学会議の生物地図と呼ばれていました
their thirty years of research funding
彼らの30年間にわたる研究資金提供
support us to be able to
私たちができるようサポートしてください
do this series of research
この一連の研究を行う
This is the current staff in my lab
これが私の研究室の現在のスタッフです
certainly
そうです
Of course, these thirty years are not limited to these students
もちろん、この30年はこの生徒たちだけのものではありません。
Just now there is something about animals
今、動物に関する話題があります
Substantive research is
実質的な研究というのは、
Congratulations
おめでとう
The older one is my long-term full-time assistant
年上の人は私の長期にわたるフルタイムのアシスタントです
Mr. Ma is a postdoctoral fellow with me
馬さんは私と同じ博士研究員です
Ph.D. has a Ph.D.
Ph.D.は博士号を持っています。
Besides I'm really
それに、私は本当に
say this very sincerely and sincerely
これを非常に誠実に、そして誠実に言います
Thanks
ありがとう
These teachers I just talked about
先ほど話した先生たち
Because they share more than 90% of the sameness with us in the mysterious system
不思議なシステムの中で、私たちと90％以上の同一性を共有しているからです。
That's why we experiment with them
だからこそ私たちは彼らを実験してみるのです
so i feel thankful
だから私は感謝しています
it was they who sacrificed their
自分たちを犠牲にしたのは彼らだった
Research on the Perfection of Human Body
人体の完璧さの研究
Let us live longer and healthier
もっと健康に長生きしましょう
so in my eyes they are very cute animals
だから私の目にはとてもかわいい動物に見えます
Our unit every year in the Central Plains
私たちの部隊は毎年セントラルプレーンズで活動しています
during festivals
お祭り中
very pious
とても敬虔な
for all experimental animals
すべての実験動物に
a counting ceremony
数を数える儀式
I think even a scientist should
科学者でもそうすべきだと思う
to express
表現するために
Finally, thank you all for listening to us.
最後に、ご静聴いただきました皆様、ありがとうございました。
Thanks
ありがとう
I think everyone is learning a new knowledge today
今日は誰もが新しい知識を学んでいると思います
So your brain connections must have increased a lot today
今日はあなたの脳のつながりがかなり増えたはずです
Now we have about 25 minutes
今、約 25 分あります
Let me answer some questions for you
いくつかの質問に答えさせてください
Raise your hand if you have a question
質問がある場合は手を挙げてください
Then introduce yourself first what's your name
それではまず自己紹介をしてください あなたの名前は何ですか
With what school or institution
どのような学校または機関と
then ask the question peace of mind
それから安心して質問してください
Then you can come tomorrow
じゃあ明日来てもいいよ
here's a microphone
ここにマイクがあります
Press the green button if you want to speak
発言したい場合は緑色のボタンを押してください
Thank you teacher Max Lin Jianzhi for the wonderful lecture
Max Lin Jianzhi先生、素晴らしい講義をありがとうございました
He is a graduate of our Taipei College
彼は台北大学の卒業生です
but i was in taiwan university
でも私は台湾の大学にいた
Additional year of law degree
追加の法学位取得年数
because no matter what
なぜなら、何があっても
thank you very much for your presentation
プレゼンテーションをしていただきありがとうございました
Then what I want to ask is
そこで聞きたいのは、
In fact, it was mentioned at the beginning
実は冒頭でも触れましたが、
Forgetting makes our brain cells work less
忘れると脳細胞の働きが低下します
But then I kept encouraging
でもその後も励まし続けた
we need to learn more
私たちはもっと学ぶ必要があります
many memories
たくさんの思い出
Then let the one of your own brain
それから自分の脳を一つにしましょう
This strength will be better
この強さはさらに良くなります
all over me
私のいたるところに
When I take it, it seems like a contradiction.
受け取ってみると矛盾しているように思えます。
We hope to know which will forget
誰が忘れるのか知りたい
take it easy on the brain cells
脳細胞を休ませてください
but you keep remembering
でもあなたは思い出し続ける
Does studying put too much pressure on others?
勉強は他の人に過度のプレッシャーを与えますか？
But this problem is in the back
しかし、この問題は裏にあります
You said how round the environment you want
あなたはどのくらいの環境が望ましいと言いましたか
That is to say, expanding the useless part
つまり、無駄な部分を拡張するということです。
Then there is another situation
それから別の状況があります
Does that mean I've been working on the same thing all the time?
ということは、ずっと同じことに取り組んでいるということでしょうか？
good for my head
頭に良い
If this is the case
このような場合は
I want to specifically clear the loss of teachers
教師の喪失を具体的に解消したい
How can we make sure in life
人生においてどうやって確かめることができるでしょうか
My life is a round of kung fu
私の人生はカンフーのラウンドです
How do I know if I'm too expert
自分が専門家すぎるかどうかをどうやって知ることができますか
the kind that wants to crush him
彼を潰したいタイプ
Then the problem with the lucky bag is that you just said
そうすると、福袋の問題は、今おっしゃったことなんです。
If you talk so much, you will be in a hurry
そんなに話したら急いでしまうよ
No
いいえ
I just
私はちょうど
you actually
あなたは実際に
i just have one question
1つだけ質問があります
That is to say, we live our daily life like this
つまり、私たちはこうして日常生活を送っているのです。
how do i make sure of my life
自分の命をどうやって確かめればいいのか
Not too specialized in trying to suppress him
彼を抑え込むことにあまり特化していない
but I live in a multi-circular environment
でも私は複数の循環環境に住んでいます
is how i know my life
それが私が自分の人生を知る方法です
I know what you mean
あなたが言っていることがわかります
But I think it's better
でもその方が良いと思う
You just said the voice hands are awesome
声の手が素晴らしいってさっき言ったよね
super exciting
超エキサイティング
this is how i feel
これが私の感じ方です
mom didn't say
お母さんは言わなかった
He allowed everyone to have an agency in the country
彼は誰もが国内に代理店を持つことを許可した
I think if it's convenient
都合がよければと思います
please tell me too
私にも教えてください
How can everyone be at home
どうしたらみんな家にいられるんだろう
if you come to work you will know
職場に来れば分かるよ
well if so
まあそうであれば
I forgot what you just said
あなたが今言ったことを忘れました
keep learning
学び続けます
Is it a bit contradictory
ちょっと矛盾してるかな
actually not
実際にはそうではありません
because we learned
私たちは学んだから
we just talked
私たちはちょうど話したばかりです
We are actually neurological
実は私たちは神経質なのです
Instead, full resurrection forms this circuit
代わりに、完全な復活がこの回路を形成します
After he reaches a certain level
彼が一定のレベルに達した後
He put it next to his brain for storage.
彼はそれを保管のために脳の隣に置きました。
At this time, the bloody nerve
このとき、血まみれの神経が
back to his original
元の彼に戻る
fix the normal state
正常な状態を修正する
ready for the next thing
次のことの準備ができています
so he's not constantly excited
だから彼はいつも興奮しているわけではない
And to the forgotten piece that says
そしてこう言う忘れ去られた部分に
He has already formed a memory
彼はすでに記憶を形成している
that membrane is there
その膜はそこにあります
but he stand by
でも彼はスタンバイしてる
He fell asleep
彼は寝た
so he is not tired
だから彼は疲れていない
you now take the gunpowder out
あなたは今火薬を取り出します
Just let him recharge from the edge
端から充電させてください
reply again
もう一度返信する
The only thing that makes nerve blood hair tired is
神経血毛を疲れさせるのはただ一つ。
this short period
この短い期間
keep making him gunpowder
彼に火薬を作り続ける
keep letting him
彼に許し続けてください
He just passed the recovery period correction period
彼は回復期修正期間を過ぎたばかりです
just let him work
ただ彼に働かせてください
just expired
ちょうど期限が切れたばかり
you just keep him working
あなたはただ彼を働かせ続けるだけです
Even the reply period hasn't been said yet
返信期限すらまだ言われてない
Come to the end
終わったらさあ
How long does it take to shake your face
顔を振るのにどれくらい時間がかかりますか
you this long time
こんなに長い間あなたは
I will now give an example
今から例を挙げます
I'm going to study again
また勉強してみます
Thirty-eight degrees mouth thirty-eight degrees
三十八度口三十八度
high school degree here
高校卒業資格はこちら
I think both
両方とも思います
I've been my high school better than I've been since graduating girls
私は高校を卒業して以来、より良い高校生活を送っています
I don't do my topic anymore
もう自分のトピックはやらない
I have no idea
何も思いつきません
The reason why this topic is not used is very simple
このトピックが使用されない理由は非常に単純です
that I don't need anymore in my life
私の人生にはもう必要ないもの
know thirty eight degrees
三十八度を知っている
what's the point, right?
どういうことですか？
But I used to be very good at this topic
でも昔はこの話題が得意だった
But what I said was
しかし私が言ったことは
you forgot to say
あなたは言うのを忘れました
you talk to me again now
あなたは今また私に話しかけます
What to do at thirty-eight degrees
38度で何をするか
i may recall some things
いくつかのことを思い出すかもしれない
It's different from what I've never learned
習ったことのないものとは違う
this is
これは
It's not that I forgot, I can call it out
忘れたわけじゃないよ、電話すればいいよ
but things you totally forgot
でもあなたがすっかり忘れていたこと
completely forgotten
完全に忘れ去られた
that's something to relearn
それは学び直すことだ
renurning
戻ってくる
So I just talked about neurovascular
神経血管についてお話しました
Tired or not but it is like this
疲れてるかどうかだけどこんな感じ
what did you just do
あなたは今何をしましたか
you say
あなたは言う
how do i know
どうやって知ることができますか
i am forgetful
私は忘れっぽいです
Do you want him or multiple
彼が欲しいですか、それとも複数が欲しいですか
this
これ
You feel
あなたが感じる
Rich and diverse may be monotonous to me
豊かで多様性は私にとって単調かもしれない
i feel monotonous
単調な気がする
Feel rich at first
最初はとても裕福に感じました
but one we'll talk about
でも、それについてはこれから話します
You are the basis of the neuroblast to speak
あなたは話すための神経芽細胞の基礎です
you just don't do one thing
あなたはただ一つのことをしていないだけです
Forever only use that group of neurotic monsters
永遠に神経質なモンスターだけを使ってください
I thought maybe you should
たぶんそうすべきだと思いました
You just finished speaking the language area here
ここで言語領域を話し終えたところです
The visual zone is here
ビジュアルゾーンはここです
art painting is here
アートペインティングはここにあります
you are using your brain
あなたは頭を使っています
you should think
考えるべきです
just trying to get your stimulation
ただあなたの刺激を得ようとしてるだけ
Do you want to go from the middle every day
毎日途中から行きますか？
exposure to stimuli
刺激への曝露
diversify a little
少し多様化する
you go for a run and use your brain
走りに行って頭を使います
also sports
スポーツも
go swimming with you
あなたと一緒に泳ぎに行きます
The neuroblasts used may be different
使用される神経芽細胞は異なる場合があります
Because swimming requires a lot of balance
水泳はバランス感覚がとても必要なので、
running is ok
走っても大丈夫です
So this is a little bit different
だからこれはちょっと違うんです
will be different
違うだろう
It's just another way of riding your bike
それは自転車に乗るもう一つの方法です
another balance
別のバランス
One is the balance of the water on the ground
一つは、地上の水のバランスです。
So the whole point of what I'm going to say is that
つまり、私がこれから言おうとしていることの要点は、
this is what you imagined
これはあなたが想像したものです
that is to say you
つまりあなたは
when you go to listen to music today
今日音楽を聴きに行くとき
Do the math with what you're thinking about this angle and how many degrees
この角度について考えていることと度数を計算してください。
It's actually two very different things.
実際、それは 2 つのまったく異なるものです。
two bodies
二つの体
So let's say it like this
だからこう言ってみましょう
Allow yourself to be exposed to different aspects of design
デザインのさまざまな側面に触れてみましょう
I don't know if it's rich for you personally but for you
それがあなた個人にとって豊かかどうかはわかりませんが、あなたにとっては
I just want your nerve cells to be rich and right
私はただあなたの神経細胞が豊かで正しくありたいだけなのです
Different designs because he accepts
彼が受け入れるので異なるデザイン
Just thinking about his health
彼の健康のことだけを考えて
Then you might feel like going for a run
そうすると、走りに行きたくなるかもしれません
maybe not that fun
たぶんそんなに面白くない
but if it's good for him
でもそれが彼にとって良いことなら
maybe you just resign yourself to being an ex-masculinity
たぶんあなたは元男らしさであることを諦めているだけかもしれません
you go
あなたが行く
You said that Wei Lu is so good in the business
ウェイ・ルーはビジネスでとても上手だと言いましたね
because of our
私たちのせいで
I think we are in my workplace
私の職場にいると思います
Researchers are very specialized
研究者は非常に専門的です
We often hear different people report
さまざまな人々の報告をよく聞きます
different things
異なるもの
According to foreign scholars
外国の学者によると
let's not go out
外出しないようにしましょう
connect to the Internet
インターネットに接続する
until the world in every field
あらゆる分野で世界へ
what is the most advanced research
最も先進的な研究は何ですか
Then there are no visiting scholars from abroad
そうすると海外からの客員学者がいない
We are often judged
私たちはしばしば裁かれます
Judging is stressful
判断するのがストレスになる
but i just said
でも私は今言いました
It is also the driving force for our progress
それは私たちの進歩の原動力でもあります
So I think we are in line with the international academic community
したがって、私たちは国際的な学術コミュニティと一致していると思います
is very close
とても近いです
Although Fysical was the first member of the committee
フィジカルは委員会の最初のメンバーでしたが、
But I think in the field of science
しかし科学の分野ではこう思います
We are with the advanced science in the world
私たちは世界の先端科学とともにあります
The direction of research is very close to the footsteps
研究の方向性は足跡に非常に近い
So I think it really provides me with a
だから、それは本当に私に与えてくれると思います
diverse and rich environment
多様で豊かな環境
ok thank you sir
わかりました、ありがとうございます
Then these two
それからこの二人
OK, bye
はい、さようなら
Hello, reviewer, I am a student of Beiyi University
こんにちは、査読者、私は北宜大学の学生です
In the Academia Sinica dedicated to announce the doctoral class
中央研究院では博士課程の発表を専門に行っている
Then my question is
それから私の質問は
Because the first two mentioned
最初の 2 つが挙げたので、
Too much water four fifths
水が多すぎる 5 分の 4
Just Talamina E2 and D3C
タラミナ E2 と D3C だけ
But I was talking about it a few days ago
でも数日前にその話をしたんです
He seems to have a relationship with SHMDZ
SHMDZと関係があるようだ
So the teacher doesn't know how to say this
だから先生はこれをどう言えばいいのかわからない
that another topic
それは別の話題
The other is the incidental topic
もう一つは付随的な話題です
Another question is
もう一つの質問は、
It's the Pretty Shoe thing I just talked about
それは先ほど話した「プリティ・シュー」のことです
But it seems that there is no special mention
でも特筆することはないようです
Then I think it actually echoes the previous
それから、それは実際に前のことをエコーし​​ていると思います
looks right
正しく見えます
Time and dimension要
時間と次元要
let it change
変えてみましょう
don't this happen to me
こんなことが私に起こらないでください
exercise more
多運動
sleep well
よく眠る
Then the answer to the question just now is
そうすると、今の質問に対する答えは、
How to know your own sports
自分のスポーツを知る方法
or activity or which sport
またはアクティビティまたはスポーツ
these diverse environments
こういった多様な環境を
good enough
十分です
it's actually really easy
実はとても簡単です
You will know if you are happy or not
自分が幸せかどうかはわかるだろう
I seem to be happy before going to bed
寝る前に幸せそうです
very satisfied
非常に満足
Then fill up and go to sleep
あとはお腹を満たして寝ましょう
did everything
すべてをやった
sportsman with our mountain climber
スポーツマンと登山家
this usually rides to the
これは通常、
the tree also becomes
木もなる
unhappy
不幸な
that's enough
もういい
ask the teacher to answer
先生に答えてもらう
answer your first question
最初の質問に答えてください
Because I'm not doing diabetes research
私は糖尿病の研究をしているわけではないので、
i don't know
わからない
but
しかし
The general direction is probably due to diabetes
一般的な方向性はおそらく糖尿病によるものです
it has a problem with its metabolism
それは代謝に問題がある
Many morning metabolism is problematic
朝の代謝に問題がある人が多い
so i don't know if
だからどうか分からない
because i'm not diabetic
私は糖尿病ではないので
So there are some things that cannot be metabolized
代謝できないものもあるので、
Accumulated in the blood brain of the gods
神々の血脳に蓄積される
damage some nerve cells
一部の神経細胞を損傷する
or an inflammatory response
または炎症反応
This is my general direction, probably like this
これが私の大まかな方向性ですが、おそらくこんな感じです
really really really how
本当に本当に本当にどうやって
I am not very sure
よくわかりません
But research on candy bars
しかし、キャンディーバーの研究
the depression i just talked about
先ほど話したうつ病
that is
あれは
birthday disease it's a bit annoying
誕生日病、ちょっと面倒だ
Which means it's really just a matter of memory.
つまり、それは単なる記憶の問題です。
But you know when a person's social function
でも、人間の社会的役割がいつ果たされるかはわかります。
can't remember when
いつだったか思い出せない
When many things are often easily forgotten
多くのことが忘れられやすいとき
it's basically its ability to socialize gets longer
それは基本的に社交性が長くなるということです
because it won't
そうならないから
because what it says
なぜならそれが言うことは
It can't remember what others say
他人が言ったことを覚えていない
So gradually its degree of socialization will become longer and longer
徐々に社会化の度合いが長くなっていきます
It is often reported in the "Bank" that
「銀行」ではよくこう報告されています。
Worldly affairs patients later
後は世事患者
He'll be engaged in the production of half-year-old melancholy
『半年のメランコリア』の制作に携わる予定
because he was isolated
彼は孤立していたから
so
それで
So when you can interact with society
だから、社会と交流できるようになると、
just try to interact
ただ対話してみてください
Because in the end, there are many incidents
結局は事件が多いから
other problems arise
他の問題が発生する
This matter is said to be a report of the clinical account
この件は臨床会計の報告書だそうです
It's the same thing as hesitation
躊躇するのと同じことだよ
In fact, there is such a problem that it is not the party involved.
実は当事者ではないというような問題があるんです。
The person involved will be a little frustrated at first
関係者は最初は少しイライラするでしょう
but it develops to later
しかしそれは後に発展します
It actually has nothing too wrong
実際にはそれほど間違ったことはありません
because it's a lot of a net
ネットが多いから
In fact, the people around it will work harder
実際、周りの人たちはもっと頑張るでしょう
People around will also be more likely to have this kind of
周囲の人もこのような症状に陥る可能性が高くなります。
Situation of hesitation
迷っている状況
so i don't know you two
だから私はあなたたち二人を知りません
Sometimes, of course, these problems are
もちろん、これらの問題が発生する場合もあります。
Medically advanced humans live so long
医学的に進歩した人類は長生きする
It's been so long since this problem
この問題からかなり時間が経ちました
A few decades ago, human lifespan was not so long
数十年前、人間の寿命はそれほど長くはありませんでした
The problem doesn't appear to be that serious.
問題はそれほど深刻ではないようです。
But that said, it seems that the lifespan of human beings will continue to increase.
しかし、そうは言っても人間の寿命はさらに伸びるようです。
Because with the development of medicine
医学の発達により
So except when you are healthy
だから健康なとき以外は
Create an environment for yourself
自分のための環境を作る
It is not easy or something goes wrong in the wrong age
簡単ではない、あるいは間違った年齢で何かがうまくいかない
you really feel symptoms
あなたは本当に症状を感じていますか
Or people around you will have symptoms
もしくは周りの人に症状が出てしまう
go to the doctor early
早めに医者に行きましょう
Just always be professional
常にプロフェッショナルであり続けてください
What tests does the doctor think can be done
医師はどのような検査が可能だと考えていますか
may be helpful
役に立つかもしれない
This means that in terms of diagnosis
つまり、診断という観点から見ると、
it's still important
それはまだ重要です
Then if you look at it from another angle
じゃあ別の角度から見てみると
i would like to say
言いたいです
This is a bit about the philosophy of human truth
これは人間の真実の哲学に関するものです
that is
あれは
In fact, from another angle, we can say that
実は、別の角度から言えば、
It's just the appearance of this problem.
それはこの問題の表面にすぎません。
you can also think like this
このように考えることもできます
That is to say, a person must be qualified to have this disease
つまり、その人はこの病気になる資格がなければなりません
He has actually lived to a considerable age
彼は実際かなりの年齢まで生きた
what ? because you don ' t see thirty or forty people
何ですか？ 30 人も 40 人もいないからです
so
それで
In fact, this person has
実はこの人は、
overcame many difficulties in life
人生の多くの困難を乗り越えた
also escaped many disasters
数々の災害も免れた
escaped many other illnesses
他の多くの病気から逃れた
That's what I mean by using a
それが私が意味するのは、
Yes, accept him with a more optimistic attitude
そう、もっと楽観的な態度で彼を受け入れましょう
that's what i think
それが私が思うことです
Just no matter who you were at the time
当時あなたが誰であったかは関係ありません
or people around
あるいは周りの人たち
because
なぜなら
look, a young man
見て、若い男
did nothing
何もしませんでした
just disappeared from the earth
地球から消え去ったばかり
just something like the interface
インターフェースのようなもの
So it's just a mental thing
だからそれは単なる精神的なものです
But from a purely medical point of view
しかし、純粋に医学的な観点から見ると、
Of course we still want the photo to know
もちろん、それでも写真を知ってもらいたいです
Because not just yourself and the people around you
なぜなら、自分や周りの人だけではないからです。
It's not so hard
そんなに難しくないよ
Resources to society also end
社会への資源もなくなる
Otherwise Medical Resources
それ以外の場合は医療リソース
Make sure these are real
これらが本物であることを確認してください
is also very disadvantaged
も非常に不利な立場にある
It's also very bad for money.
金銭的にも非常に悪いです。
So I'm fine up front
だから私は前から大丈夫です
Thank you, Professor Yi
李先生、ありがとうございました
I am Xincheng
私は新城です
I am 38 years old
私は38歳です
young old man
若い老人
Friends call me Tony
友達は私をトニーと呼んでいます
that me
それはわたしです
I get up every morning now
今では毎朝起きます
I'll just keep two of those laptops
ラップトップは 2 台だけ残しておきます
That BBC News
あのBBCニュース
But I'm too old to care
でも私は年をとりすぎて気にすることはできない
What national event water becomes president
水が大統領になる国家イベントとは
I don't care
私は気にしない
But I watch that Felix column every day
でも私はフェリックスのコラムを毎日見ています
all over the world now
今では世界中で
Whether it is Chinese or foreign
中国人でも外国人でも
Taiwanese
台湾人
Love the population in Sea Membrane
Sea Membrane の人口が大好き
proportional increase
比例増加
But there's a big reason in it
でもそれには大きな理由があるんです
is interpersonal
対人関係です
It is easy for us to understand
それは私たちを理解しやすくします
interpersonal skills
対人能力
In addition it has two main comparisons that say
さらに、次の 2 つの主要な比較があります。
our birth environment
私たちの生まれた環境
birth pressure
出生圧
one more thing
もう一つ
it says who we are now
それは私たちが今誰であるかを示しています
That shoots too much protein
それはタンパク質を過剰に発射します
so itchy
とてもかゆい
is there any rival
ライバルはいますか
So give us some guidance
それで、私たちにいくつかの指導をしてください
Disclosure
開示一下
because i'm not living
私は生きていないから
nutritionist
栄養士
I'm not a doctor either
私も医者ではありません
so i don't know
だから分からない
This is because certain ingredients
これは、特定の成分があるためです
how about extra many or extra small
特多か極小はどうですか？
but i just said
でも私は今言いました
our nerve cells
私たちの神経細胞
or starch cells
またはデンプン細胞
Its structure is very simple
その構造は非常にシンプルです
it doesn't need much from us
私たちからはあまり必要ありません
It only requires some basic
必要なのは基本的なことだけです
basic amount of protein
基本的なたんぱく質の量
fat minerals
脂肪ミネラル
vitamins etc.
ビタミンなど
starch etc.
でんぷんなど
good carbohydrate
良い炭水化物
it will be efficient to do
非常に効率的に行うことができます
neurons in our brain
私たちの脳のニューロン
all protein needed
必要なすべてのタンパク質
So I think a lot of things are
だから、多くのことはそうだと思う
Appropriate amount is good
適量が良い
In our age, there are very few people who enter
私たちの時代では入る人は非常に少ないです
The old tail dies due to lack of nutrition
古い尾は栄養不足で死んでしまう
not such a problem
そんな問題ではない
So of course there is an argument that too much protein
もちろん、タンパク質が多すぎるという議論はありますが、
Is it bad or load
悪いのか負荷なのか
then i just recall
それから私はただ思い出します
Early years in our previous generation with older
私たちの前の世代の初期の頃、より古い世代
It's Mr. Yang Zhengning, many of them
楊正寧さん、その多くは
They didn't have dead nutrition at that time
当時彼らには死んだ栄養はなかった
are not enough
十分ではありません
People's nutrition is waiting to be told by others
人々の栄養は他人から教えられるのを待っている
So I think these things are
したがって、これらのことは次のとおりだと思います
our cells or our body
私たちの細胞や体
The nutrients that need the elements are six categories
必要な栄養素は6つに分類される
almost enough
ほぼ十分
In fact, don’t talk too much, it’s a walk for everyone
実際、あまり話さないでください、それはみんなの散歩です
It is the first one that is a burden to your liver
肝臓に負担をかけるのはそれが第一です
because he's going to metabolize him
彼は新陳代謝するから
This is a burden on the kidneys
これは腎臓に負担がかかります
I don't know why the Xisheng population in Taiwan
なぜ台湾に西生人口が多いのか分かりません
will run to number one in the world
世界ナンバーワンを目指して走ります
just don't understand
ただ理解できない
it's just too concentrated
それはただ集中しすぎているだけです
things it can't filter out
フィルタリングできないもの
So it's possible we're
だから私たちはそうなる可能性がある
attitude of human absorption
人間の吸収の姿勢
things we may not necessarily need
必ずしも必要ではないもの
so that our organs
私たちの臓器が
Can't get back together
一緒に戻れない
the liver and kidney organs
肝臓と腎臓の臓器
Then you can think of our brains as
そうすると、私たちの脳は次のように考えることができます。
an organ of the body
体の器官
So just don't over
だからもうやめないでね
not too much
多すぎない程度に
if you die like this
このまま死んだら
I think you have a little lack
少し物足りないと思います
Thanks
ありがとう
our gentleman
私たちの紳士
wait a minute he doesn't ask
等一下他不問
it's okay i'm in no rush to leave
大丈夫、急いで出発するつもりはない
so he has a problem
それで彼は問題を抱えている
i can play more
もっと遊べるよ
who
WHO
hello my name is zhong
こんにちは、私の名前はチョンです
Hello Li Bo
こんにちは、李波
The question I want to ask is
私が聞きたい質問は
Like today's topic
今日の話題のように
brain is complex
脳は複雑です
This general concept is for everyone
この一般的な概念はすべての人に当てはまります
Ordinary people are not good at some understanding
普通の人は理解が苦手なところがあります
Then I want to understand
それから私は理解したいです
research on the brain
脳の研究
Of course, there are also aspects of deduction
もちろん控除の面もあります
Is there anyone who is the first in this field?
この分野で最初の人はいますか？
is the direction of research in the House of Representatives
下院における研究の方向性である
or which way to go
またはどちらに行くべきか
The main reason is that there is a lot of hunting environment
主な理由は、狩猟環境が豊富であることです。
for example
例えば
sympathetic part
交感神経の部分
its constant part
その定数部分
there's some ideology
何らかのイデオロギーがある
some people like
好きな人もいます
And another previous century
そしてまた一世紀
chairman of their memory
彼らの記憶の会長
use their memory
彼らの記憶を使う
The chairman himself is studying this part
この部分は会長自らが勉強中です
what did you ask you last
最後に何を尋ねましたか
What
何
what memory
何の思い出
that is
あれは
The chairman of the board of directors is the major field of National Taiwan University
理事長は国立台湾大学の専門分野
What is the efficacy of that field
その分野の効能は何ですか
they have done this
彼らはこれをやった
Another aspect of research
研究のもう一つの側面
I just said that some people are too old to protect their mothers
母親を守るには年をとりすぎている人もいると言いました
seen too many people
あまりにも多くの人を見ました
Then their learning is another level
そうすれば、彼らの学習は別のレベルになります
so
それで
just from a young age
ちょうど若い頃から
this one is
これは
come through hopeless
絶望的な状況を乗り越える
some people are born with
持って生まれた人もいます
Knowledge is quite rich
知識はかなり豊富です
Of course, another magnetic field related to brain waves
もちろん、脳波に関係する別の磁場もあります。
Communicate with another understanding
別の理解を持ってコミュニケーションする
like this study
この研究のように
I'm covering a wide range of topics here
ここでは幅広いトピックを取り上げています
i didn't come to ask this question
私はこの質問をしに来たわけではありません
what i want to ask is to say
私が聞きたいのは言いたいことです
At present, if research in this area
現時点でこの分野の研究があれば、
Probably the world is still super-picked up in the direction
おそらく世界はまだその方向に超敏感です
pick up the brain
脳を拾う
because picking up is blurry
ピックアップがぼやけるので
then research over there
それからあそこで調べてください
we already know
私たちはすでに知っています
probably you all know
おそらく皆さんご存知でしょう
Thanks
ありがとう
this you just said
あなたが今言ったこれ
current research on the brain
脳に関する現在の研究
memory research
記憶の研究
what is the direction
方向は何ですか
what's the point
ポイントは何ですか
this is what i was about to say
これが私が言おうとしていたことです
This is another world wave
これは別の世界の波です
this VG
このVG
I'll talk about that right away
それについてはすぐに話します
Current focus on neuroscience research
現在は神経科学の研究に重点を置いています
is the word Circuit
回路という言葉です
That is to say, our brain
つまり、私たちの脳は、
form this nerve
この神経を形成する
Between the nerve cells of the brain
脳の神経細胞の間
forming this network its importance
このネットワークの形成の重要性
It is to study diseases, to study systems
それは病気を研究すること、システムを研究することです
rather than studying single cells
単一細胞を研究するのではなく
Must study a population of cells
細胞集団を研究する必要がある
And the network it forms between this group of cells
そして、この細胞群の間に形成されるネットワーク
In our human beings regardless of learning memory
私たち人間の場合、学習記憶とは無関係に
Transmission of Pain Senses
痛みの感覚の伝達
and its role in disease
および病気におけるその役割
Stericate
ステリケート
I will talk about System Biology
システムバイオロジーについてお話します
with emphasis
強調して
on your own or circuit
自分自身またはサーキットで
neuralgia path neuralgia path
神経痛の道 神経痛の道
So we're a hardcore ghost
だから私たちは筋金入りの幽霊なのよ
integrated system
統合システム
Instead of looking at single and single cells
単一の細胞だけを調べるのではなく、
is everything that connects them
それらをつなぐすべてのもの
As for what you just said
あなたが今言ったことについては
conscious, subconscious
意識的な、潜在意識的な
Those things seem to be more of a psychological level.
それらはより心理的なレベルのもののようです。
I think this now has a field called cognitive science
これには認知科学と呼ばれる分野があると思います
not so long now
もうそれほど長くはありません
Cognitive science
認知科学
Because abandonment has to wait for the advanced development of technology
放棄は技術の高度な発展を待たなければならないため
Current trends in cognitive science
認知科学の現在の動向
at least in america
少なくともアメリカでは
Obama or something like that will go down
オバマとかそういうのは潰れるだろう
what to do
何をすべきか
There is a professor Jiang Anshi in China
中国に江安石教授がいる
do that in fruit eagle city
フルーツイーグルシティでやれよ
functional mapping
機能マッピング
It is the correspondence between functions and some packages
機能と一部パッケージの対応です
Which nerve cell does what function
どの神経細胞がどのような機能を果たしているのか
he hikes with a nerve
彼は緊張しながらハイキングする
mark him clearly
彼にはっきりとマークを付ける
remember every time
毎回思い出す
But this matter is easier to do in Guoying
しかし、この問題は国営の方がやりやすい。
Because fruit eagle is very simple
フルーツイーグルはとてもシンプルなので
he has very few nerve cells
彼には神経細胞がほとんどない
so you can go one by one
だから一つ一つ進んでいいよ
map
地図
Follow the map to find the map
地図に従って地図を見つけてください
what does this nerve cell do
この神経細胞は何をしているのか
broken
壊れた
He may not have any function
彼には何の機能もないかもしれない
hit something
何かに当たる
how is he responsible for what
彼は何に対してどのように責任を負うのか
real
本物
but in human
しかし人間では
I think this thing is difficult to do
これは難しいと思います
I've also asked a lot of neuroscientists
多くの神経科学者にも尋ねました
They find it extremely difficult
彼らはそれが非常に難しいと感じています
because
なぜなら
that nerve cell
その神経細胞
you want to talk about structure
構造について話したいのですか
it's all that simple
それはとても簡単です
i just said
私はちょうど言いました
battery discharge
バッテリーの放電
The chemical then passes on to the next
化学物質は次に次の物質に移ります。
But why this nerve cell
しかし、なぜこの神経細胞は
chop down here
ここで切り倒す
in a certain area
ある地域で
He is in charge of this matter to that matter
彼はこの件からあの件までを担当している
you spread it out
あなたはそれを広げました
Just look at his characteristics, they are all the same
彼の特徴を見てください、それらはすべて同じです
This is his rich house
ここは彼の裕福な家です
you say something
あなたは何かを言います
Aware of a better continuous test
より良い継続的テストを意識する
then you might say some people
それから、何人かの人がいると言うかもしれません
very casually
とてもカジュアルに
some people
人によっては
maybe honest
正直かもしれない
some people are very talkative
とてもおしゃべりな人もいます
What kind of neurotic do you think this is?
これはどのような神経症だと思いますか？
what are you doing
あなたは何をしている
Other access
他通路
really did not do
本当にしなかった
I don't know what to do
何をすればいいのか分かりません
So the complexity of human
つまり、人間の複雑さは、
yes
はい
suppose i should say
言うべきだと思います
That's what scientists pay attention to
科学者が注目しているのはそこだ
After rigorous experimental manipulation
厳密な実験操作の後
to get reproducible results
再現可能な結果を​​得るには
If you say he should be the same
あなたが彼も同じであるべきだと言うなら
but something
でも何か
If we are not easy to manipulate
私たちを操作するのが簡単ではない場合
such as the subconscious
潜在意識などの
why did i study psychology
なぜ心理学を学んだのか
Later I studied neuroscience
その後、神経科学を学びました
because I'm studying psychology
心理学を勉強しているので
some existentialism
ある種の実存主義
what humanism
何というヒューマニズム
i really find it difficult for me to understand
本当に理解するのが難しいと思います
Because that's abstract and I don't know the consent of that existence
それは抽象的でその存在の同意が分からないから
how can i replace him
どうすれば彼の代わりになれるでしょうか
or how to verify him
または彼を確認する方法
then i just say
それから私はただ言います
This theory of Freud
このフロイトの理論は、
It's actually amazing
本当にすごいですよ
conscious subconscious
意識的な潜在意識
He can also answer many questions
彼はたくさんの質問にも答えてくれます
For example, people in our polite
たとえば、私たちの礼儀正しい人々は、
you taught us education
あなたは私たちに教育を教えてくれました
let us many things are in our
たくさんのものを私たちの中に入れましょう
What not to do in normal life to deal with the state
状態に対処するために通常の生活でしてはいけないこと
then you may have some stress
それならストレスもあるかもしれない
So Freud's theory says
そこでフロイトの理論はこう言います
you're going to sleep
あなたは寝るつもりです
subconsciously
無意識のうちに
when dreaming
夢を見ているとき
This is dreaming has a great function
これは夢を見ることの素晴らしい機能です
but let you put your usual
でも、いつものことを入れてみましょう
Release what needs to be suppressed
抑制すべきものを解放する
It's healthier for people
それは人々にとってより健康的です
And especially Freudians like to talk about sex
そして特にフロイト派はセックスについて話すのが好きです
Sex
セックス
I think discussing what he does
彼が何をしているのかについて話し合うと思います
what he said
他講的東西
In fact, there are his theoretical techniques
実は彼の理論的なテクニックがあるんです。
He has also been quoted
彼も引用されています
just say biological
生物学的とだけ言ってください
From a neuroscience point of view
神経科学の観点から
What we often do is to
私たちがよくやるのは、
really can control that factor
本当にその要素をコントロールできる
There are doses that can exceed the
を超える可能性のある線量があります
Then we look at the result
次に結果を見てみましょう
So for magnetic fields these
したがって、磁場の場合、これらは
We will then
それでは、
I don't really know how to do experimental combat
実験戦闘のやり方がよくわからない
this may be
これはそうかもしれない
Ask a psycho to go home and work with a physicist
精神科医に家に帰って物理学者と一緒に働くように依頼してください
to do something like this
このようなことをするために
But we do have magnetic fields and all that
しかし、私たちには磁場などがあります。
The magnetic field will respond to the magnetic field
磁場は磁場に反応する
it's also true
それも本当です
Look at the bees and ants
ミツバチやアリを見てください
They all know the way to go home
彼らは皆、家に帰る方法を知っています
I think they know the way better than me
彼らは私よりも道をよく知っていると思います
they can many birds can fly that far
たくさんの鳥があんな遠くまで飛べるのね
he knows where to go
彼はどこに行くべきかを知っています
I don’t know that we in Taiwan later discovered that
台湾にいた私たちが後からそのことを知ったかどうかは知りませんが、
end of a bee's pen scar
ミツバチのペンの跡の端
there is a large area
広いエリアがあります
Is it all iron or is it all iron
全部鉄ですか、それとも全部鉄ですか
So it this iron will
それで、このアイアンはこうなります
Because the police station is sensitive to magnetic fields
警察署は磁気に敏感なため
Did this help him find his way?
これは彼が自分の道を見つけるのに役立ちましたか？
felt
感じた
Because we don't know the audience
視聴者がわからないから
Needless to say they may be sensitive to magnetic fields
言うまでもなく、磁場に敏感である可能性があります
so this is him
それでこれが彼です
what does he know about these bees
彼はこれらのミツバチについて何を知っていますか
run out fly into him
走り出すと彼に飛び込む
he went back to his house later
彼は後で家に戻った
It is the changes caused by the reprinting of those metals to the magnetic field
それらの金属が磁場に再転写されることによって引き起こされる変化です
we don't know
私たちは知りません
The magnetic field of human wisdom will be reflected by the magnetic field
人類の叡智の磁場が磁場に反映される
That's why we need to ignore our hearts and brains
だからこそ私たちは心と脳を無視する必要があるのです
That's why we need to say when it's time to go to the exam room
だからこそ、いつ試験室に行くかを言う必要があるのです
We need to reprint all possible magnetic fields
考えられるすべての磁場を再印刷する必要があります
Everything that hangs on the magnetic field must be removed.
磁場にぶら下がっているものはすべて取り除く必要があります。
Because of your influence because we will spread to
あなたの影響で私たちは広がるから
Is it a question I'm asking
それは私が尋ねている質問ですか
I'm just messing around
ただふざけてるだけだよ
the question i want to ask
私が聞きたい質問
Like IBM it uses an analog
IBMと同様にアナログを使用しています
Like a descender, it will deduce various functions by using
ディセンダーのように、さまざまな関数を推測します
Then compare this system with the brain
次に、このシステムを脳と比較します。
then do development
それから開発をする
That is to say, do it with a computer
つまり、コンピュータでやればいいのです
similarated brain like this
このような脳が似ています
similaration and then fully deduce the function of the brain
類似性を調べて脳の機能を完全に推定します
memorize and calculate what
何を暗記して計算するか
if it uses another system
別のシステムを使用している場合
Then deal with it in a temper tantrum
それから癇癪を起こして対処する
You can use my temper
私の短気を利用してもいいよ
Ok, everyone has my System on the other side
OK、みんなが反対側に私のシステムを持っています
actually walked in here
実際にここに入った
I don't know about foreign countries
外国のことは知りません
because we walk the system
私たちはシステムを歩むからです
For example, a park that looks like a cranial nerve
たとえば、脳神経のような公園
The function also has MARY square
MARYスクエア機能も搭載
Even his definition is unclear
連他的定義都定義不清楚
so you look at us again
それであなたはまた私たちを見ます
how to integrate
どのように統合するか
Because of Subsistence to
自給自足のため
Then the Tortus System
次にトータスシステム
Then System and another System
その後、システムは別のシステムに従う
The whole link is done and Grashing
全体のリンクが完了し、グラッシングが完了しました
There is still a lot of complexity
まだまだ複雑な部分がたくさんあります
Then it looks like I don't even know the basic definition
そうすると基本的な定義すらわかっていないみたいですね
I just have one question then and that is
そこで一つだけ質問があるのですが、それは
Do this like the black face
これを黒い顔のようにしてください
Deduced from overseas brain nerves and computers
海外の脳神経とコンピューターから導き出した
integrated interface
統合インターフェース
Does anyone in Taiwan do this?
台湾でこれをする人はいますか？
I think there is
あると思います
Broadly speaking, as you said
大まかに言えば、あなたが言ったように
artificial intelligence
人工知能
Partificial in Taiwan
一部台湾でも
When I went back to Taiwan while chanting Huasu Mountain
華粛山を唱えながら台湾に帰ったとき
have this name
この名前を持っています
artificial intelligence
人工知能
Then what is developed now is to use computers
そこで今開発されているのがコンピューターを使うことです
Use a similar computer
同様のコンピューターを使用する
but I as a biologist
しかし生物学者としての私は
I always feel that the computer
いつも思うのですが、コンピューターは
It is difficult to completely simulate the human brain
人間の脳を完全にシミュレートすることは困難です
It can be at the physical interface
物理インターフェイスにある可能性があります
Physical
物理的
C6M like electric signal
C6Mのような電気信号
How big is the Spike, what is the frequency?
スパイクの大きさ、周波数はどれくらいですか?
It can be even more precise than the human mind
それは人間の思考よりもさらに正確である可能性があります
But the problem is you use a computer
しかし、問題はコンピューターを使うことです
Simulate those functions
それらの関数をシミュレートする
those individual elements
それらの個々の要素
it can never be explained
それは決して説明できない
Why
なぜ
Your cell in the network
ネットワーク内のあなたのセル
this unit
このユニット
it is emotional
それは感情的です
it is fun
楽しいです
You can't explain this
これを説明することはできません
Why is this other cell
なぜこれが別の細胞なのか
it can think
それは考えることができる
or is it something that can feel artistic or abstract
それとも芸術的または抽象的に感じられるものですか？
When applied to functions
関数に適用する場合
it sees these
それはこれらを見ます
Elements of these units simulated in the computer
コンピュータでシミュレートされたこれらのユニットの要素
it can't explain
それは説明できません
it can only explain
それは説明することしかできません
Physical very basic physical phenomenon
物理的な非常に基本的な物理現象
This explanation is more precise
この説明の方が正確です
is so
そうだね
So the human brain has its very mysterious and incredible
人間の脳には、非常に神秘的で信じられないほどの特徴があります。
This guy over here is ively sane
ここにいるこの男は非常に正気です
Teacher Li and I happen to be neighbors
リー先生と私はたまたま隣人です
So I knew about this message before posting it
だから私はこのメッセージを投稿する前から知っていました
First of all, thank you because he was before the lecturer system
講師制度前なのでまずはよろしくお願いします
Introduction to that memory and forgetting
その記憶と忘却についての紹介
Then my question is
それから私の質問は
my friend's relatives
私の友人の親戚
Suffering is a flower-seeking teacher-made disease
苦しみは花を求める先生が作った病気
Some are in their twenties and thirties
20代、30代の人もいます
And he finds sex by himself
そして彼は自分でセックスを見つける
It seems that he has a difficult problem to deal with.
彼は対処するのが難しい問題を抱えているようだ。
Another related question is
もう一つの関連した質問は、
Asked for my friend in his nineties
90代の友人に頼まれました
he is a serious learner
彼は真剣な学習者です
so how is his life
それで彼の人生はどうですか
he often sleeps very little
彼はよくほとんど眠らない
Then what he's worried about is the opiates and painkillers.
そこで彼が心配しているのはアヘン剤と鎮痛剤だ。
will it affect us
私たちに影響はありますか
our brainpower
私たちの知力
right
右
OK
OK
good
良い
You just talked about the premature
あなたは今、時期尚早について話しました
This is really medical
これはまさに医療です
relatively unresolved piece
比較的未解決の部分
That is to say more incomprehensible
つまりさらに意味不明
because this is really
これは本当にあるから
innate genetic factors
先天的な遺伝的要因
accounted for a large part
大きな部分を占めた
Then I don't know his relatives
それから彼の親戚は知りません
are there many people
人はたくさんいますか
is there such a marriage
そのような結婚はありますか
So I think this is relatively impossible
なのでこれは比較的無理だと思います
when he might be bearing the next generation
彼が次世代を産むかもしれないとき
will really pay attention
本当に注意します
Then you say it's better to be cancerous
じゃあ癌になった方が良いって言うんだね
You just said sleeping pills or headache medicine
さっき睡眠薬とか頭痛薬って言ったじゃないですか。
Headache medicine
頭痛薬
i think to be honest
正直に言うと思う
I don't know if
どうか分かりません
how much did he eat
彼はどれくらい食べましたか
that pair
そのペア
You and I have been neighbors for decades
あなたと私は何十年も隣人です
but you may not know
でもあなたは知らないかも知れません
I have severe migraines
重度の片頭痛があります
I'm biased
私は偏見を持っています
I have a vascular migraine
血管性片頭痛があります
it just stinks
ただ臭いだけです
It's just that the blood vessels are very dilated.
ただ血管が非常に拡張しているだけです。
so i need medicine
だから薬が必要だ
constrict blood vessels
血管を収縮させる
It was like this when I was in college
大学時代はこんな感じだった
is a constitution
憲法です
I have eaten for more than 30 years
30年以上食べています
i feel ok
私は大丈夫だと感じています
My liver function was normal when I went for the test
検査を受けたときの肝機能は正常でした
it's basically a metabolic problem
それは基本的に代謝の問題です
It's a liver hurt stomach
肝臓が痛い胃です
But now the headache medicine
でも今は頭痛薬
it's all well done
すべてうまくいきました
aspin
アスピン
you know aspin is a slime
アスピンはスライムだということは知っていますか
really great drug
本当に素晴らしい薬
He talks about finger pain
他主論指痛
cardiovascular disease
循環器疾患
have a little preventive effect
多少の予防効果はある
But aspin because of a stomachache
しかし腹痛のため休んでいる
So later develop the most common
したがって、後で最も一般的なものを開発します
The whole world should just fix it
世界中がそれを直すべきだ
Eating the most food in the world is not an excellent disease
世界で一番たくさん食べることは立派な病気ではない
It's Prolactin
それはプロラクチンです
Because people are under a lot of pressure, they are chasing back and chasing pain
人々は大きなプレッシャーにさらされているため、痛みを追いかけ、痛みを追いかけます。
I'm eating this too
これも食べてます
I'm not eating so strong
そんなに強く食べてないよ
when i really have a headache
本当に頭が痛いとき
I will eat
食べます
I ate that day, actually that day
あの日、実際にその日に食べました
headache is not a disease
頭痛は病気ではありません
Inner symptoms are resolved
内面の症状が治まる
it's called sinclair
それはシンクレアと呼ばれています
it's not a disease
それは病気ではありません
It's fine when the symptoms are gone
症状が治まれば大丈夫です
I have eaten this way for decades
私は何十年もそうやって食べてきました
My liver function is ok
肝機能は大丈夫です
Because pronatol is different from aspin
プロナトールはアスピンとは違うので
He added a little buffer
彼は少しバッファを追加しました
he added something
彼は何かを付け加えた
so my body is not fit
だから体が合わないんだよ
Aspiny is relatively normal stomach
アスピニーは比較的正常な胃です
i look
私は見ます
i am an example
私はその一例です
so i think it should
だからそうすべきだと思う
Headache is OK
頭痛要OK
insomnia medicine
不眠症の薬
Actually, I think it's time to talk to the doctor.
実際、医者に相談する時期が来たと思います。
Because it's actually an insomnia drug
実は不眠症の薬だから
also a lot
もたくさん
the doctor will augment
医者が増強するだろう
everyone's situation
みんなの状況
will prescribe that drug
その薬を処方します
But when people get older
しかし人は歳をとると
insomnia will become
不眠症になります
just can't sleep
ただ眠れない
long sleep phase
長い睡眠段階
It's actually quite normal
それは実際にはごく普通のことです
We'll go back to places like the ghost
私たちは幽霊のような場所に戻ります
ghost is sleeping
幽霊が寝ています
sleep, wake up
寝る、起きる
when we were adults
私たちが大人だった頃
when forty or fifty years old
40歳か50歳になると
Easier
比較容易
Young people are not getting enough sleep
若者は十分な睡眠をとれていない
have been sleeping
眠っています
eight hours of sleep, nine hours like that
8時間睡眠、9時間そんな感じ
sleep eight hours straight nine hours
8時間連続9時間睡眠
you are healthy
あなたは健康だ
older people
高齢者
you may be in this person
あなたはこの人の中にいるかもしれません
Such a situation is found in people
このような状況は人々に見られます
He probably slept for five hours, six hours
彼はおそらく5時間か6時間眠ったでしょう
he just
ちょうど彼
he is enough
彼は十分です
but he only needs
しかし彼に必要なのは
so young people are
だから若い人たちは
you are going to sleep
あなたは寝るところだ
you after a while
しばらくしてからあなた
fell asleep for a while
しばらく眠りについた
it doesn't matter
それは問題ではありません
but when you fall asleep
でも眠りにつくときは
to be able to sleep for hours at a time
何時間も続けて眠ることができる
Your sleep cycle can only be complete
睡眠サイクルは完了することしかできません
every one of you what do you know
皆さんは何を知っていますか
Ccard Weifa dream period
Ccard ウェイファ夢の時代
You've heard of the rapid eye movement period
眼球運動が早い時期について聞いたことがあるでしょう。
Rapid eye movement
急速眼球運動
that's important
それは重要です
that was dreaming period
夢を見ていた時代だった
You just need to sleep for a certain amount of time
一定時間寝ればいいだけ
All these cycles he's done
彼はこれらすべてのサイクルを完了しました
so the doctor may see
医者が見てくれるように
Give him a good four hours of sleep
彼に4時間十分な睡眠を与えてください
But it's four hours better than if you can't sleep all the time
でも、ずっと眠れないよりは 4 時間マシです
or wake up in half an hour
あるいは30分後に起きる
woke up in half an hour
30分で目が覚めた
much better
ずっといい
so i think it's been a year
だから1年経ったと思う
medicine is already
薬はもう
I think
私が思うに
The world's doctors on insomnia drugs
不眠症治療薬を研究する世界の医師
Actually quite understand
実はよくわかる
because i know friends
私は友達を知っているので
He has been eating for twenty or thirty years
彼は20年も30年も食べ続けている
can help him sleep for more than four hours
彼が4時間以上眠るのを助けることができる
more than four hours
4時間以上
He goes to bed at nine o'clock and wakes up at three o'clock
彼は9時に寝て3時に起きる
he still sleeps very short
彼はまだ睡眠時間が非常に短いです
But for him
しかし、彼にとっては
He has been asleep for hours
彼は何時間も眠っています
enough
十分
So let's say it's all a bit simpler now
それでは、すべてがもう少し簡単になったとします。
take a blood test
驗個血
If dry index is normal
乾燥指数が正常の場合
If the kidney index is normal
腎臓指数が正常であれば
Actually this medicine
実はこの薬
basically no damage
基本的にダメージはありません
Holy day college classmate
聖日大学の同級生
so
それで
At 90 years old, I think I can handle everything
90歳になったら何でもできると思う
I think
私が思うに
I can
できます
I didn't know it was possible to do whatever I wanted again
やりたいことがまたできるようになるなんて知らなかった
I don't know what happened in the 80s and 90s
80年代、90年代に何があったかは知りませんが、
but
しかし
I know everything
私はすべてを知っています
ok our last question
はい、最後の質問です
but if say
でも言うなら
good
良い
good come
よかった
please
お願いします
Hello teacher, I am now
こんにちは、先生、私は今です
I now
今私は
Hello teacher, I am Zeng Jianzhu
こんにちは、先生、私は曾建珠です。
I am now at Oxford University in England
私は今イギリスのオックスフォード大学にいます
Ph.D candidate at Korea Research Center
高麗研究中心念博士
Then the subject of my research is
それでは私の研究テーマは
Provide services for the elderly in Taiwan
台湾で高齢者向けサービスを提供
Non-profit organizations
非営利団体
basically
基本上
will be fine
よくなる
so i have two questions
それで質問が2つあります
May be more practical
より実用的になるかもしれません
But it is also hoped that the
しかし、次のことも期待されています。
more scientific point of view
より科学的な視点
can provide some different thinking
別の考え方を提供できる
The first part is
最初の部分は
Yes or no
はい、もしくは、いいえ
essentially
本質的に
He is to a large extent
彼はかなりの程度そうだ
no way
とんでもない
is irreversible
不可逆的です
that is
あれは
be a patient
患者になる
it's more difficult to go
行くのはもっと難しいです
can have some thoughts
いくつかの考えがあるかもしれない
or mental and deteriorating
または精神的に悪化している
This is the first question
これが最初の質問です
Then the second question if
次に 2 番目の質問は、
The answer to the first question is Yes
最初の質問に対する答えは「はい」です
Then what I want to ask next is
それでは次に聞きたいのは、
Assume in case a family is unlucky
不幸な家族の場合を想定してください
its members
そのメンバー
this happened
これが起こりました
For the family members who accompany you
ご同行されるご家族様へ
what families can do
家族ができること
On the one hand, to help the world
一方で、世界を助けるために
have a better old age
よりよい老後を過ごしてください
On the other hand, let yourself be a care giver
一方で、自分自身を介護者にしましょう
won't have such a big burden
そんなに大きな負担はないだろう
Thank you, teacher
ありがとう、先生
The latter belongs to
後者が属するのは、
Sociological way
社会学的方法
right
右
in front
前に
unfortunately to tell you
残念ながらあなたに言うと
really no way
本当に無理
and
と
i can say that
それは言えます
The United States invested a lot of money
アメリカは巨額の資金を投資した
developing Alzheimer's drug
アルツハイマー病の治療薬を開発中
Help the world in many ways
さまざまな方法で世界を助ける
It is to give this one machine that one from the neural pathway
それは、この 1 つの機械に神経経路からの 1 つを与えることです。
Actually spent a lot of money
実際にかなりのお金を使いました
In fact, the answer is no
実際、答えはノーです
a very important
とても重要な
There is no better curative effect
これ以上の治療効果はない
The current medicine may actually
現在の薬は実際には
still the same as decades ago
数十年前と同じまま
just maybe a little more
もう少しだけかもしれない
the reason is simple
理由は簡単です
It's the cells that die and don't regenerate
死んで再生しない細胞です
That's it
それでおしまい
it is an irreversible
それは取り返しのつかないことだ
So neurodegenerative disease
つまり神経変性疾患
it will only get heavier
重くなるだけです
not only this
これだけでなく
Eight classics of life of life of life of life of life of life
人生の人生の人生の人生の人生の人生の8つの古典
It's just that the number of lost people is relatively large
ただ、行方不明者の数が比較的多いだけです
So what is the direction the United States is doing now?
では、米国は現在どのような方向に進んでいるのだろうか？
it's no longer blooming waist
もう腰には咲かない
no more liver
もう肝臓はない
What it does now is the Stensile
現在実行しているのは Stensile です
It is IPS
IPSです
is inducible
誘導可能です
that germ layer
その胚葉
cell ectoderm
細胞外胚層
Can be differentiated
差別化できる
for example
例えば
That differentiated into the liver and what and what
それは肝臓と何に分化したのか
These organs come
これらの器官が来ます
to disease
病気に
or nerve gland diseases for treatment
または治療のための神経腺疾患
because it was an embryo transfer
以前に胚移植をしたので
I remember we used to be at the restoration plant
私たちは修復工場にいたことを覚えています
Zhang Optical Restoration Factory is the birthplace of the Eight Classics
張光学修復工場は八古典の発祥の地です
He is taking embryo transfer
彼は胚移植を受けています
But this embryo transfer
しかし、今回の胚移植は
may be better
多分よくなる
but it's very controversial
しかしそれは非常に物議を醸している
because of this someone
この誰かのせいで
someone intentionally aborted what
誰かが意図的に何かを中止した
only
それだけ
no, use that embryo
いいえ、その胚を使用してください
for brain transplant
脳移植用
So what is done now is called
したがって、今行われていることは次のように呼ばれます
differentiation of stem cells
幹細胞の分化
That
それか
my home
私の家
Like many teams in the United States are
米国の多くのチームと同じように、
it's not easy to do
それは簡単ではありません
Even put a lot of announcements on this
これについてもたくさんの発表を行います
But science is always progressing
しかし科学は常に進歩しています
scientists are always trying
科学者は常に努力している
so
それで
And sometimes you know that scientific discoveries
そして時々、科学的発見が
It's all you line up like this
こうやって並べるだけで
when do you think it might come out
いつ出てくると思いますか
you can do nothing for a long time
長い間何もできません
But you also sometimes have unexpected surprises and discoveries
でも時には思いがけない驚きや発見があることもあります
is so
そうだね
So as long as there is doing
だから、やっている限り
Anyway, there is always hope for human beings
とにかく人間には希望が必ずある
There may be spiritual requirements
精神的な要求があるかもしれない
So for now
だから今のところ
In fact, the real research on Alzheimer's disease in the United States is
実際、米国におけるアルツハイマー病に関する本当の研究は、
Actually
実際
is slowly selling down
徐々に売れていきます
unless something shows up
何かが現れない限り
what's new
新着情報
that might be put down later
それは後で取り下げられるかもしれない
as you say
あなたが言うように
Is there anyone in the family like this?
家族の中にこんな人はいませんか？
I think
私が思うに
I just got the point
要点がわかりました
In fact, it may be more
実際にはそれ以上かもしれません
take care of this person
この人の世話をしてください
so
それで
because it's a big burden
負担が大きいから
I think apart from the psychological
心理的なこととは別に考えます
Psychological means to know
心理学的には「知る」という意味がある
This is an irreversible phenomenon
これは取り返しのつかない現象です
just accept it
ただ受け入れてください
In reality, I think
実際のところ、私はそう思います
Ability to ask for personal assistance to take care of patients
患者の世話をするために個人的な援助を求めることができる
let yourself get enough rest
十分な休息をとりましょう
take a break
休憩する
this thing is still important
このことはまだ重要です
Because otherwise it's just one more member
そうしないとメンバーが1人増えるだけだから
One more member is more useful
メンバーがもう 1 人いるとさらに便利です
or other symptoms of unemployment
または失業のその他の症状
Of course you said that for the patients themselves
もちろん患者さん自身のためとおっしゃいましたが
If he still has contact with the outside world
まだ外の世界との接触があれば
or when he still responds to stimuli
またはまだ刺激に反応しているとき
I think he went to play mahjong
彼は麻雀をしに行ったようだ
Talk to everyone and talk about what to pick up
みんなと話し合って何を買うか話し合う
Actually it's all good
実際には大丈夫です
just use your brain
ただ頭を使ってください
he can use his brain
彼は頭脳を使える
expose him to the outside world
彼を外の世界にさらす
Both are better than ISO classes alone
どちらも ISO クラス単独よりも優れています
is better
優れている
Because we're going to keep his nerve cells alive
私たちは彼の神経細胞を生かし続けるつもりだから
able to interact with other nerve cells
他の神経細胞と相互作用することができる
This will delay his illness
そうすれば彼の病気は遅れるだろう
Just one day, twenty years later
20年後のたった一日
I think playing mahjong is actually very good
麻雀をするのは本当に良いことだと思う
people often ask me this question
人々はよく私にこの質問をします
Not today
今日ではありません
this one plays mahjong
この人は麻雀をします
a very simple principle
非常に単純な原理
we talk about thinking
私たちは思考について話します
we say use
私たちは使うと言います
not cranky
不機嫌ではない
is thinking
考えています
It's better to think deeply
深く考えたほうがいいよ
Of course I can't be cruel
もちろん残酷なことはできない
I just answered everyone
先ほど全員に答えました
People say you do the math problems in the middle school
あなたがあの中学校で数学の問題をやっていると言われます
to count that
それを数える
C What is the angle
C 角度は何ですか
Although I think that kind of thinking is really useful
そういう考え方はとても有益だと思いますが、
Tired of thinking
考えるのに疲れた
but useful
でも役に立つ
but you play mahjong
でもあなたは麻雀をします
You also have to fight with your high pole
ハイポールでも戦わなければなりません
You're going to make a fool of yourself in three or two moves.
3、2手でバカにされてしまうだろう。
you didn't use
あなたは使わなかった
you didn't think too much
あなたはあまり考えませんでした
you won easily
あなたは簡単に勝った
so
それで
I think it's a very simple example
非常に単純な例だと思います
what is thinking
何を考えていますか
you have to
必ず
you better be thoughtful or
思慮深いほうがいいですよ、あるいは
if it is true
それが本当なら
to think hard or
一生懸命考えるか、
not just good or thought
良いことや考えたことだけではありません
or cranky
または気難しい
that's not thinking
それは考えていない
So one can touch
だから人は触れることができる
able to think
考えることができる
play bridge
プレイブリッジ
this
これ
play mahjong in the afternoon
午後は麻雀をする
go online
オンライン化する
In fact, many citizens
実際、多くの国民が
all good
大丈夫です
They said that Bajingsheng really has a doctor who also recommends that
彼らは、Bajingsheng には実際に次のことを勧める医師がいると言いました。
playing the piano is no good
ピアノを弾くのはダメだ
Why
なぜ
This is rehabilitation of limbs
手足のリハビリです
Playing the piano is a good rehabilitation person
ピアノを弾くと良いリハビリになります
So that means
つまり、
From these examples
これらの例から
that is
あれは
make him move something
彼に何かを動かしてもらう
Let your mysterious place come alive
あなたの神秘的な場所を生き生きとさせましょう
Suppose you have poor motor function
運動機能が低下しているとします
you just go to exercise
あなたはただ運動しに行くだけです
Suppose you are thinking poorly
あなたが下手に考えていると仮定してください
just do your thinking
ただ自分の考えを実行してください
That's it
それでおしまい
So he can still end up with the outside world
だから彼はまだ外の世界に行くことができる
Just try to let him end with the outside world
ただ彼を外の世界で終わらせてみてください
When it develops to a certain extent
ある程度発展すると
I think it just needs manpower
人手が必要なだけだと思います
Share coolies
クーリーを共有する
That's it
それでおしまい
Then I think the family Xiaode means
それから私はXiaode家族を意味すると思います
just to take this
これを取るためだけに
just accept the reality
ただ現実を受け入れてください
you want to be
あなたはなりたいです
a course of life
人生の流れ
that's it
それでおしまい
we were born
私たちは生まれました
Our brain cells are dying
私たちの脳細胞は死につつある
But in fact we humans are
しかし、実際には私たち人間は、
deceased
故人
But from a healthier perspective
しかし、より健康的な観点から見ると、
Now I'm going back to psychology
さて、心理学の話に戻ります
is what matters
重要なのは
So we should cherish and grasp the most
だから私たちが一番大切にして掴むべきは
When we are alive and healthy now
私たちが今生きていて健康であるとき
conscious every day
毎日意識的に
same life same thing
同じ人生同じこと
Really sometimes it depends on what people think
本当に時々それは人々の考えに依存します
The same thing, some people think he is very unfortunate
同様に、彼はとても不幸だと思う人もいる
some people are more optimistic
もっと楽観的な人もいます
I think you want to think about his good side
彼の良い面について考えてみたいと思います
He is a simple example
彼はその単純な例です
half a glass of water
一杯水剩半杯
Some people say that there is half a cup of buns left
バンズがカップ半分残っているという人もいる
Another person said it's ok and there's half a glass left
別の人は大丈夫、グラス半分残っていると言いました
That is to say, I feel grasped and fulfilled
つまり、掴まれて満たされたと感じるのです
when we are healthy
私たちが健康なとき
when my friend is clear
友達が晴れたら
Don't have any regrets after every day
毎日を過ごしても後悔しないように
I think this mentality is very important
この心構えはとても大切だと思います
because we never know
私たちには決して分からないから
what will happen next day
次の日は何が起こるでしょうか
good that
それはよかった
there is a problem here
ここに問題があります
Ask Professor Lin
リン教授に聞く
What you just said needs to be deep
あなたが今言ったことは深い必要があります
Then the speed level can be
次に、速度レベルは次のようになります。
you tell this i'll tell you
あなたはこれを言います、私はあなたに言います
besides
そのほか
I answer that speed now
そのスピードに今答えるよ
Otherwise I'm afraid I can't do anything
そうしないと怖くて何もできない
There is a very important question in the study
研究には非常に重要な疑問がある
The faster you learn, the faster you forget
学ぶのが早いほど、忘れるのも早くなります
learn more slowly
もっとゆっくり学ぶ
Because he has this consolidation
彼にはこの統合があるから
You can talk about everything
すべてについて話すことができます
The rhythm keeps turning on my machine, everyone moves
リズムがマシンを動かし続ける、みんなが動く
So his mysterious connection has been created
こうして彼の不思議なつながりが生まれました
Mysterious recipe
神秘邪方
The slower he learns, the slower he forgets
学ぶのが遅いほど、忘れるのも遅くなる
can operate longer
より長く動作できる
So the velocity is
したがって、速度は
you see what your problem is
あなたの問題が何であるかがわかります
you really want to read read read read
本当に読みたいです、読んでください、読んでください
He will use it, but it won't work
彼はそれを適用するだろうが、うまくいかないだろう
That's not the math one, is it?
それは数学の問題ではありませんね？
spell that number
その数字を綴ります
Oh you said accept
ああ、受け入れるって言ったね
You said that was paid well
料金がとても良かったと言ってました
I just wanted speed because I said it by the way
ちなみに言ったからにはスピードが欲しかっただけです
So I said that many people go to learn speed
だから私は、多くの人がスピードを学びに行くと言いました
think about it for yourself
自分で考えてみてください
need or not
必要かどうか
I feel like I feel like I'm going to live to be almost sixty
60歳近くまで生きそうな気がする
I don't think there is anything that requires me to read fast
速く読む必要があるものは何もないと思う
I was able to learn in my life
人生で学ぶことができました
i don't think so
私はそうは思わない
i can sell some reading
いくつかの本を売ることができます
But learned it very imitatively
でもとても真似して学びました
if i have to learn something
何かを学ばなければならない場合
so speed
とてもスピードが速い
For example, it is really purely for exams
たとえば、本当に純粋に試験用です
But I don't feel the need
でもその必要性を感じない
i will really feel this way
私は本当にそう感じるでしょう
because when psychology arrives
なぜなら心理学が到来すると
I tell us ACT academic results
ACTの学業成績を教えます
learn quickly forget quickly
すぐに覚えてすぐに忘れる
you say that
あなたはそれを言います
that's about math
それは数学についてです
For me, it is the study of mathematics
私にとってそれは数学の勉強です
just one two three
ちょうど 1 2 3
you fight like this
あなたはこうやって戦う
yes , like a lot of foreigners over there
はい、そこにいる多くの外国人のように
you keep watching
あなたは見続けています
Yes, you can think deeply
はい、深く考えることができます
this again
これまた
If you feel like you're making a show soon
もうすぐ番組を作りたいと思ったら
It's easy, then you don't think about it
簡単だから何も考えなくていいよ
What kind of bottom pressure do you do
どのような底圧をしますか
yes, that's what i do
はい、それが私がやっていることです
Really, this will
本当に、これは
is to pick a man to do it
それはそれをする人を選ぶことだ
So have you seen it all?
それで、全部見ましたか？
because you can't say it's hard right away
すぐに難しいとは言えないから
If you think you've reached this level
このレベルに到達したと思ったら
You just go to the next one that is more difficult
次のより難しいものに進むだけです
I think the one you can do is the next one
あなたができるのは次のことだと思う
That's it
それでおしまい
And this, psychologists still say it's very important
そして、これは心理学者は今でも非常に重要だと言います
I feel that when the ability is here
能力がここにあるとき、私はそう感じます
you want to tell you
あなたに言いたいのは
Human power is here
人間の力がここにある
you have to target your
あなたは自分をターゲットにしなければなりません
young people are still here
若い人たちはまだここにいる
Mainly for young people
主に若者向け
you want to set your goal here
ここで目標を設定したい
slightly higher
やや高いです
But don't set it too high
ただし、あまり高く設定しないでください
Because your ability is here, set here
あなたの能力がここにあるので、ここに設定してください
after your hard work
一生懸命働いた後
you will reach
あなたは到達します
achieve your goal
目標を達成する
Then you will feel more accomplished
そうすればもっと達成感が得られるでしょう
Then after the standard
それからスタンダードの後は
you set your goals a little higher
あなたは目標を少し高く設定しました
My life is all the way, you always come here like this
私の人生はずっと、あなたはいつもこうしてここに来ます
I think I'm still like this
まだこんな感じだと思う
you set it higher
あなたはそれを高く設定します
you try harder
あなたはもっと努力します
then you'll be more up to that standard
そうすればあなたはその基準にさらに達することができます
you don't want your real ability here
ここでは自分の本当の能力を望んでいません
you set that standard there
あなたはそこでその基準を設定します
Then you will really work hard all your life
そしたら一生本当に頑張れるよ
So psychologists say to understand yourself
だから心理学者は自分自身を理解せよと言っています
self-understanding is very important
自己理解はとても大切です
But you don't need to be so capable
でもそこまで有能である必要はない
you think i'm easy
あなたは私が簡単だと思っていますか
I just wanted to say it
ただ言いたかっただけです
he will have a good time
彼は楽しい時間を過ごすでしょう
I have friends like this
こんな友達いるよ
he really copes with his life
彼は自分の人生に本当に対処している
life is easy
人生は簡単です
but i just feel
でも私はただ感じている
It's a pity for the country and society
国にとっても社会にとっても残念なことだ
because he can
彼はできるから
he can contribute more
彼はもっと貢献できるだろう
So the speed you said you would
だからあなたが言ったスピードは
make it harder again
また難しくする
Progressive
プログレッシブ
just to make you feel like you've thought about it
考えたことがあると感じさせるためだけに
Okay, thank you
大丈夫ありがとう
I ask you professor
教授にお願いします
let's get away from that old man
あの老人から離れましょう
That means
つまり、
There is a saying in Taiwanese
台湾語にこんな諺があります
Very interesting to describe this time
今回の説明は非常に興味深いです
whoever despises you
あなたを軽蔑する人が誰でも
The sky is expensive
天空公貴
that way
そうやって
can you lead like this
このようにリードできますか
no i don't know
いいえ、わかりません
Every time I talk about the past
過去のことを話すたびに
Does that mean now
それは今という意味ですか
the whole old will
古い意志全体
just say that
それを言ってください
will lose dozens of memories
数十の記憶を失うことになる
this this this square
これ、これ、この広場
if nothing wrong
何も問題がなければ
So you say it and forget it
だからあなたはそれを言っても忘れます
if occasionally
たまになら
If it's like this often, he's wrong
こんなことがよくあるなら、彼は間違っている
Not all old people will be like this
すべての老人がこうなるわけではない
no
いいえ
he may be capable
他可能能力上
Universality is a bit poor
汎用性は少し悪い
But I won't say it and forget it
でもそれは言わないし忘れるよ
Forget about it, you really can't clean it up in the morning
忘れてください、朝は本当に掃除ができないのです
That is to say, dozens of memories cannot be remembered.
つまり、何十もの記憶を思い出すことはできません。
But it's been decades
でも何十年も経ちました
he can't remember
彼は思い出せない
That's because it's been decades
そうだよ、何十年も経ってから
The quality of the big guy is in the hard disk
偉人の資質はハードディスクにある
he can call out
彼は声をかけることができる
Just started to lose real symptoms
本当の症状が消え始めたばかり
the vast majority are
大多数は
You tell him what he can't remember first
あなたは彼が思い出せないことを最初に彼に話します
It's not that you just told me that you were going to tell me yesterday
昨日言ったばかりじゃないよ
I can't remember you telling him about the old days
あなたが彼に昔のことを話したのを思い出せません
is the beginning of the loss of symptoms
症状の消失の始まりです
to the end
最後まで
I can't find the year
年が見つからない
That's why he gave his son and daughter no recognition
だからこそ彼は息子と娘を認めなかった
yes
はい
is so
そうだね
still have a question
まだ質問があります
ask the professor
教授に聞く
that is sometimes
つまり時々
even myself
自分自身さえも
sometimes somewhere
時々どこかで
For example in the AAA circle
例えばAAAサークルでは
I'm enjoying what I'm going to
これからやることを楽しんでいます
but go there
でもそこに行きなさい
i want to take it out
取り出したいです
then what am i going to do
それで私は何をするつもりですか
forget
忘れる
it's strange to forget
忘れるのは奇妙だ
Go back to this AAA circle
この AAA サークルに戻る
just remember
覚えてね
that's what happens
それが起こるのです
there is a Q
Qがあります
there is a clue
手がかりがあります
because this kind of thing is
このようなことはあるので
I think sometimes people nowadays are
現代人は時々そう思うことがあると思います
too busy
あまりにも忙しい
too much distraction
気を散らしすぎます
If this happens to you occasionally
このようなことが時々起こる場合
it doesn't matter
それは問題ではありません
But what often happens
でも、よくあることは
Especially you have to remember that those things are
特に、これらのことは覚えておく必要があります。
you often use
あなたはよく使います
Didn't you say save it on the hard drive
ハードドライブに保存するって言いませんでしたか？
Need not
必要はありません
things you use in your daily life
日常生活で使うもの
But you often forget to say what you want
でも、言いたいことを言うのを忘れることが多い
often
頻繁
something is wrong
何かが間違っている
If it happens often, do you need to see a doctor?
頻繁に起こる場合は医師の診察が必要ですか?
i think you can
できると思います
You can forget to pull this off
これを外すのを忘れても大丈夫です
Because I'm not really a doctor
私は本当は医者ではないので
I'm not very light
私はあまり軽くありません
But there is something I will tell you
でも、一つ言っておきたいことがある
don't be so nervous
そんなに緊張しないでください
Some people often say that I just didn't know
よく「私が知らなかっただけ」と言う人がいますが、
where do i put my eyes
どこに目を置けばいいですか
I didn't just put it here
ここに置いただけじゃないよ
Why did I forget where to put it?
どうして置き場所を忘れてしまったのでしょうか？
That sometimes is not called forgetting
それは忘れとは言われないこともある
you want
あなたが欲しい
have you ever remembered
思い出したことがありますか
you forget
あなたは忘れています
We usually put our glasses away
私たちは普段メガネをしまっておきます
then do something else
それから何か他のことをしてください
you didn't even remember
あなたは覚えていませんでした
you didn't tell me yourself
あなた自身が私に言ったわけではありません
I'm keeping an eye on it and I'm putting it here in my diary
私はそれを観察しており、日記に載せています
then i go to do something else
それから私は何か他のことをしに行きます
take it back
それを取り戻す
no memory at all
まったく記憶がない
did not remember
覚えていませんでした
it's a drop
それはドロップです
so you don't come when they can't find
だから彼らが見つからないときは来ないでください
Some people go to match a messy entity
厄介な存在に合わせようとする人もいる
my eyes are silent
私の目は沈黙している
I don't think this is very good either
これもあまり良くないと思います
Because the more you look like this, the real
こう見えれば見るほど本物だから
the less you think about where you put it
どこに置くかを考えなくなるほど
So next time you put
それで、次に置くときは
one or two fixed places
1 つまたは 2 つの固定場所
you know where i am
私がどこにいるか知っていますか
we know here
私たちはここで知っています
next time you go there
次回そこに行くとき
If you put everything in those places
そこにすべてを置いたら
You often use this eye
この目をよく使いますね
but you can't remember
でもあなたは思い出せない
It's going to be a little troublesome like this
少し面倒なことになるだろう
that is to say, I have touched
つまり触ったということです
I think it's time for a speech
スピーチの時間だと思う
The academic affairs associate said
教務担当者が言いました
some he found in the fridge
彼が冷蔵庫で見つけたいくつか
No
いいえ
He went to the refrigerator to get something
彼は何かを取りに冷蔵庫へ行きました
get a drink and go
飲み物を買って行きましょう
change hands
手を変える
put your ice in
氷を入れてください
I think it's fun
楽しいと思います
Of course you can't find it, right?
もちろん見つからないですよね？
but you put it like this
でもあなたはこう言います
Actually, don't be afraid
実際、恐れることはありません
it's not your memory
それはあなたの記憶ではありません
It's because you didn't remember him at all
それはあなたが彼のことを全く覚えていなかったからです
something you want to remember
覚えておきたいこと
you forget
あなたは忘れています
can't remember
思い出せない
That's bad memory
それは嫌な思い出だ
Thank u
ありがとう
because of time
時間のせいで
wait there is a problem
待ってください、問題があります
We can also ask again
再度質問することもできます
ask that professor li
李教授に聞いてください
then i want to thank you all for coming
それでは、来てくれた皆さんに感謝したいと思います
Because I still need to announce
まだ発表しなきゃいけないから
Our Knowledge Feast in June
6月の知識の饗宴
Associate Researcher Chen Zhiru
准研究員 Chen Zhiru
Associate Research Fellow at our Institute of Sociology
社会学研究所准研究員
to say
言う
Tempest or New Fire Healer
テンペストまたは新しいファイアーヒーラー
Case Analysis of Collective Resistance in Contemporary China
現代中国における集団的抵抗の事例分析
Welcome everyone to participate
皆様のご参加を歓迎します
let's end then
それでは終わりにしましょう
We are talking about something wrong in this game
このゲームの何か問題について話しています
can stay
滞在できる
are we
私たちは
we say thank you again
私たちはもう一度ありがとうと言います
Eli Forward-Wing Pad
Eli フォワード ウイング パッド